- Previously on Lucifer...
- You're the Lord of Hell.
Amenadiel is right...
you are changing.
You betrayed me, Maze.
- Lucifer...
- I don't want to hear it. We're done.
Enjoying the life I gave you?
Do you want to go back?
Because I can make that happen.
Seems I'm dealing
with a bit of a mortality sitch.
I'm bleeding.
All I have to do is
wait for some pitiful thug
to end you, and
right back to Hell you go.
Who do you want me to kill?
Lucifer Morningstar deserves
everything he gets,
but I can't let you kill him.
It would seem that I'm saying no.
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
No. No.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, what have I done?
Don't worry, my
father's the forgiving sort.
Well, except when it comes to me.
Triple espresso or hair of the dog?
No.
Oh, right.
Both.
Please tell me, we didn't...
Did we ever.
And I'm pretty sure we
made Rosemary's baby.
Oh, Detective, it was extraordinary.
The heat, the gymnastics.
I mean, you had
moves that made even the Devil blush.
Oh, no, this is bad.
Whatever happened last night,
don't tell me, I'd rather not know.
What, that we didn't do the nasty?
We didn't?
Nope, I turned you down cold.
You, the guy who's been
trying to get me into the sack
since day one had a
chance to sleep with me,
and you did...?
Why-why am I naked?
What, you mean you
don't remember the part
where you passed out, woke up again,
shouted at me, "It's too hot
in this five-story hellhole,"
I believe it was,
then tore your clothes off and
proceeded to hog the bed?
I do that. Sometimes.
When I'm upset.
And you'd be upset, too, if
your ex dumped you by text.
No, I'd be relieved if Dan dumped me.
Even still,
it's very out of
character to see you so unhinged.
And out of character for me, too.
The whole "not wanting to
have sex with you" thing.
I mean, here's the strange part.
This gave me quite a rush.
Can't explain it.
I've been thinking about it all night.
Okay, last night was a fluke.
For both of us.
Never happened, leave it at that.
Right.
You snore, by the way.
Like an Albanian field wench!
Did you finally seal the
deal with your little detective?
If we were on speaking
terms, perhaps I'd fill you in.
Where are you going?
Why do you ask?
You still reporting back to my brother?
Lucifer...
No, do me a favor, Maze.
How about you let me lead my life,
and I'll let you lead yours, deal?
You can't be mad at me forever.
Oh, but I can.
It's one of the
luxuries of being the Devil.
Detective, I believe you left these
after our sleepover last night.
What's the hole at the back for?
Not mine.
Those are not mine.
More of a commando girl.
Fair enough.
Dearie me.
Someone woke up on
the wrong side of a .38.
Yeah, single gunshot
wound to the chest.
No wallet.
Tan marks where a ring
and a watch were lifted.
A staircase robbery.
Is that a thing now?
This is the Dunlear Foundation.
They help the homeless
and the underprivileged.
So, who's the dashing corpse?
Tim Dunlear himself, head
of the foundation,
former NBA star, notorious playboy.
He was into drugs, gambling, women.
My typical Wednesday.
But then he left pro ball and
he turned his life around.
He dedicated himself to philanthropy.
He was beloved.
Right, bad boy turned good.
It's interesting.
Are you Emmett Toussaint?
You found the body?
I'm Detective Decker. Can
you tell us what happened?
I volunteer for the foundation's
outreach program.
Came here to meet him, and
he was just lying here.
How did you know Mr. Dunlear?
He sponsored me to come to
L.A. after the earthquake in Haiti.
Tim was my mentor.
Handsome and saintly.
Did you see anyone else at the scene
or notice anything strange?
There was a guy outside.
He ran when he saw me.
I gave the cops a description.
Think he was homeless.
Did Mr. Dunlear ever speak of
a certain philanthropic high
after one of his selfless acts?
You know, for example,
say when he chose not to
sleep with a drunken woman?
What?
Did I say something wrong?
We are questioning a minor.
I'm sorry about your mentor.
We'll call you if we have
any more questions.
What? I just feel quite connected
to our victim.
You are nothing like Tim Dunlear.
Bad boy with a heart of gold?
I am everything like Tim.
May as well be solving my own murder.
Only you could turn a tragic death
into an excuse to talk about you.
Well, who else would I talk about?
Got these on sale.
Extra strong, UV resistant,
and still 30% off.
Do you really think
you're gonna get away with this?
Probably not.
I'll bet the SWAT team's about
to bust down the door any minute.
Not like there's much else going on
in a city of four million people.
As much as I hate Lucifer, I'm
not gonna let you kill him.
Oh, I'm not gonna do anything. No. Oh.
But you know who would want him dead?
Someone who's jealous.
Someone who hates the fact
that he's clearly got a
thing for his ex-wife.
Ooh.
Someone whose fingerprints I
put all over the murder weapon.
Sound like anyone you know, Dan?
Ooh.
Don't go anywhere.
My husband was so generous.
If they had just asked for help,
he would have given them anything.
What kind of person
would do something like this?
Well, how much time do you have?
Tim would be devastated to
know we've got to cancel
the fund-raising gala.
You're right, Kyle.
Well, we wouldn't want to
devastate our fallen hero.
The show must go on.
This is an active crime scene.
We can't have an event here.
No, that wouldn't be right.
Well, I just happen to own
the preeminent party
venue in Los Angeles.
You can hold your benefit at my club.
- I don't know.
- No, no, your husband
was a kindred spirit,
and I pledge to carry on his good work
and personally find...
and punish... his killer.
Tim always said "Tragedy brings sorrow
but also true good."
Aw.
Thank you.
You are so welcome.
If this was a robbery, our
perp's gonna want to cash in
before the cops get wind of this,
so I'll call the local pawn shops...
What is with you today?
It was rather benevolent of me,
offering up Lux, don't you think?
Well, one good deed doesn't
make you a saint.
Well, last I counted,
it was two good deeds.
But, uh, I'm not
feeling the same rush as before.
Perhaps I'm gonna have to up my game.
Whatever you say, St. Lucifer.
Oh, "St. Lucifer."
Suits me, don't you think?
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
It's funny, I've always
looked at do-gooders with pity.
Little did I know their dirty secret.
And what's that?
- Feels good to do good.
- Yes.
Good deeds do bring an
amount of personal satisfaction
to those who engage in them.
No, but I mean it's
like a literal rush, a high.
Have you ever mixed
cocaine and Molly with Pop Rocks?
It's nothing like
that. I'm just curious.
So you're feeling good about
not sleeping with Detective Decker.
Well, yes, and offering
Lux to the Dunlear Foundation,
not to mention
vowing to find Tim's killer.
You've identified
quite strongly with this man.
Yes. Yes, a man of honor, principle.
Hmm. You like the way being
good makes you feel.
- Mm.
- But true good needs
to come from a place of
selflessness, authenticity.
Well, of course.
I authentically want
people to applaud the real me.
The Devil gets a terrible rap.
So you care about
image, how you look to others.
And you're welcome.
Okay, my point is, it's wonderful
that you're evolving.
Right.
But goodness isn't a toy.
Well, the way I'm
going to play with it, it is.
I'm in between gigs.
I'm no thief, I'm an
actor, Louie DelGado.
I had an arc on Party
of Five, look me up.
I love L.A. Even the
homeless have an IMDb page.
You care to explain why you were
caught pawning Tim
Dunlear's championship ring?
Listen, more importantly, why
did you take it to a pawnshop?
The Dark Web has much better margins.
I swear I didn't do nothing.
Witnesses put you at the scene.
You're telling me this
wasn't a robbery gone wrong?
He was already dead, been
like that for a bit.
Rigor mortis had set in.
I also did a guest spot on CSI.
Ah.
Tim was my buddy,
one of the few people who treated
me like a human being.
Would your buddy have
approved of you stealing valuables
from his cold dead corpse?
Tim didn't care about stuff.
Would have wanted me to have that ring.
Give you the shirt off his back.
What about his wallet?
Uh, I was gonna return that.
Some kind of key card.
I have an alibi.
I was at a shelter on 7th.
Uh-huh. Keep an eye on Louie.
I'm gonna see if his story checks out.
I also know what it's
like to be without a home.
My father kicked me out.
It's very traumatic.
But, much like Tim Dunlear, I'd
like to do whatever it takes
to help you, so,
here, the shirt off my back.
Yeah.
And, uh, as you can see,
the Devil does indeed wear Prada.
Wow, thanks, brother.
Yes, disastrous
with those trousers, though.
Oh, what the hell?
As gratitude for telling us
everything you know.
And he's naked.
Another act
of selfless benevolence.
It's quite liberating, actually.
Oh, don't forget.
Dry-clean only.
His story checks out.
We need to get a full written statement.
And get our guy some lunch, okay?
No-no gluten
or-or dairy, okay?
Another good deed
but still no rush like before.
Am I doing this wrong?
In so many ways.
Oh?
You're not getting in my car like that.
Meet you at mine?
So, who do we suspect
of this grisly murder?
Maybe Mr. Dunlear wasn't
as saintly as he appeared.
Who knows who or
what he was involved with?
He wasn't always such a good man.
It's hard to shake your true nature.
Well, not really. Look at me.
Oh, no, I saw plenty.
- Thank you.
- Cheeky.
Oh, Lucifer, Detective.
I wasn't expecting you.
Yes, we have a few
more questions for you.
Yes, how are you holding up?
Doing my best.
One moment at a time.
Mrs. Dunlear,
can you think of any personal reason
why someone would
want to kill your husband?
I thought this was a robbery.
No, turns out
your husband was dead before
our homeless thespian
pilfered his valuables.
Did Tim have any enemies?
Anyone that would want to hurt him?
No, absolutely not.
Everybody loved Tim.
Will Fleming...
counsel for the
foundation and the Dunlears.
This won't
take long, Mr. Fleming.
Well, you're absolutely correct,
because my client is done here.
- Wha...?
- Oh.
Actually I'm
just here to talk to Vanessa
about the gala... is that, uh,
is that all right? Are you up to that?
Yes, of course.
Lovely.
So I know it's not a good time, Vanessa.
But I want to discuss...
My client is grieving.
You have any questions, you talk to me.
All right, can you establish
Vanessa's whereabouts
at the time of Tim's death?
Are you accusing my client of murder?
No, but one quarter of murders
are committed by family members.
Yes, and half by acquaintances.
Which gets to my next question.
Where were you the night of Tim's death?
Listen, you can look at me all you want.
But Tim came into contact with
a lot of people around this place.
Desperate people.
Why do I get the feeling you
have someone specific in mind?
Did you ever fight with Tim?
Last night.
You didn't tell me that earlier.
I was ashamed.
Tim told me I might not be receiving
the scholarship money he promised.
I got angry.
Said some things.
I was going to go apologize, but...
when I got there...
I'm gonna need to test
you for gunshot residue.
And get a full written statement.
Whatever you need.
First, I want you to tell me more about
Tim and his relationship
with Vanessa... what was it like?
Great...
when the cameras were on.
And when they were off?
Ah, Detective, you made it.
A little underdressed, but okay.
What happened with the orphan child?
We're holding him, waiting
on ballistics.
But he had a lot to say about
the Dunlears' perfect marriage.
Apparently Tim hadn't slept
at home in months.
Well, it's probably
all those good deeds.
So time-consuming.
Or... I was right.
And Tim was back to his old ways.
You know, that key
card we found in his wallet
was from a hotel, so maybe
he was cheating on Vanessa,
she found out,
- then decided to...
- Punish the cheating bastard
by pumping him full of lead.
Well, that's option "A."
Option "B" is the lawyer isn't
telling us everything he knows.
Option "C" is
an emotionally
distraught mistress did him in.
Ah, that old chestnut... if
I can't have him, no one can.
What did you get from Vanessa?
- Is that why we're here?
- Yes, yes.
She asked me to have lunch
with the golden donors of the foundation
on her behalf.
It's the least I could do.
Oh, the very least.
What better way to get
intel on a murder than a gaggle
of high-society frenemies?
- Oh.
- Ah!
Tim Dunlear
was a true humanitarian.
Oh, there's so few of us around.
And I have no one to
help me process my grief.
Can you believe my
therapist had the nerve
to go on maternity leave?
Oh, well, I'm here for you, Gayle.
You can tell me anything.
Oh.
Oh, ooh...
You are a good man.
Yeah, not quite the reaction
I was looking for, but,
uh, when in Rome.
To Tim Dunlear.
We all loved him.
Mm-hmm, some more than others.
So you heard about Donna Gray?
- Oh, yeah.
- So sad.
Throwing yourself at a
married man like that.
Mm, and when they
started sleeping together,
poor Vanessa.
Tim turned Donna down cold.
Not that it's any
of your business.
Oh.
Tight-lipped and angry.
Yes, well, with all that Botox,
I'm surprised she can chew at all.
This is taking too long...
maybe we should do your hypnotism,
eye-voodoo thing to get them talking.
Yes.
You would expect that sort of
behavior from me, wouldn't you?
Yeah, you making a
spectacle to help out a case.
Yeah, it's what you do.
Don't worry, Detective.
There'll be a spectacle.
These women
are lonely and unappreciated.
If I give them what they
want, they'll give us what we want.
Hello, ladies.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
Uh, you've all given so
generously over the years
to the Dunlear Foundation.
In honor of our fallen hero,
I now give you a gift
in return.
Me.
And he's breaking into song.
♪ No cares for me ♪
♪ I'm happy as I can be ♪
♪ I've learned to love and to live ♪
♪ Devil may care ♪
Gosh, you're lovely, aren't you?
♪ When the day is through ♪
♪ I'll suffer no regrets ♪
♪ I know that he who frets ♪
♪ Loses the night ♪
♪ For only a fool feels ♪
♪ He can hold back the dawn ♪
Don't hold back!
♪ He who's wise never tries ♪
- ♪ To revise what's past... ♪
- Stop it! Stop!
What is wrong with you?!
Why-why are you enjoying yourselves?!
Tim is dead!
Shame on you.
And shame on all of you.
And I give you option "D."
Let's go.
- I love you.
- Thank you.
It's true.
I loved him.
Kyle, Tim Dunlear was
a hero to all of us.
No, no.
You don't understand.
Tim and I were in love.
- Oh.
Right,
so Tim was cheating on
his wife with a man.
I did not see that coming.
The Devil usually has impeccable gaydar.
Tim was, uh, in denial
about his sexuality for years.
And then, um...
we met.
Hmm, that explains
why he was never at home
and all the secrecy.
Did you two ever meet at a hotel?
No.
No, that-that would've been too public.
Uh, we only ever met at my apartment.
Huh. What about Vanessa?
Did she know?
They, um,
you know, they-they had an arrangement.
Tim wanted it kept secret.
And Vanessa agreed.
She needed the Tim Dunlear brand.
Monogamy fails again.
So, if Tim didn't want
out of the closet,
were you aware of anyone
that would want to blackmail him?
Or threaten to go to the press?
No.
Um...
But Tim texted me this photo
for safekeeping.
I... I have no idea
what it means.
- Hmm.
- It's actually the last I ever
heard from him before...
Do you want another song?
If there's one thing I
know about kimchi fried rice,
it's that heat really kicks
things up a notch.
You almost died. You came back,
and this is what you do
with your second chance?
You know what happens when you die?
I can't say I do.
Well, if you've lived a life
like I did, you go to Hell.
Oh, yeah.
In my case, it was
for a couple of seconds.
Down there, though, it was years...
and years.
And there's a door just for you.
And inside, Hell
uses what you love against you.
For me, I love life.
Everything about
it. Got a hunger for it.
So...
they starved me.
No food.
No other people.
No nothing.
No TV.
Malcolm?
Hmm?
You need help.
You always were a scrappy one.
Ah.
Yeah.
I do need help.
Never to go back.
So I made a deal.
And all I got to do
is put a bullet in Lucifer.
I pull the trigger.
You take the fall.
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Five-second rule.
Teaching,
building,
creating.
I'm Tim Dunlear.
Together we can educate Haiti today
for their better tomorrow.
Mr. Fleming?
What are you doing here?
I understand you've been asking
some pretty invasive questions
at a luncheon.
I have reason to
believe that your client
knows more than she's letting
on about her husband's death.
Vanessa Dunlear's entire
world has fallen apart.
I mean, what kind of a
person targets a-a grieving woman?
A very rich grieving woman
who stands to
inherit her husband's estate.
Every cent that Tim had goes
back into that foundation.
Which you would know,
because now that Tim's
gone, you took control.
That's an interesting turn of events.
You are messing with the
wrong people, Detective.
Good people.
Back off.
You'd never know that Lux
was a den of iniquity, would you?
Well, as long as you don't look
too closely at the floors.
Will Fleming wants to scare me off?
Bring it on.
Question is, whether he's protecting
himself or Vanessa.
Or maybe they're just good people.
Because you're suddenly the authority?
Give me a break.
Detective, even if Vanessa is guilty,
this is a woman who's
denied herself carbs since the '90s
and stayed married to a gay man.
If she doesn't want to talk, she won't.
And as for their attorney,
well, he certainly doesn't strike me
as the confessional type. Okay.
Maybe I can't get them
to talk, but you can.
Come on.
I've seen you do it dozens of times.
No.
Not here. Not tonight.
Am I missing something?
I feel like you're
protecting our main suspects.
No, I'm just
thinking about the children.
You want to push pause on
a murder investigation
so you can have a party?
Detective, I made a promise.
The ladies, the-the foundation,
the proud nation of Haiti...
they're all depending on me
tonight.
Now, Tim Dunlear may be dead,
but his legacy lives on,
and right now he needs
to go change into his tux.
It's about the greater good, Detective.
The greater good would
be parking your ego
and helping catch the bad guy.
The old Lucifer would have known that.
Wh...
I miss him, by the way.
At least he had my back.
Detective!
Oh...
Glad someone's having a good night.
What are you doing here?
You've ruined my life.
The least I could do is ruin your night.
Enjoy your evening.
How'd you even find me, Maze?
Followed the sweet stench of failure.
Look, don't blame me for
your problems, all right?
It's not my fault
that you betrayed your boss.
My problems are your problems.
Which would be the only thing
that you and I have in common.
And so you came here because...
because you have
nowhere else to go?
Yes, I do.
I have lots of places to go.
Lots of places.
And because you have no
one else to talk to, either.
Says the angel sitting here
eating a medium rare steak
by himself.
What?
It's not like you
were going to drink it.
You're so boring.
I'm actually not boring.
I'm pretty exciting.
My definition of "excitement"
is fun.
Danger.
Sex.
Spontaneity.
You are none of those things.
Yes, I am.
Give me one example.
You know that story about
Lucifer and the goat?
Yeah?
No.
That was you?
That was me.
A whisper here,
a divine appearance there...
Word got around.
He hates the goat thing.
I know!
He could never figure out
where it came from.
You know, I've waited a
thousand years to tell someone that.
Leave the bottle.
Thanks for this, Kyle. I
know it's your job on the line.
Whatever it takes.
I want to find who did this.
Thank you.
So this here, this last text from Tim...
looks like it was from
Port-au-Prince.
Tim didn't tell me
he was going there.
It wasn't on his calendar.
Could he have traveled under the radar?
Sometimes he booked his own travel.
He-he had some buddies
who own private jets.
Sometimes they would travel as a group.
So if Tim stayed in a hotel there,
maybe that's why he had the key card.
Third-world technology.
Maybe that's why
we couldn't read the magnetic strip.
We do charity work in Port-au-Prince.
We raised money to buy
land to build a school.
Maybe that's what the
text of the barren field was.
That photo was from a few days ago.
The school would be almost
finished by now.
Unless it was never built.
Unless the money the foundation raised
went somewhere else.
Or to someone else.
Really?
That's your move?
You were planning to seduce me?
That is... truly desperate.
I'm not here to seduce you, Will.
But I do know what you desire.
What is it you think I desire,
Detective?
To do good.
To help people.
I did some research into you, Will,
and apparently, you don't charge
for your services here
at the foundation.
I make a nice living,
thanks to my corporate work.
Yeah, you protect your
clients like a bulldog,
but underneath it all, you're
a big softie, aren't you?
I don't need to take
money away from those kids.
No.
But Vanessa does.
What the hell does that mean?
I looked into a school
that was supposed to be built
with the foundation's
money in Port-au-Prince.
It doesn't exist.
What?
I think the money went elsewhere.
After all, Vanessa had a
hell of an expensive lifestyle
to keep up after her
husband left the NBA.
That is ridiculous.
Besides, non-profit financials
are a matter of public record.
They are.
But they're so
complicated, it would be pretty easy
to hide a few outgoing wire transfers.
Here. I think Tim Dunlear
looked into these
financials and figured it out.
So he flew to Pout Au
Prince to see for himself,
and when he realized
where the money went,
he confronted Vanessa
and she killed him.
That is pure speculation.
It is.
So help me get proof.
If Vanessa transferred money to herself,
it'll show up in her personal
financial records,
which you have access to.
You want me to violate my client's trust
based on a hunch?
You took this job to make a difference.
This foundation can still do good
the way Tim wanted it to.
If you help me.
Detective.
Is that you?
Hope you've come to your senses.
Well, that depends on
who you ask, Mr. Morningstar.
I'm here to murder you.
Well... that is a buzzkill.
I'm sorry.
Strange, disheveled gunman,
have we met?
Briefly.
Detective Malcolm Graham.
Ah, yes, of course!
The infamous Malcolm.
Tough times?
You here to steal my watch?
Well, there's no need.
You've caught me in a charitable mood.
You could also use a decent suit.
The closet's that way.
Thanks.
I'm still going to kill you.
Ah...
I should also mention
that if you pull that trigger,
it's a one-way ticket
to eternal damnation.
Hell?
Oh, I'm not going to Hell.
Now or ever again.
No?
See, I made a deal with an angel.
And I've got orders to take you out.
Your ass for mine.
Sorry, it's...
My holier-than-thou brother
has hired someone to kill me?
Well, this really is Opposite
Day, isn't it?
You know what, Malcolm?
It's nighttime now.
It's funny how things seem
so much clearer in the dark.
Is that all you got?
Interesting.
Most people wet themselves when
they see my nastier side.
Huh.
Well, most people
haven't been to Hell and back.
Rumor says
you're not immortal anymore.
That if I pull this trigger,
it's bye-bye, Devil.
Of course.
Right. And what do you get in return,
Malcolm?
Your brother doesn't kill me.
I stay out of Hell, live out my life.
I love life.
You've been duped, Malcolm.
Huh?
Angels can't take a mortal life.
It's Dad's rules.
Sorry.
And even if you do kill me...
what happens when you do die?
Because you will... eventually.
You'll still go back to Hell, Malcolm.
There's nothing
that my brother can do to prevent that.
What's that?
This?
This is my Pentecostal coin.
It's a subway token for
the damned, if you will.
I was going to use it to
get back to Hell eventually.
I suppose you could use
it to get out of Hell, too.
Could come in handy
for someone like you,
don't you think, Malcolm?
It's all yours if you don't shoot me.
One-time offer.
There you are.
Can't very well start our
party without our guest of honor.
Mrs. Dunlear.
Are you okay?
Yes, yes, I just
needed a little pick-me-up.
It's been an exhausting day.
Facing one's mortality will do that.
I think we'll all
deserve a vacation after tonight,
a chance to mourn Tim properly.
I fly out tomorrow.
One of those Swiss med spas
that masquerades as a resort?
No.
No, I own a small ranch
outside of Buenos Aires.
Lovely.
I knew some folks who moved to
Buenos Aires back in the day.
Oh. Good people?
Nazis. No extradition
treaty in Argentina.
Just a nasty bunch of
miscreants hiding in plain sight.
Gosh, they got away with murder.
You did kill your husband, didn't you?
No, that's absurd.
I have to admit, I'm
not entirely sure why,
but Detective Decker will figure it out.
She always does.
I loved him.
And Tim loved me.
Well, no, technically, he
loved your assistant, Kyle.
Yes, but I... I would never...
Tim was a good man.
He was selfless...
Yes.
Yes, he was.
Everybody loved Tim, and he
asked for nothing in return,
not even his own happiness.
Well, as the old saying goes,
you can't keep a good man down,
not even in death.
So how about we go downstairs,
see this night through, and then...
Oh, bloody hell.
Lucifer!
Where's Lucifer?
Lucifer Morningstar, where is he?
Out of the way.
Hey!
You're alive.
Yes.
Yes, it would appear
that way, wouldn't it?
What are you doing here?
I came to stop Malcolm; he's
planning to shoot you.
Malcolm?
No, no, this wasn't him.
He's taken care of.
He is?
How?
Well, I made him an
offer that he couldn't...
You know the line.
You look terrible, by the way.
Rough day at the office?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, you could say that.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I've got a charity to attend
and a killer to punish.
How do I look?
Pretty good, actually.
Yes, I thought as much.
Oh, have a drink.
Two, if you like.
Who says the Devil can't be charitable?
Thank you all so
much for your generosity.
I would also like to
thank our host, Mr. Morningstar.
He was going to say a few
words, but unfortunately he's been...
Right on time.
How are we all this evening, eh?
Such a well-preserved crowd.
Love your work, Dr. Broffman.
Tucking marvelous.
Right, we're all here to
honor Tim Dunlear's legacy,
and what better way to do
that than to reveal his killer?
Wouldn't you agree, Mrs. Dunlear?
Time to show your
friends your true colors.
Tell them all your nasty desires.
No need.
We already have everything,
how she embezzled
money from the foundation,
and when Tim found out
about it, you killed him.
Ah, see?
Told you she'd figure it out.
You have no proof.
Actually, we do.
We have
proof of the embezzlement,
and that's enough for probable cause.
Vanessa...
I earned that money.
I supported him when he left pro ball.
I let him sleep with my assistant.
- Oh.
- That money should go to me,
not those kids.
Tim was going to ruin everything.
I had to.
Now, doesn't that feel better?
Huh?
Vanessa Dunlear, you're under arrest
for the murder of Tim Dunlear.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
There it is again, that rush.
Looks like someone had a good night.
I know bed head when I see it.
We're talking again?
Well... life's too
short to hold grudges.
Doesn't mean all is forgiven, mind.
I mean, you'd have to do something
pretty extraordinary
to wipe this slate clean.
I had sex with your brother.
And that puts you in my
good graces how exactly?
Well, I was his inside
woman, and now I'm yours.
Yes, well, I suppose that
could come in handy,
especially since he
just tried to kill me.
What?!
- Wait, you were shot?
- Mm-hmm.
And you didn't bleed?
He hired a gunman.
I mean, I talked the chap out of it,
but then this demented socialite...
I mean, it's a long
story, but I survived,
which is more than can
be said for my Armani.
But I don't understand.
How could you still be alive?
Well, that is the question,
isn't it, Maze?
Why is it that sometimes I'm immortal...
and other times I'm all too human.
Oh, that's interesting.
What?
I need to go and test a theory.
Oh, and, um...
tread carefully, Maze.
May I come in?
Who? St. Lucifer or the Devil?
Yes, rest
assured, St. Lucifer's retired.
Really?
'Cause I just got a text
from Kyle saying that someone gave
money to Emmett
Toussaint's scholarship fund,
enough for a full ride.
An anonymous donor.
Well, good for Emmett.
Glad it worked out.
Mm-hmm.
- Listen, Detective, I...
- I want...
- Oh.
- Sorry.
No, you.
Um, I've been thinking a
lot about the other night,
why I showed up drunk to your place,
why you wouldn't sleep with me,
and I think us,
our thing,
maybe it goes beyond just work.
- Or sex.
- What sex?
Congratulations, the first
woman to give the Devil blue balls.
Anyhow,
I, uh, I just...
I can let my guard down with you.
I don't do that with anyone else.
You make me vulnerable.
And... maybe that's okay.
Detective...
if it's any consolation to your pride...
it appears you make me vulnerable, too.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net