- Previously on Lucifer...
- I'm going to remove
Pierce's immortal curse
so he can finally die.
I shall fly down to Hell,
pluck your brother's soul and
drop it into a vacant body.
This would make you innocent.
- Amenadiel's nice.
- If he were nice,
he wouldn't be sneaking around
behind my back with my friend.
When will you understand that
we were trying to protect you?!
I don't believe you.
I know this is scary,
but we need to start
- in your Hell.
- There are
so many things that Father
can still take away from you.
There is a bomb.
If they move, the whole thing blows.
I just wanted to say thank you again.
- Couldn't have done it without you.
- Without me,
you wouldn't have been in
danger in the first place.
If the detective had died,
it would have been my fault.
I know I promised
to help you end your curse,
but we need to dissolve
our unholy alliance.
The risk is too great.
I'll put it on.
Ladies and gentlemen, Axara!
♪ Boy ♪
♪ I just, I-I can't explain it. I... ♪
♪ I see her face ♪
♪ Everywhere ♪
♪ About two weeks ago ♪
♪ Remember that night
when you came on over? ♪
♪ I got a confession ♪
♪ I saw everything you wrote her ♪
♪ How could you call her baby? ♪
♪ I saw the pic she sent you ♪
♪ Why would you lie and tell
her that there's so much ♪
♪ We have been through ever since ♪
♪ That night... ♪
Oh, my God, Jill?
- Jill?
- Stay back! Everyone, stay back!
Jill?
Oh, Jill.
Help me!
Someone help!
Somebody help!
I've decided to take
myself out of the spotlight.
My Father's spotlight, to be exact.
So, no more killing Pierce
to get back at your dad?
Correct.
I mean, that whole "mark of
Kane" thing was so dreary,
so nihilistic.
There are far better
ways to spend my time.
- Oh?
- Yes.
Well, I could brew
my own artisanal beer.
Take a nude painting class.
Buy that pet shark I've always wanted.
Maybe you're taking a step
back because of the bomb scare
that threatened both you... and Chloe.
Don't be ridiculous.
We're in the line of
fire every day, Doctor.
I mean, it's all part of being heroes
- for the people.
- Don't get me wrong.
If the bomb was God targeting
Chloe for your defiance,
then maybe it's good
that you're quitting.
Well, quitting is a strong word.
I'm just saying,
sometimes we push
boundaries we shouldn't
and cause rifts with
people we care about.
It's only fair
we take our share of
responsibility in a conflict,
even if the other is...
somewhat irrational,
demonic, even.
Indeed. Nothing wrong
with dousing the flames of contention.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- Maybe even apologize.
- Well, let's not go crazy.
But perhaps I can stop poking
the bear that is my Father.
Get off his radar for a bit, you know?
Mellow out.
♪ I close my eyes ♪
♪ Only for a moment ♪
♪ And the moment's gone... ♪
What do you want, Lopez?
You know, I just noticed
that you may be a little blue.
So...
Ta-da!
To cheer you up.
No, it's not new kicks. It's better.
It's... a compliment box.
I went around the
precinct and asked everyone
to write a positive
little note about you.
- Why?
- So...
that whenever you're feeling down,
you can just pull one out,
and it'll perk you right up.
Like, maybe now would be a good time.
"Pierce has nice arms."
Well, agreed. You sure do.
"The lieutenant has really great arms."
Right again. Two arms, two compliments.
"Pierce...
is...
wicked smart, so funny,
generous and amazing."
Now that is a compliment.
It says I have really
nice arms, doesn't it?
Nah, nah, 'cause
that'd be really awkward
and weird, you and me here
talking about a third arm.
And, um, I need to go
check on a lab thingy.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've been trying so
hard to cheer up Pierce,
but this is some next level bro-wallow.
You got to get in
there and do something.
Yeah. I don't know.
- What? Why not?
- Well, it's just...
Pierce isn't really a fan of me.
Well, then this is your
chance to change that.
I mean, Dan, if anyone
knows what it feels like
to be in the crapper, it's you.
- Thank you.
- No.
What I mean is you can relate, okay?
But when you're down, you always,
always pull yourself back up.
You are positive dude numero uno.
Okay. I guess I could try.
Good luck.
You got this.
Hmm.
♪ All we are is
dust in the wind... ♪
Okay, I'm a little confused here.
One of the backup dancers
was dressed as Axara?
- Yeah. I don't really understand it, either.
- Yeah.
- It normally doesn't happen like that.
- I think
- she was looking to get...
- Okay, but you're the manager, correct?
Rohan Donahue, yeah.
So, here's the deal.
Axara and a backup dancer, Jill,
decided to switch positions last minute.
Maybe she felt the
act was getting boring.
You'll have to ask Axara for details.
We got her back to the
hotel as fast as possible.
So was this the first
time she had switched?
Yeah, she didn't say anything
to anyone on the crew.
Except for Jill, of course.
And no one knew, that means
Axara was the intended target.
Let's not jump to any conclusions
until we've explored all the angles.
We don't know if anyone was a target.
Maybe it was an accident.
It wasn't.
This is a piece of big-time
professional firework.
From far away: "Ooh!"
From up close: "Ah!"
Fireworks weren't even
part of Axara's show.
Let alone pointed
right at the spotlight.
Does this mean we're cancelling
the Asia and the Europe tours?
Let's not panic until we know
exactly what happened here.
Jill's dead, Rohan.
And it was supposed to be Axara.
Yes, which means the shadowy
assassin would likely try again.
And again,
until the butchery is done.
Statistically speaking.
- He's right.
- Okay.
As long as Axara's in the spotlight,
she has a target on her back.
Yes.
The spotlight is dangerous.
Who am I kidding?
I'm not mellow.
I'll never be able to take myself out
of my dad's spotlight, but...
I can take the detective out of mine.
And focus on other people.
What? What are you talking about?
Nothing.
You'll thank me later.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So you're Axara's bodyguard, are you?
Now, I've always had an interest
in the personal
protection business, Rob.
- Bob.
- Bob, right.
Is that short for "Robert"?
No.
Fascinating.
Oh, it's lovely getting
to know you like this.
Your hopes, your dreams. Hmm?
Been working out as well.
Are you coming?
Uh, no, I'm not really interested in you
and what you're doing. I
think I'm just gonna stay here
and chat to my new friend, Rob.
- Bob.
Right. Bob.
Big fan of old Bobby here.
In fact, if someone were wondering about
my list of favorite people,
Bob might just be at the top.
Really?
Oh, most definitely.
We should go upstairs.
Thank you, Bobby.
I thought rock stars
only got the best weed.
It's sage.
After what happened to
Jill, I'm smudging my space,
and my heart.
And my lungs.
It actually changes
the ionic composition
of the air and reduces
the body's stress
response to tragic events.
Oh, such compassion
from one so young.
Please, tell me more.
Can you think of anyone who
may have wanted to hurt you?
You should check Axara's social media.
So many obsessed crazies.
Love you, Cece.
And she makes a mean turmeric smoothie.
Wait, speaking of mean,
there was one guy who
did kind of threaten me.
I mean, I didn't take
it seriously at the time
because he's a bit of a diva, but...
- Patrick.
And who might Patrick be?
My ex-backup singer.
Really toxic individual.
Rohan fired him last week, and
like I said, he's a drama queen.
But he said something
like, uh,
"I hope Axara dies a
horrible, painful death."
Yes.
Mm, mm.
Suppose it might be worth a glance.
Maze, it's-it's me.
Linda.
Come on, Maze, I...
I brought you a gift to,
you know, bury the hatchet.
I don't want to lose you, Maze.
And so,
I lost Amenadiel.
No man is worth what we have.
Please, just hear me out.
Oh, excuse us, I think we're
in the wrong interrogation room.
You're looking for Patrick Manning?
Yes.
- That's me, honey.
- Wow.
I see someone stole
some of Axara's spotlight
and fishnets as severance pay.
Why am I here?
I'll ask the questions, Patty.
Oh, I always knew Cher was a feisty one.
I'm Donovan McCann, Patrick's lawyer.
So, why is he here?
We believe that Patrick made
an attempt on Axara's life last night.
Killed a backup dancer by mistake.
- Say what?
- We know that you still
had the backstage security pass,
which means access and motive.
Yes, cold-blooded retaliation
- for your recent firing.
- Firing?
That's bananas.
So you're saying you didn't try
and take Axara out with a bang?
Course not.
Do I hate her?
Yes.
It was a bitch to work for that bitch...
The long hours, never getting credit...
But she did not fire me.
I quit.
That's not the story
her people are telling.
I bet. Those sycophants
will say anything
to protect her fragile ego.
Well, Patrick. Patty.
If you didn't want Axara dead, tell me:
what did you desire?
Uh... to be Axara.
But my version.
A better version.
Which is why I could
never want her dead.
How could I compete with
her if she was kaput?
Yes.
Where were you last night?
On stage.
Performing my act at
the Hideaway in WeHo.
After which, she was mobbed
by fans in the parking lot.
Tuesday's the new Friday
now that Patty's doing Axara.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ask around.
Aw, so sweet.
Donovan was right about last night.
It was cray-cray at the Hideaway.
Everyone wants a piece of Axara 2.0.
You wouldn't believe
the obsessive wannabes.
- Sad.
- It's sad.
Axara has more followers than the Pope.
"You are my life, I would
do anything to meet you.
Literally anything."
Gosh, I can't think of
anyone I care about that much.
Except for Miss Lopez.
World's Greatest
Forensic Scientist?
Oh, my gosh.
That is so sweet.
Wait. Did I miss my birthday?
Well, every day's a celebration
when you're around, darling.
Mwah!
Anyway.
When obsessed people don't
have their love reciprocated,
sometimes they snap.
Well, I've gone through them all,
and on a scale of #ILoveYouAxara
to #IWantToLivelnYourSpleen,
there's, like, a zillion suspects.
A zillion and one if you count me.
You weren't even aware
of her until this case.
Okay, name your favorite song.
Well, um, there's so many.
Anyway, we're not just
looking for a crazy fan,
we need someone who
had an all-access pass.
Well, Axara's assistant let me check out
- all of her social media accounts.
- Mm-hmm.
And apparently, she held
an online contest last week.
Winner won a VIP pass to
the Hollywood Bowl show.
Meet our winner: Benny Parker.
And these are some of his tweets.
"I can't wait for our love to be real."
"I wil make you feel the same way."
"You and I will be together forever."
That's subtle.
Sounds like Prince Charming
needs some attention from the LAPD.
Right.
Thank you, Miss Lopez.
I mean...
Oh, no, poor Pauline.
Pauline?
My friend who works the
intake desk at the precinct.
I'm helping her through a bad breakup.
We've grown quite close since yesterday.
Mm-hmm. Right.
I know what you're doing.
Our bomb scare made you realize
just how dangerous this job is.
And that you and I
could lose each other.
At any time.
So you're focusing on other people,
you're keeping your distance
as a way of protecting yourself.
And you know what, Lucifer?
That's cool.
If you need to "reverse-Oprah" me
just to feel less afraid,
then by all means, knock yourself out.
What? I am not afraid.
Just realized I've been
a tad myopic lately.
- Why not spread the love?
- Hmm.
I mean, everyone
deserves a little Lucifer.
How generous of you.
Thank you very much.
After me.
Benny Parker, LAPD.
Seems I'm not the only one ignoring you.
Perhaps you're just not
that interesting, Detective.
Benny?
Benny.
Well, talk about a dead end.
"Axara's art celebrates life.
I tarnished it with death.
I have no right to stay in her world.
I lived for Axara.
Now I die for her.
Benny."
Wow.
I hope that no one
ever loves me that much.
So, did the M.E. confirm
that it's suicide?
Still running the autopsy report,
but the bottle of sleeping pills
found in his hand, half empty.
Right and factor in Benny's VIP
pass which means he had access.
Yeah, it means that Benny
had tons of time and opportunity
to plant the firework that killed Jill.
A textbook post-murder
guilt-driven suicide.
A little too textbook if you ask me.
Oh, look what just arrived.
Who wants a T-shirt? Here you go.
- And, oh, one for you.
- Nice.
One for you.
Definitely for you.
What you can't fix,
decorate, am I right?
Ah!
Miss Lopez.
Aw.
What is all this?
Axara swag.
Thank you gifts for solving the case.
Apparently, she'd have come in person,
but she's busy rehearsing
for her rescheduled show at the Bowl.
Well, technically, the case isn't closed
- till we get the final autopsy report.
- Exactly.
And until then, it's LAPD jurisdiction.
Which means no shows.
Well, I'm afraid you'll
have to take it up
with the police commissioner
'cause apparently,
he and Axara are poker
buddies. It's all be sorted.
Oh, hello.
An Axara bobblehead.
♪ I'm not gonna die no more. ♪
Who's deserving of this little, uh...
Ah! My good friend,
Mr. Janitor.
That should cheer you up.
I think you'll be very proud.
I forced myself to
speak to a coworker who
has terrible breath.
It was probably only for a few minutes,
but it seemed like a decade.
Hello, I'm trying to
compliment my... you.
Clearly, something is on your mind.
Come on, I'm all ears.
I am so sorry.
Um, but you're paying
me to listen, so...
Well, yes. But the whole
reason that I'm here
is to learn to be less self-centered.
Okay, um...
Okay, fine.
Um, I'm, I'm just having
a wee bit of a conflict
with a, with a friend of mine.
Conflict? My specialty.
Mediating... conflict, I mean.
Let me help you.
Uh, that's very nice.
It's a very nice offer, but...
I know. And it feels so strange. It's...
I feel so good, it's like I'm floating.
Although that might...
might be the three
gimlets I had at lunch.
So, yes?
Uh...
Oh, my God. Chloe.
Okay, so you know how you thought
Axara's superfan's "suicide"
was a little too neatly wrapped up?
- Mm-hmm.
- You just won the super
totally right hunch
of the millennia award.
- So Benny's not our guy?
- No.
Benny died the day before
that firework exploded.
So Benny is not our killer.
He's our first murder victim.
So Benny's suicide was staged
before the attack at the Bowl.
Yeah. A frame job to cover
up the real killer's tracks
which means major pre-meditation.
And that Axara's still
in serious danger.
The killer's still out there.
Exactly.
This month's winner is...
Pauline.
And I think we can
all agree that Pauline
deserves her place in the spotlight
far more than others.
So if you'd all like to
raise a glass, if you
have one, to Pauline.
Lucifer knows she's a temp, right?
- Yeah, just tell him to meet me in the car.
- Yeah.
I don't know exactly
what you're going through,
but I've been there.
That very stool, actually.
Have you, Espinoza?
You know, talking about it might help.
You know, really opening up to someone.
I mean, that's what...
that's what I did.
And now everything's coming up Dan.
No, seriously, man, I'm happy.
You know, I'm-I'm ready to start dating.
Hell, you and I are even friends.
Friendlier.
I guess I could try.
Lay it on me.
I'm here for you, bro.
It's just life, you know?
It's like this eternal wasteland
of meaningless existence,
a dark void staring down at you
like a beaten dog scrounging
on the side of the road,
just waiting to get mowed down
by the next tsunami of crap.
Wow.
Hmm.
Maybe we all are just dust in the wind.
I am not cancelling my show.
Well, it turns out
that your troubled fan
was framed for Jill's murder.
So, with the killer still out there,
I can't let you perform tomorrow night.
Detective, if I hid under a rock
every time there was an issue,
I'd still be doing bar mitzvahs.
Also, you'd be under a
rock. Most unpleasant.
Okay.
Detective.
Now, I say we let Pinhead sing.
I mean, after all, some people
are just destined to
be in the spotlight.
Others not. Like you, for example.
So not helping.
You know, maybe you
should wait in the car.
You know what? Maybe you should both go.
I assure you, I'm fine.
Detective, what are you doing?!
This is...
no time for heroics.
Not that I care.
Building searched. All clear.
You poor, poor dear.
Can I get you something? Some tea?
More face needles, perhaps?
Uh, I'm fine, your partner's
actually the one with the medic.
Who?
Oh, her.
No, that's, uh, that's just a scratch.
No, it's you
that I'm focused on.
Okay, great. Thank you.
Okay, so I have your
security team in place.
For tomorrow's show, right?
Smart to beef things up.
Yeah, I don't think you understand.
There's no show.
While you're in danger, you're under
24-hour LAPD protection, led by me.
- That's ridiculous.
- Agreed.
She's a terrible choice.
I'll do it.
Look what we found in the laundry chute.
I'm gonna head back to the
homestead to expedite ballistics.
- You want to come?
- Excellent plan.
Why don't you go with Miss Lopez,
and I will keep you safe,
you little gem.
So you're gonna be my bodyguard?
Are you even a real cop?
Consultant, actually.
But I can assure you
that my penthouse has
top-notch security.
And every other amenity
you could possibly desire.
Hmm.
We'll see.
Come on, girls.
What a treasure.
Okay,
the only reason I'm agreeing
to this is hiding Axara
at your penthouse is
an unpredictable choice.
But, listen, if there's
even the slightest hint
that she is unsafe,
your duties are revoked.
Right.
What?
Just, you said "duties."
Come on.
♪ About two weeks ago ♪
♪ Remember that night
when you came on over ♪
♪ I got a confession ♪
♪ I saw everything you wrote her ♪
♪ How could you call her baby? ♪
♪ I saw the pics she sent you ♪
♪ Why would you lie
and tell her that... ♪
Bravo, Miss Axara.
Yes, I adore your shaky groove thing.
And I'm sure my custom
- Italian leather settee does, too.
- Sorry,
I need to rehearse.
Right, yes, of course. Of course.
Whatever you need.
- Help me.
- Right, uh, chaps,
why don't you, um...
you wait downstairs.
I've got this.
- Thank you, Rob.
- Bob.
Bob. Bob, yes.
Now, please tell me,
how can I better focus
my attention on you?
Mm...
Maybe you can make yourself useful.
Unless that's just a prop.
Prop? Please.
Mozart, Liberace, Elton.
- Who?
- All the greats were my pupils.
But none as bright as you, of course.
Whatever.
Right.
"C."
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Don't let it happen again. ♪
♪ I won't. ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La... ♪
Voice of an angel.
God, it would be if your
A-flat wasn't out of tune.
I beg your pardon?
Perhaps it's you who's...
whose perfect pitch
allows you to hear what others...
cannot.
- Um...
- Hmm.
You know what, never mind.
I need a break anyway.
Is this my smoothie stuff?
Yes. Yes, but, uh, please,
allow me to shower you
with my culinary expertise.
Right.
W-Wait, are... No, no, no.
Aren't you gonna wash them first?
And rinse off all the
nutrients? Don't be silly.
Uh... Hold on.
Wh-Where's my fresh turmeric?
You can't make it without
the right ingredients.
I couldn't agree more.
Just-just stop. Just let me do it.
- Please, forget it.
- I will...
You don't even know what you're doing.
Do this, Miss Axara!
You've got to be kidding me.
Everyone loves Axara.
What kind of psycho
would want to gun her down
in cold blood like that?
It's you.
- What?
- The gun
that we found at the Roosevelt,
turns out that it's registered to you.
Oh, this is insane.
I mean, that looks like my gun.
I keep it in the tour
bus for protection.
- But someone must've stolen it.
- We also uncovered
the insurance policy that
you took out on Axara.
Apparently, if anything happens to her,
you get a huge chunk of change.
Is that also insane?
First of all,
I would die if anything
happened to that girl.
Secondly, all managers have
insurance policies like that.
But, trust me,
the payout is nothing compared
to managing an entire career.
Why would I kill the goose for one egg?
I don't know. Maybe the goose
is a pain in the ass.
Okay.
Unless you've got something
else to say, I'm leaving.
I do have something else to say.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Jill Murray, Benny Parker,
and the attempted murder of Axara.
No!
Wait.
We will start by stating our grievances.
Who would like to go first?
She lied and betrayed me.
Next.
Brave start, Mazikeen.
And you, Doctor?
Well, no grievances.
Um, Maze is right.
I hid the truth, which was
a betrayal of our friendship.
And if I could take
it all back, I would.
But I can't.
So, all I can do is say...
I'm sorry.
And I miss you, Maze.
Thank you,
Doctor. That was really heartfelt.
And now is there anything that...
you'd like to apologize for, Mazikeen?
She just said she boned my ex.
I didn't do anything.
Well, it always takes two to tango.
Yeah, Linda and Amenadiel.
One, two, naked tango.
Me, screwed.
Resolving conflict means,
uh, accepting culpability on both sides.
If you don't let all
the icky feelings out,
things tend to fester,
and turn gangrenous, and, well...
nobody likes losing a limb.
Not true.
And I didn't do crap.
She called dibs.
On someone she doesn't
even have feelings for.
I'm a demon, Linda.
What do you expect?
You can't admit to a
single thing you did wrong?
I've done a lot of things wrong.
Like, a lot.
But at least I don't
claim to be the good one.
Pretend to stand on
some moral high ground.
You know, despite all
the books you've read,
all the degrees on your wall,
you forgot the one rule that matters.
Hos before bros.
Well, it's pretty tricky
to follow that rule
when you seem to have slept
with, oh, half of Los Angeles.
And yet, you begrudge me
the one man I've cared about
in a really long time.
And yet, I still gave him up.
That's how much I care
about our friendship.
Go... to... hell.
Okay. Great start.
Um, all part of the process.
Good time for a breather?
We're done.
Okay.
What on earth do you think you're doing?
You. Get naked.
I beg your pardon?
You said you wanted to
focus your attention on me.
Well, yes, but, uh...
And I always have sex
the night before a show.
It... it calms me.
Well, I'm sorry, but you'd have
to tie me down with steel chains
to have sex with you.
I'd be up for that.
No! What... it wasn't a suggestion!
Demanding. I like it.
- Miss Axara.
- Uh-huh?
- I love sex.
- What a coincidence. Me, too.
But, and this may be a first...
Okay.
I'm really not in the mood.
You know what?
I don't think you like me.
Really?
Whatever gave you that impression?
But... but everybody likes me.
Apart from the person
who tried to rocket you
- into a bloody red glare.
- Okay.
If you don't like me,
why were you so hell-bent
on being my bodyguard?
Because I'm trying to take my focus off
someone very dear to me.
But... a friend, actually.
Well, no, indeed, more a coworker.
Oh.
The detective you work with?
How did you...
I may be a self-centered
diva, but I have eyes.
Why are you trying to convince yourself
that you don't like her?
I'm not trying to convince my...
It's not me I'm trying to convince.
It's my Father.
I defied Him,
and He's big on that "eye
for an eye" sort of thing.
So I'm afraid that
he's gonna come after...
the things that I care about the most.
Well, you're a cop, sort of.
Get a restraining order or something.
Well, I'm afraid it's not that simple.
Dad's all-powerful.
Works in government?
Mm, rules the universe.
Frickin' politicians.
Well, hey, if it helps,
I know how you feel.
After what happened at my show,
it seems like everyone's trying
to take away the thing
I care about the most.
What? Fresh turmeric?
Funny. Funny, but no.
Music.
Ah.
But here's the deal.
You can't let anyone come in between you
and the things you're
passionate about in this life.
Or it ain't worth living.
Well. Thank you, my self-centered diva,
for your counsel.
It's duly noted.
Hey, I don't know about you,
but I could use a drink.
Oh, well now you are
talking my language.
Long as it's not orange, right?
Right.
Lovely.
I wasn't sure if you're
a single malt girl...
Bugger.
Epic toxicology report.
It turns out the manager
didn't just kill Benny,
he tortured him, too.
I mean, it's bad enough
that he made him take
all those sleeping
pills, but to force him
to eat all that stuff, too?
I mean, that is just cruel, man.
Wait, so what does this mean here?
Oh, right, sorry, yeah.
It's the chemical compounds.
So first, he fed Benny raw turmeric.
- Hmm.
- And kale.
A lot of kale.
And then, a boatload of spirulina.
But this all sounds like
ingredients for a smoothie.
Yeah, smoothie of death.
No, I mean, the pills.
It could've been blended into a smoothie
like the one that Axara drinks.
Be a good way to disguise the taste.
You know what? I don't think
the manager's the killer.
Beard-to-misery quotient.
It's a science, man.
After my divorce, I went
for the old Walter White.
Whatever you do, do not go full Hagrid.
Kenny Rogers, tops.
Oh, hey, uh, a buddy of mine's here.
He's a real "glass
half full" kind of guy.
He actually pulled me
out of a dark spot once.
Hey.
Maybe he can help you out.
Amenadiel.
Pierce.
Or not.
Uh, since you guys
obviously already know each other,
how about I just give you
some time to catch up? Hmm?
Yeah, I saw a food truck
on the way in. I'm just
gonna grab myself a burger.
Protein style.
Something... Yeah. Okay.
I'm gonna be back later.
I can't allow you to defy my father
or drag my brother
into one of your schemes
to remove your mark. This ends now.
Okay.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Look, I'm way ahead of you.
I got my hopes up
thinking that Decker was
the key, and then Lucifer.
But that's what the Sinnerman thought.
Then I thought resurrecting
Abel could end my curse.
But I made a mistake.
I was wrong.
'Cause here I am, alive and well.
Well, alive and miserable, actually.
So I'm done.
Finito.
I quit.
You happy?
Yes.
Yes,
because this means I did it.
I destroyed your alliance with Lucifer.
I prevented you from defying my father.
I passed my test.
If you passed your test,
why don't you have your wings back?
Well, maybe my test has multiple parts.
Um, if so, that's okay.
It's God's will.
- Right?
- How do you do that?
How do you stay so positive?
It's called faith, Pierce.
See, I spent a lot of
time doubting myself,
but now I realize that
it's about the journey,
not the destination.
How could you possibly
have any faith or hope
when you're in a loop
of endless suffering?
♪ At first I was afraid ♪
♪ I was petrified ♪
♪ Kept thinking I could never live ♪
♪ Without you by my side ♪
- ♪ Then I spent so many nights ♪
- Bloody hell.
♪ Thinking how you did me wrong... ♪
- Isn't she supposed to be on lockdown?
- Uh...
- I'm calling Chloe.
- No! No, I mean,
no need to get the detective involved.
I've got this.
♪ And now you're back
from outer space ♪
♪ I just walked in
to find you here ♪
♪ With that sad look
across your face ♪
♪ I should have changed
that stupid lock... ♪
Go back upstairs.
You're in danger.
Give me the microphone.
Go on, now, go.
♪ Walk out the door ♪
♪ Just turn around now ♪
♪ 'Cause you're not
welcome anymore ♪
♪ Weren't you the one
who tried to hurt me ♪
♪ With good-bye... ♪
Did you think I'd crumble, hmm?
♪ Did you think I'd
lay down and die? ♪
♪ Oh, no, not I ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
♪ Oh, as long as I
know how to love ♪
♪ I know I'm still alive ♪
♪ I've got all my life to live ♪
♪ And I've got all my love to give ♪
♪ And I'll survive ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey... ♪
Give me the microphone.
♪ 'Cause you're not
welcome anymore ♪
♪ Weren't you the one who tried
to break me with good-bye? ♪
♪ Think I'd crumble? ♪
♪ Did you think I'd
lay down and die? ♪
♪ Oh, no, not I ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
♪ Oh, as long as I
know how to love ♪
♪ I know I'll stay alive ♪
♪ I've got all my life to live ♪
♪ I've got all my love to give ♪
♪ And I'll survive ♪
♪ I will survive ♪
♪ Hey, hey. ♪
See?
How could I ever leave this?
No one's ever gonna scare
me out of the spotlight.
Ever.
Yeah? Try me. Come on.
You.
You were supposed to keep her safe.
No offense, darling, but
you're the one with a knife.
What's with the knife, Cece?
You're gonna hurt someone.
Does it even matter?
Two people are dead, you were shot at,
and you still won't stop.
Don't you see the danger you're in?
Again, am I the only one
who sees the irony here?
You said you would take a
break after the L.A. shows
and then you added Asia
and Europe to the tour.
That's two more years.
- So?
- So?!
That's two more years now.
And then another two and another two.
When does it end?
Never.
Hopefully.
I am tired of sharing you, Axara.
Remember high school?
Before all of this.
It was just you and me,
singing along to Beyoncé.
Well, you would sing,
I-I would just watch
and eat cookie dough.
I want that.
You have to know by now.
I love you.
Love me?
Oh, my God, Cece, what did you do?
She was trying to protect you.
Force you out of the spotlight
by any means necessary.
Even murder?
I-I didn't know what else to do.
You almost killed me.
How is that protecting me?
She was never trying to kill you.
Oh, what is she doing here?
Cece ran your social media.
It was easy for her to
start an account as you
and access all of your private texts.
So you knew about the
choreography switch.
I just wanted to scare you.
I'm never gonna stop singing, Cece.
Not even for me?
My music means more to me than anything.
You have to know that by now.
Drop the knife, Cece, it's over.
No.
No!
I just wanted her to be safe.
I know you did.
Well, who's the heroic one, now?
- What?
- Oh, my God. Lucifer, are you okay?
Why wouldn't I be okay?
Oh.
Oh, God, whatever you
do, don't pull it...
out!
Oops.
What were you thinking,
tackling somebody with a knife?
It's not me I was
worried about, Detective.
Lucifer.
You see, it's like I was saying, Pierce.
You got to have faith
because life can surprise you.
Now, if my brother,
the Devil, can have that...
Maybe I can, too.
God.
Hey, look at you, buddy.
Seems like someone's feeling better.
Okay.
Hi.
Lieutenant.
Congratulations on another solve.
Thank you.
Thanks, I appreciate that.
I'm just glad Axara's okay.
Well, I guess more than okay.
Her show's back on for the night
and she sent me two VIP
tickets to say thank you.
Well, you deserve them.
So, who are you taking?
Oh, I don't know. It's just...
I thought you'd never ask.
Oh.
Yeah.
Sure. Yeah, why not?
- Great, I'll see you later.
- Okay.
Morning, Detective.
- What?
You sure you don't want
to throw a surprise party
for the guy in evidence lockup?
Ah, right, yes, I
suppose I deserve that.
No, no, I am back to status quo.
- Hmm.
- Since I realized,
ultimately, I can't control you
or the world around
you, for that matter.
So there's no point trying to extinguish
the proverbial spotlight, is there?
I may just have to take a knife
to the chest every now and then.
Right.
Hello.
Tickets for Axara's show. Tonight?
Excellent.
Right, what time shall I pick you up?
Um...
Well...
it didn't seem like
you were that interested
in hanging out with me lately,
so Pierce and I are gonna go together.
Oh. Right, yeah, of course.
Of course. Well...
have fun.
I've heard she's amazing live.
♪ Da, da, da, da, da ♪
Uh...
♪ Da, da, da ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da, da ♪
♪ Well, I woke up ♪
♪ Tossing and turning ♪
♪ An unfamiliar
fire's been burning ♪
♪ And I don't know ♪
♪ How to feel ♪
♪ I'm not used to real ♪
♪ It's too real ♪
♪ For more than two
years I've been lonely ♪
♪ And then you came around ♪
♪ Ever so slowly ♪
♪ When I needed it most ♪
♪ You just hold me ♪
♪ And then you'd unfold me ♪
♪ Every layer ♪
♪ I don't want to run from it ♪
♪ This is the happiest
I've ever been ♪
♪ I'd rather escape
with these memories ♪
♪ Than worry about losing you ♪
♪ No reg, no reg, no
reg, no regular love ♪
♪ No reg, no reg, no reg ♪
♪ No regular love ♪
♪ No reg, no reg ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da, da ♪
♪ Da, da, da, da, da,
da, da, da, da, da... ♪
I think I've made a horrible mistake.
♪ No reg, no reg, no regular love. ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net