Previously on Lucifer.
Lucifer Morningstar..
Is that a stage name or something?
God-given, I'm afraid.
Your return to the Underworld
has been requested.
Remind Dad that I quit Hell
because I was sick and tired
of playing a part in his play.
Oh, don't say it. Come on, don't say it.
I'm now an official
civilian consultant for the LAPD.
I want what's best for Lucifer.
Then give me something
that I can use against Lucifer,
and I'll make sure you're
both back where you belong.
He doesn't confide in me anymore.
But there is someone he
does talk to... a doctor.
Hello there, neighbor.
I actually need someone to
confide in about a patient.
And hey, listen, if
you have any patients
- you need to talk about...
- You have no idea.
Just shoot me, Detective, please,
because maybe you'll finally realize...
You're bleeding.
What's happening to me?
You're changing, becoming vulnerable.
Maybe even...  mortal.
Oh, Mazie. I know that you'll
always protect me.
No matter how mortal I
become, the Devil can depend on that.
_
♪ Oh, sinner man, where
you gonna run to? ♪
♪ Sinner man, where
♪ Where you gonna run
to, all along them days? ♪
♪ Well, I run to the rock ♪
♪ Please hide me,
I run to the rock ♪
♪ Please hide me, all
along them days ♪
♪ But the rock cried
out, "I can't hide you" ♪
♪ The rock cried out...
Where you got this one going to?
San Diego.
Who gave that order?
♪ All along them days ♪
♪ So I ran to the Devil ♪
♪ He was waitin', I
ran to the Devil ♪
♪ He was waitin' ♪
♪ I ran to the Devil ♪
♪ All along them days ♪
♪ And I cried, "Power..." ♪
Yeah, yeah, Pete. Erwin here, 413.
I got a guy bringing down
the Morningstar thing here.
♪ Lord ♪
♪ Bring down the power, Lord ♪
♪ Bring down... ♪
Erwin,
what's going on? Are you okay?
♪ Power... to... the... ♪
♪ Lord...! ♪
What made you
think you'd get away with it?
If you come clean
now, I'll go easy on you.
So, tell me...
did you eat...
the chocolate cake?
No, Mommy.
I'm sorry.
It's just cake, Chloe.
Cake is so not the point, Dan.
This is about honesty
and personal responsibility.
Fine.
I got this.
Hey, Monkey.
Do you remember when we had that talk
and we said that
lying is a really bad thing?
Well,
some of your birthday cake is missing.
Now, I didn't eat it,
and we know Mommy didn't eat it, so...
is there something you want to tell us?
I ate it.
Mm-hmm.
But Lucifer said it was okay.
Oh, really?
He said, if you really want
to do something, you should.
And I really wanted to
eat some chocolate cake.
Huh. That's...
interesting.
Why don't you go grab your stuff.
Oh, I am so glad to
hear advice from Lucifer
is on the personal responsibility
lesson plan.
Dan, it's not what you think.
You know what, Chloe?
Your private life is
none of my business,
but when it comes to Trixie...
keep Lucifer out of it.
Decker.
Yeah, yeah. I'll hold.
Okay, just don't forget
tomorrow night's Taco Tuesday, okay?
- I can't do it.
- Why?
I'm working a stakeout in Van Nuys.
We agreed on planned
family time so that Trixie
can maintain some
normalcy during the separation.
I know, but... this is important.
I thought you wanted to work things out.
I don't have a choice,
Chloe. This is work.
Yeah, I've never heard that one before.
Yeah.
Long Beach?
Okay, I got it.
Thanks.
You know,
when Trixie asks where you are tomorrow,
I'll be sure to tell her
that something important came up.
Oh, Lucifer.
I brought the after...
after party.
Meet Brittany...
and Brittany.
Wow.
Hello, Brittanies.
Yes, very nice to meet you.
- Hello.
Shall we move the party upstairs?
I'll need my
clothes on, actually.
Sorry, girls. I'm late.
For what?
- Work.
- Please don't tell me
you actually believe you work
- for the police.
- Work for, work with.
I'm a civilian consultant.
The detective called.
There's been a murder.
My services are needed.
Brittanies...
why don't you make my friend
feel better, hmm?
And, uh, this
bruising is from what?
Possible imprint.
I'll know more once I'm back at the lab.
Okay. Call me when
you get something.
Howdy, partner.
We're not partners.
Right.
So, what unpleasantness
felled this heap of unrealized
ambition then?
Suffocation, a crushed trachea.
And this heap has a name.
Erwin Scovell, 55. He
worked security here for 20 years.
Ooh, talk about suffocating.
Vice suspects this place
has been used by criminal organizations
to store illegal contraband.
Container went missing,
so Scovell probably walked
in on a robbery in progress.
Security cameras were
disabled, so no video.
Probably gonna need to canvass the...
Lucifer, it's a dead body.
A little respect.
Do you know, I am amazed
by the deferential regard
you people hold for rotting flesh.
I mean, this poor
sap's either already in Hell
or in the Silver City
enduring Uriel's welcome speech,
which is far worse
than Hell, if you ask me.
Let's pretend for one
second that you're someone else.
Someone nice, someone mature.
Ooh, I love role-play.
Great.
So, since we don't have any leads,
let's focus on the next
steps of the investigation,
like what was in the stolen container.
But I've already solved
it. I know what killed Erwin.
What?
Boredom.
I mean, getting murdered is probably
the most exciting thing that
ever happened to him.
When do we get to raid a
drug house or shoot someone?
I mean, I gave up an
epic foursome to be here.
A man died, and we're going to
do everything we possibly can
to catch the killer.
Pass.
Are you joking?
Hard pass.
Hey! After all of your manipulations
to get to work with me, you're
really gonna walk away
because you think this case is boring?
Just call me when you've
got a murder with a pulse.
Or at least someone good-looking.
I mean...
Is the Brittany buffet still serving?
- Okay, got it.
- Huh?
God, I was hoping for a good shag
just as a palate cleanser
to wipe the foul taste
of boredom from my mouth.
We need to talk.
Well, as long as
it's not the detective's
homicide/robbery
snoozefest at the docks, I'm all ears.
You know, I don't know how they do it.
40 hours a week, 52
weeks a year, 50 years.
I mean, I didn't leave Hell just
to step into another one.
Yeah, well, about that robbery/homicide
snoozefest.
The container that's
missing, it was yours.
What container?
The container.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.addic7ed.com -
Didn't you hear what I just said?
The container is missing.
I heard you.
Then why aren't we out
there recovering it?
Why fuss? I suppose if somebody wants it
badly enough to steal it,
then perhaps they should have it, then.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
This doesn't upset you?
I don't know what to tell you, Maze.
I guess it's not that
important to me after all.
Well, it's your container...
and your reputation.
What about my reputation?
Well, apparently, it's
okay to steal from you now.
But...
if it doesn't bother
you... doesn't bother me.
We're
canvassing the entire area
for witnesses now, ma'am.
Okay, good. Let's check
with the nearby businesses,
- All right.
- and check the...
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
What? Have you thought of
all new offensive things
- to say?
- No, I've changed mind.
I've come back to help. Any leads yet?
I need your help like
I need a third boob.
- Mmm!
- Wait.
Don't say a word. Knew it was a mistake
the minute it came out of my mouth.
We're partners, and I'm
offering you my services.
I think you need a refresher course
on how partnership works.
You left me hanging, remember?
Yes, but now I'm here
because of the robbery.
Robbery? Why?
Because the container that
was stolen was mine.
You somehow left that out before.
Well, I didn't know before.
Maze handles
logistics... storage and such.
And did you know that
this facility was used
- to house illegal contraband?
- No.
But what better place to store my stuff
than somewhere
people hide illicit goods?
Asking the obvious here,
but was your stuff illegal
contraband, too?
Define "illegal."
What was in the container?
- A personal item, insignificant.
- Yeah, but what was in it?
The only thing I
brought with me to Los Angeles.
I know, but you're not
answering the question.
Look, I was storing
some stuff, it was stolen,
the theft sets an awful precedent,
so I'm obliged to make
the person responsible pay.
Now, if you let me help,
I'm certain we can solve
this case quickly.
And I have a lead.
Snow cones?
This is your lead?
We don't have time for this.
We should be working.
- What can I get you?
- Uh, yes.
I'll have two Tropic Wonders
and your face smashed into the ground.
What?
What the...?
Lucifer, what are you doing? Stop!
I believe they call this interrogating.
Lucifer, stop!
- He needs to tell me where my stuff is.
- Don't.
- I just sell snow cones.
- Lucifer!
This isn't how we do things.
This pathetic sap's real
name is Frankie Costa,
and his real job is
transporting and storing illegal goods.
Maze set up the warehouse through him.
So if someone knew to
rob it, he'd be involved.
I wouldn't steal from my own operation.
That warehouse is off-limits.
Hey, man.
I'm trying to get out
of the storage racket.
Yes, focus, Frankie.
Who took my property?
I don't know.
I'm trying to find out myself.
This is bad for business.
And who would know
about the storage service?
Who are you?
I'm someone with one of these.
But this guy doesn't have one.
So say if I were to walk away,
he can do whatever he wants to you.
Of if you're not
responsible, you can point us
in the right direction
of someone who is. Cool?
Okay, okay.
Los Diablos.
The biker club?
Yeah.
I run the warehouse, but
they run the docks.
If anything went down, they
would know about it.
That's all I know.
I swear.
All right, all right.
Fine.
That was incredible.
It was musical, poetic really.
We were like fish and
chips, salt and pepper.
Hipsters and condescension.
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't arrest you for assault.
Fine, Frankie's a complete scumbag,
and he skimps on the cherry syrup.
So that's two, actually.
Uh, something's going on with you,
and it has to do with that
mysterious container,
so no more games... what's in it?
It was a gift from my father.
That's still not an answer.
I mean, what, was it his memoirs?
Some priceless porn collection?
Look, if we're gonna
work together on this,
you're gonna have
to trust me, all right?
You're right, we
shouldn't work together on this.
Aren't we being a touch dramatic?
You know, I put up with a lot of crap
to let you in on my cases,
and that's because thus
far you've been honest with me,
but now, for some reason,
you're not telling me the full story.
I'm telling you
everything you need to
know to help find my stuff.
A man was murdered, and all you
can talk about is your property?
Yes, but if we find
it, then you find out
who killed the security guard...
it's win-win.
So, please, enlighten me.
Under what rock
will we find Los Diablos?
It's a very on-the-nose name,
if you ask me.
We won't find them anywhere.
It's a conflict of interest.
Look, Chloe, I told you,
there's nothing I can do about tomorrow.
Truce.
This is a call for Dan the detective.
All right?
I need your help.
Okay.
It's about my case.
Homicide at the docks.
Security guard killed during a robbery.
Yeah, that container that was stolen,
it was Lucifer's.
That storage facility was
filled with black market goods.
Yeah, it was.
You think what Lucifer had stored
in there may be illegal.
Whatever is in that
container, he won't tell me.
And for a man who's all
about over-sharing, says a lot,
so I want you to look into him,
try and find out what
he might be hiding.
Absolutely.
LAPD.
Boss is out.
Yes, I know.
What do you want?
I need to see your books.
Without any foreplay?
Your boss has reported an operating loss
for the last five years.
So?
So this club is packed every night.
At 20 bucks an
appletini, it doesn't really add up.
You're Chloe's ex, right?
And you're Lucifer's pet on a leash.
Now answer the question.
Well, technically, that
wasn't a question.
Is your divorce final yet?
That's none of your business.
Now, are you gonna show me your records,
or do I need to get a warrant?
We have nothing to hide.
That's great.
I'll be right here.
Mm-hmm.
Actually, the books are in the office.
And there are way too many
of them to carry all by myself.
But if you come out back with me,
I'll let you see whatever you want.
Just the books is fine.
Right this way.
Straight ahead, to the left.
When Chloe told you to
leave, how did that make you feel?
Well, pissed off, of course.
Whatever was stolen from you
must have been very important.
No.
Actually, no, it's the
principle at stake here.
I mean, nobody steals from
me and gets away with it.
This loss brings up an
issue that we've been skirting
since we began our work together.
- Right.
- Your identity.
It's
still the Devil, darling.
Yes, but who are you trying
so hard to become?
Nobody.
I'm completely unbecoming.
And yet you keep trying on many
hats to hide your horns.
Playboy, cop, club owner...
Yes, you forgot "master of
all things tongue-related."
Speaking of which, shall we?
That's for later.
I think we're onto
something very important here.
One of the hardest things we ever do...
is learn to be ourselves.
I want you to tell me who you believe...
is the real you.
I...
I am...
second-guessing your
skills as a therapist.
You're feeling judged.
So you're lashing out and judging me.
But that's excellent.
It's transference.
Which means you seek my approval.
I seek no one's approval.
And time's up.
Suddenly I'm no
longer in the amorous mood.
Okay, hold on...
Hold on, Lucifer.
You think that's a fight.
I think it's progress.
Or maybe I'm just realizing
what a waste of time this is.
I'm glad you came ba...
- Oh.
- Is everything okay?
It's-it's you. Hi.
I'm sorry, it's just, uh, thin walls.
Oh.
Yes, everything's fine.
Uh, please.
Thanks again for
drinks the other night, Linda.
Uh, yeah.
Yes, that was fun.
Yeah.
All right, so what kind of parent
names their kid Lucifer?
I'm sorry, I don't mean
to be unprofessional, but...
We're colleagues. Cone of silence.
And I don't believe his
real name is Lucifer.
We talk in metaphors.
Mmm.
Patients with delusions.
They can be really challenging.
Mm, he's actually quite charming.
Yeah, but even Satan disguises himself
as an angel of the light.
2 Corinthians, chapter 11, verse 14.
Ah.
Two years of seminary school
before I decided I wanted to help
people in a different way.
Ah. Interesting.
I thought you seemed... pure.
Listen, you really helped me
with my patient the other day,
and I would love to return the favor.
I know the Bible inside and out,
so if you ever need a consult,
just let me know.
Whoa.
Just
quit defending him, Mom.
You know Dan's never gonna change.
Mm-hmm.
What's for dinner, Mommy?
Greens, you little cake monster.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know why
I even bother telling you.
He's-he's not gonna change, Mom.
You know, Dan's just the way he is,
and I wasn't asking for the world.
I just wanted to see a little effort,
and it's probably too late.
Ah, it's pointless to
discuss this with you.
Why? Because you always take his side.
Look, Mom, I...
- Daddy!
- Shh!
- Hey, Monkey!
- What are you doing here?
And why are you wearing a pillow?
Well, those are...
that... those are great questions,
and I'm gonna answer both of them later.
But right now, I need
you to do something for me.
What?
Get me some clothes, and
don't tell Mommy that I'm here.
I thought you said lying
was a bad thing.
It is, it's terrible, but
this-this is different.
Because we're gonna play a game.
It's called "Sneak
Daddy Out of the House."
That still sounds like a lie.
You know, it's complicated, Monkey.
You're just gonna
have to go with it, okay?
What's in it for me?
What do you want?
- Chocolate cake.
- Done.
- For a whole year.
- Absolutely not.
Mommy, I'm thirsty!
Okay, fine.
Done.
Now will you please go
get me some clothes?
What the hell did you do to me?
What do you mean?
One second, I'm standing here,
next second, I'm in my ex's bed naked.
Well, you're welcome.
So,
did it work?
You two have sex?
No.
Why would you think that
putting me in her bed naked
would get us to have sex?
- Always works for me.
- And why would
you even want Chloe and I to have sex?
So that you and her will
get back together,
and she'll be out of Lucifer's life.
You're not from around here, are you?
You have no idea.
You can't just smash two
people together like Barbies,
and think that that's gonna fix things.
Relationships, they
take time and effort.
And you got to work at it, like...
it's your job.
Humans are so exhausting.
Here are the books you wanted to see.
Oh, no, we're not through here.
You assaulted a police officer.
I'm taking you in.
And what exactly
are you going to say happened?
Hmm?
That a tiny female bartender
knocked you out,
stripped you naked
and put you in your ex's bed?
I can't explain it.
Lux's books are clean.
How is that even possible?
I had them run for
discrepancies with receivables.
I looked for hidden payments.
Whatever Lucifer's into,
it's not running through Lux.
All right, thanks for trying.
Listen, Chloe...
I want to talk to
you about Taco Tuesday.
Hey, Dan, I got to go.
Next time you secretly
follow someone, don't tailgate them.
Draws a little attention.
It's not my fault you
drive like an elderly turtle.
Lucifer...
go home.
Detective...
It sucks not getting what you want.
Now you have to deal with it
like the rest of us.
I'm sorry.
What did you just say?
I apologize.
I crossed the line this morning
with Mr. Snow Cone.
It was a mistake.
I realize that now.
Wow.
You must really be desperate.
I prefer determined.
Look, I need your help to find my stuff.
But you have to admit I've
proven myself useful.
Despite the methods employed,
Frankie did give us a solid lead.
Insanely wild guess,
but this is where
we'll find some Los Diablos.
There's an imprint on the victim's neck
that we found under UV light.
Killer must've worn
some kind of bracelet
when he strangled the security guard.
Cross look familiar?
Well, what do you know?
Our suspect awaits.
Shall we?
What happened to the music?
Hey! Come on, man!
What are you doing, man?
What is this? What's going on here?
What's going on with that?
Excuse me!
Pardon the intrusion,
you Village People rejects,
but one of you has stolen something
that belongs to me.
So please identify yourself, so
I can punish you accordingly.
Who do you think you are?
I thought we were past you
thinking you're invincible.
I really want to find my stuff.
What the hell did you just say?
Hmm? Harry Potter?
There you go.
Mess him up, Renny.
Well, since you're obviously lower
on the human evolutionary chain,
perhaps your hearing hasn't developed
as well as it should,
so I'll repeat myself.
Who...
stole...
my...
property?
Everybody back the hell
off or you're going to jail.
Pardon my boys.
They don't always have the best, uh,
people skills.
Take a breather, Renny.
Now!
Be cool.
Hank Cutter.
I'm in charge here.
Oh, a Mrs. Police. How are you?
Why don't we chat in my office, okay?
Follow me.
We heard that you control the docks,
and if anything goes
down, Los Diablos are in on it.
Really? We're just a riding club, okay?
Whose members have been
arrested for guns, drugs, murder.
A few bad apples shouldn't paint us all
in a bad light, now should it, ma'am?
But it does paint you as suspects.
Hey, look, just because we
have a reputation as outlaws
doesn't mean we had
anything to do with a murder.
You like being
considered a criminal, don't you?
Yeah, you do.
What else do you want?
To own a clothing line.
Oh.
Clothing line?
I-I did not see that one coming.
Yes, managing bikers
must be so exhausting.
All that brawling and pillaging.
- I'm 54.
- Really?
I'd rather be in my
hammock playing my Stratocaster.
All this motorcycle
riding's enlarged my prostate.
It's unpleasant.
That's an
unfortunate occupational hazard.
Tell me about it.
Look, we've trademarked our name.
We're selling T-shirts and jackets,
and we're gonna re-brand and...
go legit.
"Legit."
There's a lot of money
in the apparel industry.
All the more reason to
keep our noses clean.
See, we used to cover
the docks, not anymore.
I specifically ordered them off-limits.
Maybe someone missed
the re-branding memo.
Killer wore a
bracelet with an iron cross.
Left an imprint on the dead security
guard at the warehouse.
Look, uh, a lot of
bikers wear iron crosses.
Yeah, well, I'm interested in your
guys who have iron crosses.
Hey, look, I've told
you everything I know.
If you have any more questions,
feel free to contact my attorney.
But we're not finished yet.
Yeah, we're done.
Thank you.
But why are we leaving?
He's hiding something.
It's obvious.
We need to force it out of him.
We have this little
thing called due process.
We can't just force
things out of people.
Besides, there's an easier
way to get our bad guy.
You saw the look on
Cutter's face when he saw that photo.
He knows exactly who robbed the docks.
He's gonna need to
deal with this immediately.
Or it puts his plan to
re-brand in jeopardy.
Defying his orders...
it's a huge challenge to his authority.
He's not gonna want to deal
with this in public.
Bet you the first person he goes to see
is the owner of that bracelet.
What, so your strategy is
just to sit here, paralyzed,
hoping that Cutter leads
us to the suspect?
What a terrible idea.
Hmm, you think so?
I do, I mean, for one,
even though Cutter's no brain surgeon,
surely he wouldn't just...
Wouldn't what?
Well done, Detective.
A toast to Dr. Linda Martin,
therapist to the Devil himself.
I should put that on the door.
Mm, well, it sounds like he's dealing
with some genuine issues.
I'm just having such a hard
time getting through to him.
Maybe it's because you've
been humoring his metaphor
without fully embracing it.
You mean, completely accept
that he's actually the Devil?
Mm-hmm.
It's worth a try.
If only I knew someone who
could help me with the Bible.
I know so much about it, it's
almost as if I was there.
If he's positioning himself
as the Devil, right?
He must see himself as evil.
Mm!
No.
Actually, he's struggling.
I think he thinks other
people see him as evil.
You seem attached to this patient.
I am...
very motivated to help him.
I see.
Well, um,
every culture in the world
and throughout history, for that matter,
has its very own myth of the Devil.
Mm-hmm.
But the one thing that
they all have in common
is that the Devil is essentially
a rebellious son.
Sounds like my guy.
I thought it might.
Now, if you're really serious
about embracing the metaphor, Linda...
truly embracing it... I
know how you can get to him.
But he might not
like what you have to say.
But will it help him?
He may not realize it, but yes.
Then let's do it.
I've sat in a parked
car and not had sex.
Ew.
You can't enjoy this.
This sitting around endlessly,
waiting for something to happen.
You know, if sitting
here not being entertained
is so terrible, then maybe it's a sign
you should be somewhere else.
Have I done something to offend you?
Only every time I see you.
Ha, ha, ha. No, this is different.
For the first time, I
don't think you're being
honest with me. You have this
mysterious container that was stolen
that someone was willing to kill for.
You make shady deals with shady people.
You're violent.
Your personal records only go
back five years, and the books
from Lux are way too clean.
It's...
I had Dan go and check it out.
You had Dan deal with Maze alone?
Oh, dear. For the first time,
I actually feel
sorry for Detective Douche.
It all points to you being a criminal.
So what's the big deal?
What if I am a criminal?
I'd have to arrest you.
Ooh, whip out the
cuffs, then. Why shy away
from a little bondage fun?
You know, Lucifer, this is serious.
And despite all your weirdness
I...
I actually really like working with you.
So, anyhow...
What a momentous
revelation, Detective
Decker. We should celebrate.
You can celebrate from jail
when it turns out I'm right about you.
I have never lied to you.
And I will
never lie to you.
What was in the container?
Russian dolls.
Russian dolls?
Here we go.
Oh, I knew it was
gonna be that Renny guy.
About that warehouse...!
Think I won't?
This is Unit 831.
Shots fired at 21st and Lewis.
We need backup and an ambo, now.
Unit 831,
all units in the vicinity...
There.
Bloody mortality.
Been a while since I had a good hunt.
That tingling sensation
running up your spine... inevitability.
And the bit running down your leg?
Fear.
Now...
you give me what is mine.
Wasn't my idea, I swear.
He didn't tell me what
was in the container.
But I looked.
I saw them.
Who stole them?
Oh, God...
Who... stole them?
They were yours.
Who stole them?
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Oh...
you are gonna more than sorry
unless you tell me everything.
Please. Please, don't...
No!
No! No!
No, don't!
I couldn't stop him.
Hey, you all right?
Looks like Cutter's gonna make it.
He just gave a statement.
Cutter?
The guy Renny shot.
Renny was pissed about the direction.
Of the club, he
thought they were selling out.
So he went out on his own,
robbed the warehouse and
killed the security guard.
We got justice
- for Erwin Scovell.
- Wonderful.
And they've recovered one container
belonging to...
a Lucifer Morningstar.
Where?
Inside.
You didn't take a sneaky
peek before telling me?
You'd never lie to me, right?
You're gonna watch me open it.
You're damn right.
Wow.
Hmm...
I told you.
Why go to all this trouble for dolls?
Oh, come now, Detective.
I have to keep some
mysteries for myself.
Enjoy your dolls.
They're gone.
Want to grab that?
Hi, Daddy.
Hey, Monkey.
This is for after dinner, okay?
- Hey.
Thought you had an important work thing.
Well, it wasn't as important
as having tacos with Trixie.
And you.
That is, if it's not too late.
Yeah.
We're just making the salsa.
Great.
That smells so yummy.
Oh, good.
I'm glad you came back.
Well, I needed to
get my parking validated.
So your items were never recovered?
No.
Earlier, you said
that the items weren't that important.
Yet now, you seem very
upset that they're gone.
Well, I'm a walking paradox.
What can I say?
Sometimes we need to lose something
before we can understand its value.
I didn't lose anything.
No.
No, you were a victim of a crime.
It's only natural that
you would feel violated.
And often, our feelings of loss
connect to how we feel...
about who we are.
Oh, right.
So we're back on that, are we?
You want to talk about my identity.
Yes, because you're the Devil.
You told me your names.
But you left out a few others.
Abaddon.
Belial.
Prince of Darkness...
Someone's been brushing
up on their Sunday school.
Yes. But before you
fell, you were known as Samael.
The Lightbringer.
I don't go by that name anymore.
That was a name that
connotated your father's love for you.
Right.
Was casting his son into Hell
also an expression of his love?
Oh, God didn't cast you out of Heaven
because he was angry with you.
How can you presume to
know God's intentions?
Oh, I don't.
I can't.
Then maybe stick within the limits
of your intellectual capacity.
Or maybe my simplicity
offers me a different perspective.
God cast you out
because He needed you
to do the most difficult of jobs.
- It was a gift.
- Gift?
He shunned me.
He vilified me.
He made me a torturer!
Can you even begin to
fathom what it was like?
Eons spent
providing a place for dead mortals
to punish themselves?
I mean, why do they blame me
for all their little failings?
As if I'd spent my days sitting
on their shoulder,
forcing them to commit acts they'd
otherwise find repulsive.
"Oh, the Devil made me do it."
I have never made any
one of them do anything.
Never.
What happened to you is unfair.
Unfair?
This is unjust.
For all eternity, my
name will be invoked
to represent all their depravity.
That is the gift that my father gave me.
It was an act of love.
How do you know?
Because you are his
favorite son, Samael.
Do not call me that, please!
You are his fallen angel.
But here's the thing:
When angels fall,
they also... rise.
All you have to do
is embrace all that you are.
I can't.
Yes, you can.
You just have to be
open to the process...
You don't understand.
- I can't!
- But why?
Because they stole them from me!
Someone's got them, Mazikeen.
Someone's got my wings.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net