Previously on Lucifer...
Kane is alive.
You know, for an immortal,
you really do bleed a lot, don't you?
PIERCE: I still feel all the
pain that comes with death,
just the wounds heal.
AMENADIEL: I am a soldier of God.
His favorite son.
Oh, that's gonna be a thing, isn't it?
It was weird
seeing you and Amenadiel so chummy.
It makes me feel left out.
I'm missing time.
It's like someone else
was living my life.
I've been pretending
like I remember it all
because otherwise, everyone
would think that I'm crazy.
My Dad screwed us both.
But perhaps there's a way
for us to screw Him back.
If we're gonna kill you,
we have got to do it together.
["THE ANSWER" BY AQUAMOAN PLAYING]
♪ I'll be ♪
♪ The answer ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah... ♪
What do you got for me?
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah... ♪
Also Download Other Tvseries For Free At
www.Flashtvseries.Tk
- I said no phone.
- Sorry.
Thought I turned it off.
It's just my sister.
The cops are calling you?
Your sister's a cop?
She works in forensics.
Trust me, okay? Just...
put the gun down.
[PHONE BEEPS]
Come on, Jay, I'm your sister.
I'm not supposed to have to
leave a message after the beep,
you're supposed to call me back.
[BEEPS]
LUCIFER: Take off your shirt.
Don't flatter yourself.
In my quest to help you
die, I've done some research,
and I think the key
may lie in understanding
the mark that my Father placed on you.
Oh, that's a waste of
time. I've already tried
to figure out what it means.
I've read every book, I've
analyzed every language.
Well, have you ever let
the Devil take a gander?
Didn't think so.
[SIGHS] Okay.
Well, where's the rest
of it? The tattoo on top.
The skull and the spears.
Well, my body's constantly healing.
I have to reapply the
tattoo every few months.
Well, why bother at all?
Because it represents
my immortality, my curse.
- I hate it.
- Yes, yes.
You hate living forever
'cause you can't see
how much fun it is.
I'll never understand you.
What?
Do you have something?
- Seriously?
- Well, it's worth a try.
God, this was much easier in The DVC.
DVC?
My research text. Also a movie.
By the way, Tom Hanks
is a national treasure.
Also a movie. Not as helpful, though.
Your research was watching
The Da Vinci Code?
- And the sequels.
- No offense, Lucifer,
but I don't think this
is in your wheelhouse.
You're right.
Amenadiel's the brainy one.
We should ask him.
That's a good idea.
You think he'll help?
Well, we've grown much closer, he and I.
I'll convince him.
♪ ♪
En garde!
[ENGLISH ACCENT]: Oh, no!
No, no, no, please. Please,
don't harm me, fierce warrior.
I-I-I surrender!
I will spare your life.
This time.
We're wearing the same shirt!
- Sushi shirt!
Come on in.
MAZE: I don't know
what's going on out there,
but I hate it!
[GRUNTING]
Oh.
Hey, Ellen.
- It's Ella.
- [GRUNTS]
Decker's not here.
I'm, um, actually looking for you.
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
Trix,
sever their Achilles first.
If they can't walk,
- they can't betray you.
- They can't betray you.
Got it.
Okay.
What's up?
Um, well, my brother
came into town yesterday,
and I can't
- get ahold of him.
- [GRUNTS]
Good talk. See you later.
No, wait. I-It's not like him
to just disappear.
I can't find him.
Anywhere.
And everyone says
that you are the best
bounty hunter we've got.
Ah, so he's a criminal.
No. No, no, no, no.
But... I got a bad feeling.
Please, I need your help.
I'll pay!
Next time, lead with that.
So, does that mean you'll help me?
AMENADIEL: No.
What do you mean, no?
God cursed Kane because
he killed his own brother.
And you want to remove that curse,
which God placed on him
for a very good reason.
Does that even sound
like something that I would help you do?
Well, it did, until
you put it like that.
Look, this is important
to me, Amenadiel.
I need your help.
Just take a look at the mark, and maybe
it'll jog something in
that geeky brain of yours.
If Father wanted you to
understand Kane's mark,
He simply would've...
Send my angelic brother down to help me?
Nice try.
We've been through a lot, you and I.
I thought we were getting along.
I thought we were...
well, brothers, for once.
We are, Luci.
But you're also my test.
The reason Father has placed me
here on Earth without my powers.
- So I need to protect you from yourself.
- [SIGHS]
I gave my word, Brother.
That's not my problem.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
MAZE: My sources say your brother
had a meeting here last night.
- Really?
- This place belongs
to a diamond dealer.
Fahrid Nasser.
Never heard of him. But my brother
is a diamond authenticator. I
mean, makes sense he'd be here.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY] Well,
apparently, this Fahrid guy,
real sketchy dude.
Okay, my brother is literally the one
who determines if diamonds are legit.
Okay? That's the polar
opposite of sketchy.
So if he was here, he had his reasons.
No.
No, no, no. No.
[EXHALES] Thank God.
I mean, too bad for this dude, but...
thank you, Big Guy.
Yeah. Huge relief.
Your brother's not dead.
Instead, he might be the killer.
Also Download Other Tvseries For Free At
www.Flashtvseries.Tk
[INDISTINCT POLICE TRANSMISSION]
Can't believe you called the cops.
Maze, for the last time,
stop telling people
not to call the cops.
ELLA: And why wouldn't
I call this in, okay?
Even if Jay
was here, he's innocent.
Which means he might
have seen who did this.
Wait, he might be in danger.
Is this the brother who steals cars?
Oh, no, Jay's the oldest.
- And you know how older brothers are.
- LUCIFER: Yeah.
- Oh. I'm an only child.
- Oh.
Well, Jay is the good one.
The one we all looked up to.
I mean, I know my
family's got its issues,
but not Jay.
I mean, he really made me believe
I could live a good life.
Mm, well, that's what eldest
brothers want you to think.
Always talking down to you
from their pedestals that
they put themselves on.
But when you need them to
help you kill someone...
[CHUCKLES] where are they then, hmm?
[SCOFFS]
We still don't know for sure, guys,
if he was even here.
- He was here.
- Maze,
I know you've got your
sources or whatever.
But I'm just saying, until fingerprint
and DNA analysis comes back,
- we don't know...
- I found his wallet.
Maze, where did you get that?
It was in the corner over there
when we first walked in.
What? He's still my bounty,
and I haven't found him.
CHLOE: "Jay Lopez."
It's your brother.
[SIGHS] Which means he's definitely...
Not the killer!
Based on the blood spatter,
the bullet was fired
from this angle, right?
It looks that way.
But this looks like powder burn, okay?
So the only way to shoot
from this angle further back
would be if you were a lefty.
And... drumroll, please... my brother
is a righty.
So, obviously, there must
have been another person here.
Uh, okay. Okay.
Well, we'll start looking
for this left-handed shooter.
But, in the meantime,
I really think it's best for everybody
and-and your brother
if you just step away
from the investigation.
Okay, yeah. I-I get it.
But I'm gonna go and try to find Jay.
I really would prefer you don't.
He could be in danger.
Okay, I'll call you
if we find anything.
Great. Now that we're
done with that charade,
shall we track down Ms.
Lopez's murderous brother
before she does?
I trust Ella's instincts.
It does seem like there
was another person here.
So, just to be safe,
let's pursue both scenarios.
Brothers can't be trusted, Detective.
You're just delaying her
inevitable disappointment.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
I've been through some...
[SIGHS] trauma.
And I've been avoiding it. [CHUCKLES]
But, recently, um, events
have caused me to realize
that I need to...
face my fears.
Lucifer mentioned that you
worked wonders with him.
I mean, you see someone
who calls himself the Devil.
So anything I say can't sound
too crazy, right? [CHUCKLES]
I haven't been to therapy before.
Is this where I start...
telling you what I'm going through?
Um...
a couple of months ago,
I had a near-death experience.
And I think that-that
when I was dead, um,
I think that I was in Hell,
- reliving the same nightmare...
- I can't help you.
Excuse me?
You need to leave.
Now.
Oh, I'm...
Of course. I'm s...
[CHUCKLES] I'm so sorry to have...
to have wasted your time.
[DOOR OPENS]
I really am beyond help, aren't I?
[SIGHS]
Brothers. [CHUCKLES]
Am I right?
I mean, you get it. You killed yours.
I wish I had that option.
Amenadiel won't help, I take it?
Nope.
No. I mean, I shouldn't be surprised.
Ever since he found
out he's Dad's favorite,
he's been a bit of a dick.
- What do you mean?
- Well, lots of chest puffing
and peacocking.
I mean, even more than usual,
with that insufferably smug...
No, I mean, how do you know
that he's God's favorite?
It's a long story,
involving a flaming sword
and a space vagina.
But the quick version:
a book said it, so it must be true.
Anyway, not to worry.
I'll find a way to bring him round.
Our victim's Fahrid Nasser... he's
an international diamond salesman.
So it makes sense that
you'd find a loose diamond
in his office, but can you skip
to the part where you help us
track down Ms. Lopez's
disappointment of a brother?
I thought we were looking
for another suspect.
We are. Despite Lucifer's attempt
to make this case about what's
going on with his own brother.
- You were saying, Dan?
- Well,
it would make sense to find a
diamond in a broker's office,
unless that diamond was reported stolen.
Fortunately for us,
diamonds are pretty easy to track.
Each one of them has a serial number
laser-etched into it.
I usually get them to add crude
drawings to the back of mine.
- Where was it stolen from?
- A diamond boutique
in Beverly Hills. Here's the kicker...
Fahrid, our victim,
he's one of the store's
diamond brokers.
So, what, he sells to them,
uses that as a cover
- to the case the joint, then robs it?
- Maybe.
File on the robbery's pretty thin...
No security cameras, no witnesses,
- not a lot to go on.
- All right,
well, maybe Fahrid had an accomplice?
That could be our other suspect.
Let's go to the jewelry
store, see if we can drum up
any new leads now that we
know Fahrid is involved.
["RUN RUN RUN" BY KARI KIMMEL PLAYING]
♪ I'm gonna find ya ♪
♪ Wherever-ever you are ♪
♪ I'm gonna get ya ♪
♪ You're never gettin' too far ♪
♪ I'm gonna run, run, run... ♪
[SIGHS]: Ah, the diamond industry...
Truly the greatest trick
someone other than me
played on the world.
Thousands of dollars
for lumps of old coal.
Incredible.
Ah. Hello there. We're here to...
We're here to...
to get a ring.
- [GIGGLES]
- We are?
Yes. Yeah, he was gonna surprise me.
But I knew what he was up to.
- [NERVOUS CHUCKLE]
- We're engaged.
How nice.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Mm.
Sweetie, I-I don't know if
we came to the right place.
I expect a, a much...
higher clarity, and-and the
color here is blech.
Oh, I see you have
quite a discerning eye.
I have some other wonderful options.
- Just a moment.
- Thank you.
I... am confused.
The file said that there
was no security footage.
All these cameras, they're
not new, which means
they were here at the time
of the robbery, which means
this is probably an inside job.
Yeah, I got that part... flush out
the accomplice, et cetera, et cetera.
No, how do you know
so much about diamonds?
Well, I've watched enough Real Housewives
to fake it with the best of them.
[LAUGHS]: Oh. Wonderful.
Really?
[LAUGHS]: No. No.
These still won't do.
How about this... why don't
I show you what I don't want?
This is what he got
me for Valentine's Day.
I didn't know that my future husband
was that cheap.
I am not cheap.
That diamond is of the highest quality.
Is it? Is it of the highest quality?
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's see.
[CHUCKLES]: Oh.
Uh-huh, excellent color, and...
And what?
Uh, I'm sorry, uh...
I recognize the serial number.
But, uh, this diamond is...
stolen.
- No.
- Stolen?
LUCIFER: Can't be.
Stolen?!
You cheap son of a bitch.
I... For the last time, I am not cheap.
- I'm gonna have to call the police.
- Oh, yes,
please, please
call the cops. [LAUGHS]
I want my future ex-husband arrested
- for being cheap.
- R-Right. For the final time, d-darling...
No need to get the authorities involved.
I'm Tiffany James, the owner.
Why don't you come with me,
and we'll find you the perfect diamond.
So, tell me exactly what
it is you're looking for.
It's funny, Ms. James,
I was waiting for a clerk
to make a run for it,
or a security guard to start sweating.
But the owner of the store...
Excuse me?
Why rob your own store?
[LAUGHS]
I don't know what you're talking about.
- I'm LAPD.
- And I'm not cheap, for the record.
But let's cut to the
chase, shall we, Tiffany?
How did you help Jay
Lopez steal diamonds
and murder Fahrid Nasser?
Who's Jay Lopez? Wait.
Fahrid's dead?
Stop prompting the witness.
Fine. But the sooner we prove
Ms. Lopez's elder brother
is a liar and a
disappointment, the better.
Would you excuse us for a second?
- Thank you.
- [SIGHS]
It's obvious that you're having
some kind of fight with Amenadiel,
but right now you need
to focus on the case.
- Fine.
- And for the record...
I wish I had a brother to fight with.
But...
So, you admit to knowing Fahrid.
Of course... He sold diamonds here.
Wow, I can't believe he's really dead.
Oh, a complete shock to you and
all your associates, I'm sure.
So let's get on with it, shall we?
Tell me...
Tiffany,
what is it you desire?
To punch every millennial in the face.
Really? [CHUCKLES]
I mean, I don't disagree,
but still.
They've ruined our entire industry.
With their social consciousness
and ethical issues.
Sales are way down because of them.
Do you know how hard it
is to stay afloat?
So hard that you have
to rob your own store?
No one was supposed to get hurt.
We just wanted the insurance money.
[CHUCKLES] This was an insurance scam?
- Then why kill Fahrid?
- I didn't.
Fahrid was supposed to
sell the diamonds back to us
after he cleaned them, but...
now...
Well, I mean, if anyone is cheap...
it's her.
Oh, why are we here?
Jay would never, ever
stay in a place like this.
Two days ago, he used his debit card
at a gas station around the corner.
So? Dude wanted a Slurpee...
It doesn't mean anything.
You don't come into this neighborhood
unless you have a
reason... And if you're here
to do criminal activity, you
come to a hotel that takes cash.
- He is not a criminal.
- Yeah.
You've... never seen
this guy, right?
Have you seen him?
Unless you got a warrant,
I ain't answering either of you.
Aah! Aah!
I'm gonna give you two choices.
I can either break your arm...
[GRUNTS IN PAIN]
or I can cut your...
Maze! Just...
Do you have
a brother, sister,
anyone who you care about,
who it would just kill you
if you didn't know where
they were, if they were safe?
Threatening his family?
Hard-core, Ellen.
Ten bucks an hour ain't worth this.
[GASPING BREATH]
[GROANS]
[RELIEVED EXHALE]
No Jay here. See?
Oh, no.
Michael Knight.
Who's that?
Knight Rider.
Jay's favorite show.
[KNOCKING]
Doctor.
I got your text. What's wrong?
Charlotte Richards.
What about her?
She came to see me... as a client.
Oh, good, good.
She took my advice.
Why would you send her to me?
Because you're the best.
She tried to kill me.
When she stepped into my office,
everything she did came rushing back.
Doctor...
my mother is gone.
Charlotte Richards has
done nothing to you.
She's just an innocent
woman who needs help.
[EXHALES]
Here.
[SIGHS] At least she
didn't try and kiss you.
Hey, Chloe.
This is Don Zeikel,
the insurance adjustor
that covers Tiffany James's store.
I'm in your debt.
It's rare we actually
catch insurance fraud.
Makes me miss being a cop.
Bet you don't miss the sad
amounts on the pay stubs.
No. Better Scotch and
stylish clothes don't make up
for that rush you get
when you catch a bad guy.
Now that I've gone corporate,
I just pay out the claims.
- Why's that?
- Oh, it's practically an untraceable crime
if the thieves got a cleaner.
- A cleaner?
- It's someone who can replace
the microscopic serial
numbers on the diamonds.
- Like a diamond authenticator.
- Sure.
Why? You know of an
authenticator involved?
- [SIGHS] Not yet.
- Well,
please keep me in the loop.
Great. Thank you.
Why do I get the feeling that
our two-pronged investigation
just lost a prong?
We got to find Ella's brother.
♪ ♪
You got any siblings?
Thousands and thousands.
[CHUCKLES]: Yeah. It could
feel like that sometimes.
You close to any of 'em?
My family doesn't do "close."
We mostly tortured each other.
Aw, man, us, too.
My brothers used to put their knees
on my arms and dangle a
loogie right over my face.
- Sounds horrifying.
- But then,
if I was ever in trouble,
they always had my back.
No matter what.
This is it.
Whoa!
No need to go all kung
fu on this innocent door.
Well, aren't you full of surprises.
Nice job, Ellen.
It's Ella.
[DOOR CREAKS]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
[CHOKING]
Jay?
♪ I'm all out of love ♪
♪ I'm all out of love for you... ♪
So I finally get to meet
the infamous Amenadiel.
Look, I know who you are,
and I know what you want.
But I can't help you.
- Sorry.
- Oh, come on,
- buddy, I just want to chat.
- Yeah? About what?
The weather.
Sports.
By chance, you have any
idea how annoying it is
to be an immortal human being?
I can't say that I do.
Oh, well, let me enlighten you.
You see, first you get to
watch everyone you love die,
over and over.
And that sucks.
And on top of that, it's boring.
I've been everywhere there is to go.
Tried every kind of food.
Sex. Music.
Nothing surprises me anymore.
Have you tried Game of Thrones?
It's been a literal Hell on Earth.
Well, the punishment
fits the crime, Pierce.
A little harsh if you ask me.
My Father always has His reasons.
Right.
I've always wondered
who your Father would assign
such an important task.
It must have been
someone He really trusted.
Maybe... His favorite son.
You marked me, didn't you?
Yeah. It was me.
- And you deserved it.
- I didn't come here
to argue right or wrong. In fact,
I just need your help.
And, see, the good news for me is,
this can actually hurt you now.
You put this mark on me.
Now you're gonna tell
me how to get rid of it.
I didn't kill anyone!
MAZE: And what better way
to prove it than by
swinging a bat at us?
I thought you were trying to kill me.
No, we're trying to help you, Jay.
Your wallet was found
at the scene of a murder.
What the hell's going on?
Fahrid, the dead guy?
- Yeah?
- He was a gem broker
I worked with in L.A.
a few times in the past.
He hired me to
authenticate some diamonds.
Stolen diamonds.
If they were stolen, I had no idea.
But now that I think about it,
Fahrid was acting kind of strange.
- Strange how?
- Jumpy.
He must have made me jumpy,
too, cause I had to pee.
I was in the bathroom when it happened.
You know how I get when I'm nervous.
When I was in there, I heard arguing
and then gunshots.
After I came out, I saw
Fahrid. He was... dead.
I was freaked out, so I bailed.
Hmm.
- [ELLA SPEAKS SPANISH]
- Ella!
I work for the cops, Jay!
I could've helped you.
- Why? Why did you...?
- I didn't want to worry you. Stop!
Please be civilized.
I know it looks bad, but
you got to believe me. I...
I didn't kill anyone.
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE BEEPS ON]
Hey, Chloe. What's up?
So we've had no luck
finding this supposed other person.
We may need to
consider other scenarios.
Like that maybe Jay...
wasn't just a witness to the murder.
Look, I know that this is
tough, but I think it's best
if we talk to Jay first.
So, have you had any luck finding him?
No. No luck.
Okay. Okay. Well,
let us know if you do.
BOTH: She's lying.
Who's lying? Your stylist?
Ella. More and more, it looks like
her brother Jay might be our shooter.
And because she's too close to it,
she can't see the facts clearly.
We need to get inside Ella's head,
figure out where she's taking Jay.
If you were her, where
would you guys go?
Ooh. Uh... strip club.
- Comic-Con.
- Bar.
A forensics convention.
- Strip club.
- Dude, you already said that.
Why would Ella take her
brother to a strip club?
- For the free buffet.
- Above all else, Ella's dedicated
to her job. If she truly
thinks Jay is innocent,
she's gonna want to
prove it, which means...
She'll go back to the crime scene.
So what's it gonna be, Amenadiel?
You gonna help me die, or vice versa?
Pierce, do as you must,
because I can't help you.
You're proud. I get it.
You don't want to upset Daddy.
You might not care if you get killed.
Are you willing to let
an innocent die for pride?
You wouldn't.
I killed my own brother.
What makes you think
I wouldn't kill some random
person to finally have peace?
Maybe the guy wearing the scarf indoors.
No one'll miss him.
Enough!
Yes. I gave you the mark.
But I was only the messenger, Pierce.
I have no idea how to remove it.
Actually, I believe you.
Everybody out! Now!
What are you doing?! I told
you everything I know.
I thought you wouldn't
have been of any use,
- but I needed to make sure.
- [SCOFFS]
So now what?
Well, now I finally get
to kick your angelic ass.
[GRUNTS]
You know, that didn't
feel as good as I'd hoped.
But you know what they say.
At first you don't succeed...
This won't end well for you.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪ Here we go, here we
go, here we go again ♪
♪ Tell your ma, tell your
pa, tell your girlfriend ♪
♪ Here we come, here we
come, here we come again ♪
♪ Take you on a ride
that never ends... ♪
Your Shotokan's not bad.
How's your hapkido?
- Better than yours.
- Yeah?
♪ Better than who came before us ♪
♪ Don't bore us, get to the chorus... ♪
This is getting fun.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
♪ Don't bore us, get to the chorus ♪
♪ Can't stop, can't stop,
can't stop the unstoppable ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stand in our way ♪
♪ Can't stop, can't stop,
can't stop the unstoppable ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna stand in our way... ♪
Are you still having fun?
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh ♪
- [GRUNTING]
- ♪ Yeah, we're back ♪
♪ Yeah, we're back, yeah,
we're back for good ♪
♪ From New York all the
way out to Hollywood... ♪
Don't make me do this.
Do what? You gonna kill me?
♪ Spin you round... ♪
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS LOUDLY]
[GROANS]
Don't think a little
death... is gonna stop me.
♪ Hey... hey ♪
♪ Hey... hey. ♪
Okay, walk me through
exactly what happened.
Like I said, I was in the bathroom
when I heard the gunshots.
Then I stayed quiet.
After I saw the gunman leave, I came out.
Whoa, whoa, wait.
You saw the shooter?
Yeah, I peeked out from the door
and saw him standing over Fahrid.
Jay, if you saw him,
you can identify him.
He wore all black and a ski mask.
I-I didn't get a good look at him.
Come on. Think, Jay. Think.
There has to be something
that you remember.
Wingtips. The guy
wore red wingtip shoes.
Does that help?
Everything helps.
Okay, so you said you saw
him from the bathroom, right?
Jay, the... door opens outward.
So?
So... Jay, from your
vantage point inside,
it would have been impossible
for you to see the killer
standing over the body.
Look, I saw what I saw.
Where's the stash room?
If Fahrid is a diamond thief,
he'd definitely have a stash room.
And if I were him,
I would hide it right...
here.
Looks like laser-engraving equipment.
CHLOE: Ella?
What the hell, Ella!
Did you call the cops?
I trusted you!
No. I swear, I didn't call them!
- This is much more fun than a strip club.
- Is that a stash room?
- Yeah. Full of laser-engraving equipment.
- LUCIFER: Ah!
Seems that Don Zeikel fellow
you were telling me
about was onto something.
Who was onto what?
He's the insurance adjuster
for the missing diamonds.
He said that equipment
replaces the serial number
on the stolen diamonds.
Is that what you were doing?
Okay, fine.
Yeah, I was in here
cleaning the diamonds.
But it was a one-time thing.
Jay, stay calm.
Relax, Jay. We'll go to the precinct,
talk about this, figure it out.
But first you need to put the gun down.
Why? No matter what I say or do,
you're not gonna believe me.
So what's the point?
Wait! You don't have to do this.
Oh, Ms. Lopez.
You still think he's innocent?
[INDISTINCT CHATTER,
CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
Well, Ellen...
it's been fun.
You can't leave.
Why? Job's done.
But Jay needs our help! I mean,
so he got mixed up with some bad dudes.
Okay, he's not a murderer.
He's like Harrison
Ford, but less growly.
The whole police force
thinks that he's guilty now.
We need to get to him first.
You hired me to find him. I found him.
The fee doesn't include
post-seizure baby-sitting.
Please.
[SCOFFS] Fine.
I could stay...
for a price.
But...
I thought... you and I...
you know, we-we connected.
You really don't care at all
about helping me find my brother?
You mean the brother
who forged diamonds,
pulled a gun on us,
probably killed a guy,
and who's definitely been
lying to you all this time?
No, not particularly.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe Jay's not who I thought he was.
Maybe it was... all a lie?
No, but you know what?
Family shouldn't do that to each other.
I mean, we're supposed
to help each other.
Okay.
Good talk.
[SIGHS]
No sign of him.
That was certainly exciting, wasn't it?
- Go ahead. Say it.
- I...
"I told you so, your
brother's a killer."
Come on, say it... that
you were right all along.
Ms. Lopez, uh...
[WHIMPERS]
How could I have been so blind?
I mean, Jay lied to me about everything.
He obviously lied about
seeing the killer. too.
Not necessarily. Ella?
Wait. Maybe Jay did see the killer,
not from the bathroom,
but from right here.
What exactly did he say he saw?
ELLA: Uh, a guy wearing a mask
and... red wingtip shoes.
LUCIFER: Wingtips? Oh.
That's oddly strong
footwear game for a murderer.
Yeah. Stylish.
I think I know who killed Fahrid.
JAY: Fahrid told me
you'd be at this hotel
right before you killed him.
I'm not letting you get away with this.
You're Fahrid's diamond nerd.
I should've figured you'd be in town.
I'm getting blamed for what you did.
You're gonna confess to the murder.
Whatever you want.
Let-let's go to the police.
I-I'll tell the truth.
No!
Do it right now.
Call the cops.
Sure thing.
Uh, can I use your phone?
Mine's dead.
Never held a gun before, have you?
You're gonna kill me now, too?
No. Need you to clean
those diamonds, first.
Then I'll kill you.
Ella, you're too close to it.
- No, Chloe, I can help. It's my brother.
- Hey, hey.
Just trust me, okay?
I promise you, we got this.
♪ I've got all the time ♪
♪ In the world... ♪
♪ ♪
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
That's gonna leave a mark,
at least for a little while.
[GRUNTS]
We don't have to do this.
You didn't have to curse me, either,
but you did that, didn't you?
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
Accept the punishment that you deserve.
You know nothing
about what I deserve.
Oh, I know that my
Father is punishing you
because you killed your own brother.
Yeah, notice anyone else in here
who plotted to kill his own brother?
No, that was different.
Well, it was only
different 'cause you failed.
We are nothing alike.
Yeah, you're right.
At least I had the
balls to do it myself.
[PANTING]
You pawned the task off on
someone else, you're worse.
And if this is the punishment
that I get for my crimes,
what do you deserve?
There it is, that look on your face.
That's what I wanted.
That feels good.
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
Little help?
Jay.
JAY: Get the hell out of here,
crazy woman who I don't know.
And leave you with this psycho
killer, Jay? Are you nuts?
See? Left-handed.
- I knew you were innocent.
- Are you two done?
LAPD knows that you
killed Fahrid Nasser,
thanks to your "on fleek" shoe game.
Look, Fahrid and I
had a good thing going.
For years, he'd steal the diamonds,
I'd write the claim, we split the money.
But the bastard got greedy.
Cut me out. Nobody cuts me out.
Look, man, I'll do whatever you want.
Just leave her out of this.
Sorry. She's seen my face.
You okay?
That's so Maze.
[INDISTINCT POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Hi.
Hey.
So, the knife...
just came out of nowhere, huh?
Yep, just random blade out of thin air.
I mean, anyone could've thrown it.
Crazy.
Ella, I know it was Maze.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
She's my roommate.
I recognize the knife.
But don't worry, she's not in trouble.
She was just trying
to protect you, right?
She saved my life.
So I doubt the DA will press charges.
All he did was intend to
change the serial numbers
on the stolen diamonds,
it's not a crime.
Lucky Jay.
I'm sure if any other cop
had been working this case,
he would have ended
up in prison or worse.
So, well done, Detective.
Oh, my God.
Did the world just turn upside down?
Did you just admit to being wrong?
[LAUGHS] I wouldn't quite go that far...
[LAUGHS]
but I'm sure if you had a brother, he...
he would be very proud of you.
Thank you.
Anyway, this whole torrid affair
started with a bag of stolen diamonds,
so where are the diamonds?
Well, we're still
checking Zeikel's stuff.
You know, houses, cars.
I'm sure they'll turn up.
[CHUCKLES] Indeed.
Uh, did I forget
something at your office?
No. I, uh, I actually,
I actually came to apologize.
For what?
For refusing to treat you.
My extreme reaction
had nothing to do with
how scary... [CHUCKLES]
your story sounded.
Believe me, I've heard much, much worse.
I was holding you accountable
for things you simply didn't do.
I hurt you, didn't I,
during my lost time?
It doesn't matter.
It wasn't you.
So if you want to come
back for a session,
I'd... I'd like to try and help.
I don't need handouts.
I mean, you don't have to treat me.
I think I do...
for both of us.
I just have to check one thing.
Ow!
[EXHALES]
Excellent.
[SLOW HAND CLAP]
LUCIFER: Ah, the slow hand clap,
it never gets old, does it?
[LAUGHS] Hey, man.
It's not what it looks like.
Save it.
Evil Lopez.
Clearly this wasn't a "one-time deal."
It seems you're not quite as virtuous
as your sister would like to believe.
Whatever, man. You
don't know what it's like
making sure everyone's looked after.
It all falls on me.
Ah, so you felt entitled
to stick your hand in
the proverbial cookie jar
because it "took care of your family"?
It started small.
I had to bail a brother out.
Then Abuela needed surgery.
Guess who they all came to.
I didn't choose this.
But the Armani suit
must help ease the pain.
[SCOFFS] I take care of my family,
so if I get a little bit, too, so what?
I'm not perfect.
But you like them to think that you are.
When, really, you're
no better than them.
You're gonna tell Ella, aren't you?
All right, just...
let me do it.
She should hear it from me.
You're not gonna tell her anything.
And neither am I.
You're not?
No.
Ms. Lopez puts a lot of faith in you,
and losing that faith would hurt her.
And I won't allow that to happen.
I'll get my act together, I promise.
No need to promise, Jay Lopez.
Because I'll be watching you,
and if you ever disappoint her again...
I'll come for you.
♪ The mind says no sir ♪
♪ But the body says please ♪
Bloody hell.
♪ The heart stays silent... ♪
What does the other guy look like?
Immortal.
♪ And I don't know why
I'm telling you this ♪
I'm the one that gave
Pierce his mark, Luci.
♪ There's a road once traveled... ♪
[SCOFFS]
Right.
So that's why you wouldn't help.
Didn't want to remove your handiwork.
All of this has nothing to do with me.
I... I couldn't just remove
it, even if I wanted to,
because it's supposed to be there.
Father cursed him for a reason.
[SCOFFS]
I know you think
you're friends with Pierce.
I get it, but I am warning you, Luci.
He has but one selfish goal.
And working with him
will only incur Father's wrath.
[LAUGHING]: What the...?
That's the bloody point.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS] Look, I know...
you're just being a good older brother.
Trying to protect me, 'cause
you think I need protecting.
Yes, that's right, because
I am my brother's keeper.
I am grateful,
Brother, truly, I am.
But I don't need protecting.
All that I am saying
is that this alliance with
Pierce will not end well.
Well, one can only hope.
And all I'm saying
is that if you continue to meddle,
Amenadiel...
then you will be in my way.
Well, then, Brother.
Yes.
I guess I'll be in your way.
Also Download Other Tvseries For Free At
www.Flashtvseries.Tk
www.tvsubtitles.net