- Previously on Lucifer...
- Is it possible
you're not dealing with
something? Chloe and Pierce?
Perhaps you're not as okay with
that relationship as you think.
Decker's the one who's gonna suffer.
Getting her to fall for
you and then vanishing?
Ruthless.
I don't care who I have to hurt,
as long as it allows me to finally die.
Neither I nor Lucifer have the power
to get anyone into Heaven.
There's no hope for me.
I'm going to Hell.
And I am sick
of that stupid little brat of yours.
Pierce, I lo...
Stop.
I can't do this.
What?
Why?
Why did you hurt her?
Why?!
I couldn't... hurt her like that.
Your mark. It's gone.
Just like that... it's gone?
I don't understand. How?
How the hell
did you finally get rid
of your bloody mark?!
I don't know.
I guess the plan worked.
What plan?
The plan to get Chloe to fall for me.
And why would you have a plan for that?
'Cause I finally figured
out what makes us vulnerable.
Us?
It's Chloe's love.
Think about it.
She loves you, you bleed.
Now she loves me, so I can die.
Well, congratulations,
'cause you've just
come to the most absurd
conclusion I think I've ever heard.
Is it?
I tried to stop her
from saying the words.
I didn't want to hurt her.
I guess I was too late.
She already loved me.
Well, allow me to disabuse you
of your misguided notions.
Regardless of the detective's
possible affections,
I think the reason
that your mark is gone
is glaringly obvious,
isn't it?
The moment you chose to pull the ripcord
on your dubious plan,
Dad chose to screw with you.
By giving you exactly what you wanted.
I mean, come on, really.
It's God 101, isn't it?
I really wouldn't be so sure.
Well, you know what? Who cares
why your mark is gone.
The point is that you,
my mortally challenged
friend, can now die.
So just say the magic word
and I'll be... I'll be happy
to help you on your way.
Yeah? We'll go old school, shall we?
Come on!
Let's rock and roll!
Stop.
I got it.
Are you sure?
'Cause really, really, I don't mind.
I've got it.
Fine.
Suit yourself.
- I guess this is good-bye.
- Yeah.
But, on the bright side,
see you never.
Hey, Ella, do we have, uh...
the-the forensics on the Duckworth case?
Dope shades, missy!
Thanks.
Yeah, I only wear mine inside
when I'm like, super hungover
or, you know, for some
reason I've been crying.
Right.
Oh, no.
What happened?
It's...
Pierce and I broke up.
What?
- Yeah.
- Why?
You were so great together.
Uh, yeah. I... I don't know.
I guess he just, he
freaked out and he ran.
I-I'm guessing
he's terrified of intimacy. I...
I'm just trying not
to take it personally,
'cause it's not like this is
the first time this has happened,
so I just...
wonder if it's something I'm doing.
No way.
That is some bull to
the crap, right there.
Okay, anyhow...
I'm gonna walk into Pierce's office
and I'm gonna give that
studly, big-armed man
a serious what for.
Hey.
Please do not say anything.
All right? It's just gonna
make things more complicated.
Fine.
Okay, I-I won't interfere.
How could you do this to her?
You made her so happy!
If you must know,
I was trying to protect her.
I broke things off
because I didn't want to hurt Chloe.
I know you're my boss, so
don't take this the wrong way,
but do you know how stupid that sounds?
If you really cared about her,
then what are you protecting her from?
I guess nothing anymore.
I can actually be with her.
I can grow old with her.
Uh, maybe...
I mean, that's a little
cart before the horse, don't ya think?
No, you're right, Lopez.
I totally screwed this up.
Yeah. You did.
- I need to win her back.
- Mm-hmm.
How am I gonna do that?
I have faith.
- Good morning!
- Morning.
Detective, uh, as someone
who goes to therapy,
I understand you must have many...
feelings following last night's debacle.
So, if you feel the need to discuss...
No, it's okay. I really
don't want to talk about it.
Excellent. I mean, you know,
whatever works for you works for me.
After all, if all goes as
it should, we'll probably
never be hearing from that
lying lieutenant ever...
again...
Shouldn't you be, uh, I don't know,
having tea with Hitler by now?
Change of plans. I don't
want to die anymore.
I want to win Chloe back.
I beg your pardon?
No time to explain.
Okay, I know you probably
hate me right now,
but please, just hear me out.
You were right, about
last night... I got scared.
Things got very real between us and I...
I couldn't handle it. Okay?
And... I'm not used to feeling this way.
And I realize that now and that's why
I promise it'll never
happen again, because...
because I love you.
What?
I love you, Chloe.
Wh-What do you expect me to say to that?
Well, that you love me, too.
Look, Marcus, as much as I appreciate
hearing you say those words...
that's what they are:
they're just words.
I can't trust them anymore.
Our victim is Reina Markova,
29, prima ballerina
for the L.A. West Ballet
four years and running.
Cleaning staff found her when
they came in this morning.
Any witnesses?
Uh, no. She's known for
taking rehearsals alone.
Especially when she's two days away
from a big premiere like Giselle.
Hmm. Hey, Ella.
Any idea of the time of death?
Looks like she was killed
roughly ten hours ago.
Oh, what a coincidence.
She's been dead almost as long
as your dreadful relationship to Pierce.
They broke up?
Actually, he broke up with her.
- Okay.
- What about cause of death?
Right.
Well, according to
the ligature marks on her throat,
she was strangled...
using the ties from this.
She was killed with her own shoe?
Not her shoe. Different size.
But why leave the murder weapon behind?
Maybe whoever did this
freaked out and ran?
- We've seen it before.
- Oh, yes, we have,
from the lowest form of
scum on earth... like Pierce.
Well, come on.
I mean, we're all
thinking it, aren't we?
Anyway, time to get the
slipper back to the lab.
Any other questions, here's my prelim.
Uh... I'm gonna join her, 'cause...
because this is awkward.
Oh, and, uh, personally,
I'm with you, buddy.
Screw that guy.
So, we're searching
for a murderous Cinderella.
Yes, someone timelessly evil.
Almost like a cretinous
lieutenant named...
Enough, Lucifer.
This murder has nothing
to do with Pierce.
Well, not literally, perhaps...
I know you want me to hate him.
To tell you he's terrible.
But the truth is, our relationship
is none of your business.
- Former relationship, you mean?
- Yes.
- No, no...
- No?
- I-I don't, I don't know.
Point being, you need to back off.
Whether I decide
to take Pierce back or not, it just,
it has nothing to do with you.
Or maybe it still does.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Great news!
The detective still makes me bleed.
Which means there's hope.
Uh, hope for...
Well, for the detective, of course!
Hope that she hasn't fully succumbed
to that intolerable knob, Pierce.
Even if he has lost his mark.
Pierce lost his what now?
Allow me to catch you up.
So, the lieutenant
has a ridiculous theory
that, shockingly, may hold water.
He believes that the
detective's affections
are what make me vulnerable.
And now that she cares for him...
Well, long story short, old
ham hands isn't cursed anymore.
He's mortal.
So, your vulnerability is proof
that Chloe cared for you...
but now she cares for Pierce,
- so now he's vulnerable, too.
- Close.
She cares for Pierce and me.
As proven by my bleeding.
Yet, for some inexplicable reason,
she's on the fence
between the two of us.
And how does that make you feel?
Well, it makes me feel...
like I...
like I need to tip
the scales in my favor.
Show her
which side the grass is greener on.
And why do you want to
tip Chloe to your side?
Because, as her partner,
it's my duty to save her from
making a terrible mistake.
Uh-huh.
Pierce has clearly blinded her
with his charming oaf routine.
So I need to open her eyes.
Show her that I'm better than
him in every possible way.
And what if Chloe does choose you?
Well, then, things can finally
go back to the way they were,
before Pierce, obviously.
Uh...
Why do I feel like I should've
stopped him this time?
What the hell is this?
It's pretty self-explanatory.
- The plan is off.
- Why?
We were so close to
getting happily-sexed Decker
to fall for you.
Yeah, and I messed it up,
okay? I broke up with her.
You broke up with her?
What happened to
getting rid of your mark?
Doesn't matter.
I'm done with grand
plans and manipulations.
I don't want to use Chloe anymore.
What about what I want?
Because if we don't
get Chloe to love you,
then we can't lift your curse.
And if we can't lift your curse,
then I can't kill you
and hang it on Lucifer.
Framing Lucifer for murder
is the only way to blow
up his life on Earth.
Keep your voice down.
What don't you get?
My side of the plan
doesn't work without yours.
And I need this
to get back to Hell.
I'm sorry. Like I said, the plan's off.
Says you.
Detective.
Pardon my tardiness,
but I come bearing gifts.
What is this?
Well, I know how you like
your seasonal beverages,
so I got you a "Luck o' the Irish" Latte
and... oh! To be sure, to be sure,
little something extra.
Oh, y-you got me a lemon bar.
Mm, well, they're your
favorites, aren't they?
- Mm...
- Look, Detective,
I know that you're going through
a difficult time right now,
and what you need
is someone who knows you.
I know. It's just...
- Um...
- It's just what?
Ooh, lemon bars. My favorite. Mmm.
Oh, man, these are
amazing. Who made 'em?
Uh, Pierce did.
Would you believe that hunk bakes?
On second thought, who
needs the empty calories?
Hmm.
Hmm, looks like someone
is trying to crawl their
way out of the doghouse.
Mm-hmm
- Is it working?
- Yes, is it?
Let's just focus on the case.
Ella, what do you have?
Uh, so I got a lead
off the murder weapon.
No match on the DNA, but I
did find a signature of sorts.
The ballet shoe had traces
of olive oil, Evian and beeswax.
So our killer's a bumblebee
with expensive taste?
Or a ballerina.
Dancers all have their own unique way
of prepping their shoes.
And, according to her social media,
guess who uses those exact ingredients?
Reina's former understudy
and L.A. West Ballet's
new prima ballerina,
Amber Fontaine.
So either she took out her competition
or the killer somehow
got one of her shoes?
No, no, no, definitely
looks like a Black Swanto me.
And bras and up. Ladies, arms out...
Sorry to interrupt.
We'd like to speak
- with Amber Fontaine.
- For what?
We're extremely busy here.
Yes, us, too.
Solving the crime of a
brutally murdered ballerina.
But Amber didn't have
anything to do with that.
And we only got two days
- to get this show up and running.
- Easy, easy, Gwen.
They're just doing their jobs.
I'm sorry.
We're just all pretty
emotional right now.
Yes, clearly some more than others.
We know it was your shoe
that was used to strangle Reina.
That's crazy.
The killer must've stolen
them out of my locker.
I mean, Reina's locker.
Look, respect for going
full Tonya Harding,
but if you're gonna kill someone,
you should get your
story straight first.
No, Reina's locker was
mine for, like, a week
when she left the
company for her new gig.
But when she came back,
I had to return it.
I-I must've left my
pointe shoes in there.
- Where were you last night?
- Home.
Sleeping like a baby.
You can ask my roommate.
Now that Reina's dead,
I'm back to being tied in knots.
Yes, murder can do that.
No, as much as I thought that I wanted
her spot, to be able to dance
with a legend like Miguel,
I-I wasn't ready.
I was happy to keep learning from Reina.
I thought it was our
gain and their loss.
Whose loss exactly?
You know, America's
Next Prima Ballerina.
The TV show Reina was gonna host.
You know, I'm inclined to
believe our young ingenue.
If there's nothing she and
Reina were competing for,
it makes her motive far less compelling.
Yeah, we need to look into this TV show,
see why she turned it down.
Well, it certainly wouldn't
be art over commerce.
No one has that kind of passion...
Are those from...
Marcus. Yeah.
Bastard.
Luci, what is so urgent?
Why'd you call me here?
Because enough is enough. It's time.
We need to get rid of Pierce.
What exactly do you mean by
"get rid of Pierce"?
Well, what do you think I mean?
Yeah, we're not gonna kill him, Luci.
I know, angels can't kill humans,
yadda yadda yadda.
Spare me the lecture.
Besides, killing Pierce
isn't the answer anyway
because, inexplicable as it is,
the detective actually
cares for the man,
and breaking her heart isn't the goal.
I got to admit, I'm a little
fuzzy on that one myself.
What is the goal?
For the detective to
realize she needs to pick me
over that blithering
clod, Pierce, which...
gah, shouldn't even be an issue, but...
- I'm in.
- You are?
You are my brother and my test.
Whatever needs to be done.
Well, I have to admit,
I didn't expect that
to be quite so easy,
but I'm not one to look
a gift-angel in the mouth,
I'll take it.
So what's the plan?
We need to make the detective realize
that Pierce isn't the
man she thinks he is.
We need to prove to her
that he is a two-faced,
loathsome biblical liar.
I mean, how hard can that be?
He is the man behind the whole
Sinnerman thing, after all.
Um... what?
Oh, I'm sorry. Didn't I tell you?
Fun fact: Pierce equals
criminal mastermind.
Anyway...
You run with that, and I'll
keep working on the detective.
Read my lips:
Dance is pain.
You want to feel sorry for yourselves?
Then go back to Kansas
or wherever you're from.
That is Myles Druker.
Only one of the most amazing
choreographers in the world.
Choreographer with a bum leg?
Is this one of those, "those
who can't, teach" scenarios?
He was a dancer who lost
his leg in a car crash.
But he never believed
in playing the victim.
Instead,
he turned his tragedy
into an inspirational story
for all of us to follow.
He's also the creator of
America's Next Prima Ballerina,
the show that Reina was gonna host,
until she reneged on her deal
and it cost him a fortune.
Right. Well, I don't see why
he wouldn't take such a loss in stride.
- You see what I did there?
- Mm-hmm.
In stride?
You must be aware that Reina Markova
was killed last night.
Yeah, I heard. Big whoop.
Well, for a potential
cold-blooded killer,
you're being quite... obvious.
I mean, I just don't think
Reina was much of a professional.
Then why'd you hire her?
Let's just say I was... pressured
into our collaboration.
By whom?
By none of your business.
Look, I'm a very busy man,
so unless you're gonna charge me
with anything, we're done here.
Well, actually, no.
I just have one more question.
Uh, take note, Detective.
Here's something I can
do that other people,
rhymes with Shmierce, cannot.
Tell me,
what is it that you truly desire?
- I wish...
- Yeah.
That car crash never happened.
Why? 'Cause it crushed your leg?
No.
Because it didn't crush my leg.
Oh!
Right, well.
Care to explain?
Everyone believes the
accident ruined my career.
Well, the truth is, it made it.
I built my brand on the notion
that I could overcome anything.
I walk around with a
prosthetic every day
covering my real leg.
Polypropylene.
Oh. So is that why Reina left the show?
She found out you were a fraud?
No, she quit because I
accused her of blackmailing me.
I was sent an e-mail
with a video that exposed me...
You know, with two working legs...
Said that if I gave Reina a
job, the video would disappear.
So I did.
But she didn't send it?
Apparently not,
even though it was sent
from her e-mail address,
because when I confronted
her, she went ballistic.
Said that she didn't need any
handouts and quit right there.
But if she didn't
blackmail you, then who did?
Beats me.
Right. Well, you better
not be pulling our legs.
What are you doing here, Charlotte?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm a terrible person that's...
that's led a terrible life, so I'm...
I'm preparing myself for damnation.
In a three-star hotel?
It's what I deserve.
Well, it's time to sober up.
I need your help with a legal matter.
Don't you want to ask
someone less damned?
I don't think so.
I need to find a way to prove
that Lieutenant Pierce
is the criminal mastermind
also known as the Sinnerman.
Say again?
Lieutenant Pierce has
been leading a double life
for quite some time now.
I need to prove it,
and then I need get
him out of the picture
so that Lucifer can be with Chloe.
I'm gonna need a little
bit more information.
A very long time ago,
God tasked me with blessing
a couple with a miracle child.
Now, that child became Chloe Decker,
who, it appears,
was placed on this Earth
to cross paths with Lucifer.
Now, since Lucifer is my test,
bringing those two together
must be my final task.
At which point,
hopefully I'll be restored
in my Father's eyes.
Okay, let me see if I
understand this correctly.
I help you,
I help enact God's will?
In a way, yes.
And could that...
put me in His good graces as well?
Maybe.
Good enough.
I'm in.
And I think I know how to get started.
Well, I'd say that was rather
impressive, wouldn't you?
I exposed a fraud of a
man and got us a lead.
It's like the whole
world is pointing towards,
well, me, today.
Yes, Lucifer,
very impressive.
Unfortunately, until cyber traces
this blackmail e-mail,
we have nothing to do tonight.
Oh, nonsense, nonsense.
The night's still young.
Why don't we, um, I don't know,
- go for a drive?
- For a drive?
What are we, 80? Why
would we go for a dri...
Ta-da!
I mean, it's not flowers, but
it does go zero to 60 in, well... fast.
You...
- You got me a car?
- Mm-hmm.
Wait, do you think this is
some sort of competition?
Of course. If it isn't
painfully obvious,
anything Pierce can do, I can do better.
It's not about stuff, Lucifer.
Thanks anyhow.
Good morning.
Good morning?
Last I checked, didn't you move out?
It's mea culpa time.
I came to earn my way back
into the house.
Really? And how do
you plan on doing that?
Well, I tried to think
of something nice,
but that's not really my strong suit.
But then I heard you
and Pierce broke up.
So, I figured he hurt you.
Maybe I just hurt him back?
Thanks, but-but no.
I mean, at least not yet.
Ah.
Men are so fricking confusing.
Yeah, they're dumb. Really dumb.
Mm-hmm.
What happened?
Well...
one minute, things
with Marcus are great.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then the next,
he ends things, and, uh...
And now he's doing all of these...
really, really sweet
things to win me back.
And it does seem really nice,
but I just don't know if I can trust it.
I don't know, ho...
How do you know if you can trust people?
It's simple. I can't.
People will always let you down.
You know what I do trust? Pain.
And I admit,
Pierce is in a whole lot of it.
What? How do you know that?
Well, I may have already gone
to his house to kick his ass
before it occurred to
me I should probably
have asked for permission.
- Maze...
- But I...
I stopped myself. So there's that.
Oh, Pierce was putting on a brave face,
but... dude was hurting.
Hey, Mom, what's for break...
Hey.
It's gonna... take a little time.
Hey, Dan, what's up?
Cyber came back.
Turns out the blackmail e-mail Myles got
pinged to an apartment registered
to a William Sterling...
Chairman of the board
of L.A. West Ballet,
well-known surgeon,
married, two children.
Why would he be trying
to get Reina a new job?
Uh, maybe he was trying to
get the company some press.
Who knows?
Uh, what's the address?
- Lucifer.
- Detective.
Good morning. Please,
- come in.
- What are you doing here?
Well... I realized that you were right.
It's not about the stuff
that I can give you,
it's about actions.
So, I decided to get a jump on the case
and take a few things off your plate.
Which, I might add, is
the opposite of Pierce,
whose job it is to put
things on your plate.
- Uh-huh. Where's Sterling?
- Not here.
Which is convenient,
as it's given me time
to learn a few things about our, well,
slightly deranged suspect.
Lucifer, did you break in here?
Detective...
I'm disappointed you'd
think so little of me.
Would you believe it if I told you
an attractive neighbor
with a key simply let me in?
Unfortunately, yes.
Excellent. Then, on with the tour.
So, I have come to the conclusion
that we are inside the
lair of a creepy stalker,
evidenced by photos
of Sterling with Reina.
Clearly photoshopped.
Uh, some of her
undergarments lying around.
Don't want to know how he got those.
And, um... for the grand finale...
a shrine dedicated to
Reina's old costumes.
Probably liked the smell of
her old sweat... disgusting.
Lucifer, I think...
Sterling is a lovesick obsessive
who wanted to see Reina's star rise?
Yes, me too. But clearly his gift
of a shiny new job wasn't met kindly,
and so he...
Aha!
Ha, I caught you, you sicko!
What did I say, Detective?
Actions, not stuff.
Lucifer, let him go. He's not a stalker.
He and Reina were having an affair.
Isn't that right, Mr. Sterling?
Uh...
I never met anyone quite like her.
She was the love of my life.
You mean, the love of
your Tuesday afternoons
and occasional Saturday
mornings, don't you?
You are married, with offspring,
are you not?
You don't always get to pick
who you fall in love with.
Is that why you
blackmailed Myles Druker,
to show Reina how much you cared?
I don't know what you're talking about.
There's a blackmail video that
was sent from Reina's e-mail.
It was pinged from
this physical address,
and that's why Myles hired her.
And when she found out, she quit.
Did she confront you? Rebuff you?
'Cause it can be quite daunting
when somebody doesn't
appreciate your gifts.
Perhaps you,
oh, I don't know, lost your temper.
Uh, that's absurd. I didn't care
who Reina worked with.
I certainly wouldn't hurt her over it.
But if you didn't send the e-mail,
- then who did?
- Mm.
I don't know.
Maybe someone snuck onto her computer.
- Is that her computer?
- Yeah.
Who else knows about this place?
No one, I thought.
Guess I was wrong.
Okay, well, we're gonna need to
take the computer into evidence.
I cannot believe
how well this is working out.
I mean, finding Pierce
with a known fence?
Who knew the LAPD could be so helpful?
Well, the LAPD didn't help with this.
I called in a favor, had
Pierce's phone hacked.
Charlotte!
If I wanted to break the law,
I wouldn't have gone to a DA.
And if I hadn't cut
corners, we wouldn't be here
as quickly or efficiently or
as... Well, hell, who cares?
We're working for God now. Right?
Well...
can't argue with results.
Okay, I think we got what we need.
Uh, not exactly.
I'm afraid all that you have
are a few photos of an envelope.
If we want to expose Pierce,
we have to find out what's inside.
Aw, crap. He's on the move.
Well, maybe we...
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna
need to borrow your bike.
Don't worry, it's for God.
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
I said, who are you?
Ms. Richards.
Why are you...
Following you?
Well, it seems I let my better judgment
get away from me.
I don't understand.
It's complicated.
See...
when I heard that you
and Chloe broke up,
I started thinking about you.
I know how hard it is
to be stuck in a dark place.
Sometimes, all it takes
is the right person
to get you out.
After all...
we both have needs.
Another time.
Hell, I'd be the
luckiest guy in the world,
but I'm in love with Chloe.
Sorry.
I know we knew what was on this video,
yet somehow actually seeing
Myles' fake-fake leg...
- So much grosser.
- Great.
The man's an embarrassment
to both dance and prosthetics.
Well, we're just lucky that
cyber could retrieve this
from Reina's computer.
Dan, is there any way to tell
who made this from the footage?
Nothing, no voice. Not
even a measly cough.
Whoever did this was
pretty damn careful.
Yeah, we're still
waiting for DNA results
from the computer's keyboard,
but if the killer wore gloves,
I mean, we're out of luck.
It's Pierce.
Well, someone needs to hit "ignore."
We'll get it.
Hey, Pierce, what's up?
Chloe, hi.
Listen, I realize that
lemon bars and flowers
aren't gonna cut it.
I think I figured out
a way to prove to you
you can trust me.
Can you meet me at my
place for dinner tonight? 8-00?
Eh, I don't know.
Chloe, please.
Listen, if you don't
want to see me after,
I promise I will never bother you again.
Just... just come over.
You gotta eat, right?
Okay. Yeah, I can do dinner.
Great. I'll see you then.
- Detective.
- Hmm?
I couldn't help but
overhear a part of your call
and I understand that you're torn,
but before you make a decision
about Pierce I'd like the chance
to express some
thoughts to you, as well.
Okay. Go ahead.
Right, well, I...
Actually, can we do this in private?
My place, one hour?
Uh... okay.
Lovely.
Detective.
Thank you for coming.
I thought you were having
me over to tell me something?
Well, all shall be
explained in due time.
But please, take a seat.
Now, I hope you like
chateaubriand.
Um...
Lucifer, what is all this?
This is to help you
make an appropriate
decision about your future
and, dare I say,
our future.
Now, we've been through
a lot, Detective.
But now the two of us are alone
in front of this beautiful meal
in this romantic setting, I can finally
ask you the question I
brought you here to answer
and I hope, well, I hope
you can answer honestly.
Isn't this better than
anything Pierce could do?
You did all of this
to... to show up Pierce?
It's impressive. I know.
Detective.
Those aren't tears of joy, are they?
Why are you doing this to me?
To prove to you that you
shouldn't be with Pierce.
Why do you care who I'm with?
'Cause he... he doesn't deserve you.
Then who does deserve me?
Someone...
someone better.
You can't have it both ways, Lucifer.
Detective, I...
Hey, Dan. What's up?
We got a lead.
So, DNA on the computer
came back negative.
So, we decided we had to watch
the creepy leg video again.
But that's when we saw it,
hidden in the window's reflection.
It looked like one of
those Magic Eye pictures.
- You know the ones where it looks like...
- G-Guys, what did you see?
- Oh. Yeah.
- Oh, right. Yes.
We are sending over the
enhanced image as we speak.
Recognize that costume?
Okay, we know Miguel
is behind the video,
but what I don't understand is why.
Why would he risk everything
just to get rid of Reina?
Well, isn't it obvious?
He wanted to be with her.
There.
Why did you do it?!
Why did you have to
take Reina away from me?
Answer me. Why did you kill Reina?
Drop the weapon!
You had no right! You had no right!
Wait!
Don't you see?
He didn't want to kill Reina.
Lucifer, get back.
He tried everything to simply
get her out of the way.
All those times you came to pick her up.
She was your friend.
How could you hurt her?
I thought he cared for her.
Yes. But she was also an obstacle
to being with the woman
Miguel loved... Amber.
But why kill Reina?
Because she found out I was
trying to blackmail Myles.
She was gonna get me fired.
And then he wouldn't even be able
to work in the same company as Amber.
Why didn't you just
tell Amber how you feel?
Tell her the truth?
Because...
I was afraid.
Afraid she wouldn't love you back.
But I do.
I-I do have feelings for you, Miguel.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
To think...
you could've had everything you wanted.
All you needed to do was
tell Amber how you felt,
but you blew it.
And so did I.
It's got to be around here somewhere.
Oh, I got it.
It's empty?
I don't understand.
Was he on to us?
I mean... did he destroy what's inside?
Maybe he just took it with him.
I'm sorry, Charlotte.
We did everything that we could.
We're just too late.
Don't be ridiculous.
If I believed in "too late" I
wouldn't be doing any of this.
No, we are not giving up.
After all, you don't quit
when you're doing God's work.
I'm so sorry.
Ever since you left my
office, I've been struggling
between my role as your therapist
and my concern for you as a friend.
Friendship won.
But too late, it seems.
Well, I royally screwed
up this time, Linda.
Turns out
I'm just as bad as our killer.
Oh, God. You killed Pierce?
No.
But I did try everything to get
that lovesick, former immortal
out of the picture when
really all I should've done
was told the detective how I felt...
how I really feel.
Then why don't you?
I can't.
What are you so afraid of?
At first it was your devil face.
What now?
You don't want Chloe to
see that you have wings?
Who cares?
- I do! I care!
- Why?!
Because she doesn't
have a choice, does she?
Neither do I!
It's all part of His
master plan to toy with us,
to make us dance for
His bloody amusement.
That's an excuse.
Don't you see?
You're doing the same thing as Him now.
By not telling Chloe the truth,
you're taking her choice away.
No.
No, it's different.
You know, the truth is...
no one really knows what
your dad's responsible for.
We're all just guessing.
Even you.
But you know the one
thing He can't control?
What you do in this moment right now.
So I ask you,
the Devil...
what do you truly desire?
I want her to choose me.
Then tell her.
Yes.
I'm sorry for just stopping by,
but when you didn't make dinner...
No, I, i-it's... I'm sorry.
This case has, you know, been...
It's okay.
I can say what I need
to say here... now.
Okay.
For days I've been thinking
about how I screwed up.
Tried to figure out how
to make things better.
When you find that person
who gives life meaning,
Chloe, nothing else matters.
Okay, well...
I know you don't trust me.
I know I've made mistakes.
I've made an eternity's
worth of mistakes.
But please, let me
spend the rest of my days
making it up to you.
What? What are you doing?
Chloe Decker, will you marry me?
Yes.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net