I never felt like that before.
That was...
Exhilarating.
That man was so terrible.
Truly evil.
We made him pay.
Please.
Who can we punish next?
I want to feel like that again.
Yes, it's quite the rush,
finally being who I'm meant to be.
But, sadly, my dear, criminals
don't line up to be punished.
So that's why you work with the LAPD.
It all makes so much sense now.
You use them to find the bad guys.
Well, I want in.
Ah!
- Do you now, darling?
- Mm-hmm.
Maybe we could do it together.
Find the worst of the worst
and give them what they deserve.
So, Julian, you admit to...
human trafficking and to
the murder of Gary Van Blunt
and officer John Reyes.
Yes.
You're going to jail for a
really long time, cop killer.
- At least I'll be safe there.
- What?
If you didn't break your
back falling down a hill,
we need to know about that now.
I fell down the hill.
I f... fell down the
hill, I sw... I swear!
Chloe.
What's up?
Julian's reaction.
Does it look familiar to you?
- Huh?
- Like people we've seen before
after a certain consultant
has been left alone with them.
What do you mean?
- I think Lucifer did this.
- That's crazy.
You know what's crazy? How
much Lucifer gets away with.
I'm sick of it. Aren't you?
Lucifer wouldn't do this.
He wouldn't go this far.
He would never take
justice into his own hands?
Especially as a cop was killed
because of his stupid recklessness.
You need to cut him some slack.
You have had a target
on his back ever since...
well...
Charlotte.
I'm just not sure if you're
looking at this objectively.
That's all.
Like you are?
I could understand Lucifer
callously ignoring our duty
to keep humans and the divine separate.
But you?
How could you do this?
A child...
with a human?
Wonderful human.
I know how difficult this
must be for you. All right?
I used to be just like you.
Looking down on humans
as if they were ants.
But we need to realize
that we are not above them.
I am above them.
But you...
You don't even have your
powers anymore, do you?
No, I can no longer
slow time and I'm glad.
My powers, they kept me at a distance,
kept me disconnected from humanity.
And I think that's why they're gone now.
Because I don't want that anymore.
You were the one who taught me
that celestials and
humans need to be separate.
Yes, Remy, I did, and
now I am telling you
that I was wrong.
Let me show you.
Hey, Ella, who do we have?
Hey, Chloe.
Victim died from a gunshot straight
to the head up on that bridge.
But apparently murdering wasn't enough.
So they tossed his body over
the bridge like day-old garbage.
Broke nearly every bone in
his body from the looks of it.
Hmm.
Are you okay?
Just death. People die.
Mm-hmm.
Well, we just deal with it.
Anyhow, what do we know about this guy?
Sam Zofrelli.
Rap sheet filled with
drug possession charges.
Oh! We also found traces of cocaine
in his pockets, but
no sign of drug use.
So I'm thinking probably dealer.
- So you think this was about drugs?
- Maybe. Pockets were empty.
Keys, wallet, all gone.
But the body was here for hours
so could have been taken
by anyone brave enough
to frisk a corpse this effed-up.
But why throw a body over a bridge
that's already dead?
Where's Lucifer?
Oh, he's been ignoring me actually.
Oh, he's with Eve.
Yes, probably with Eve.
What you think of her?
I think that she's rubbing off on
him and not necessarily in a good way.
Good morning, Detective.
Please don't tell me she's behind me.
She's behind you.
Hello.
Lucifer.
This is a crime scene. No
visitors. No offense, Eve.
Eve wants the same thing we do.
- Catch a killer.
- Yes.
I am here to learn from you, Chloe.
I want to know everything there is
to know about catching criminals.
Especially the very, very bad ones.
Can I talk to you, alone?
Of course.
This isn't gonna work.
I agree. A gingham pocket square can
be a bit aggressive, but I'm feeling it.
- No. Eve being here, not OK.
- Why not?
You can't just join a
case for the fun of it.
We are solving a
murder. This is serious.
Oh, I agree. Very serious.
If that's how you feel,
I completely understand.
Where are you going?
If you don't want us here,
we'll find the killer on our own.
You can't do that.
Oh, yes we can.
Okay, fine.
Fine. Eve can ride
along just for this case.
Exciting!
This is going to be so much fun.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
Lucifer, this guy looks really guilty.
What about this guy?
That's one mean looking face.
- We should punish them.
- One criminal at a time, dear.
Decker.
No, I will not accept his call.
Who was that?
Nobody.
Ah-ah-ah!
Lucifer's bringing his
girlfriend on cases now, huh?
She's actually really sweet.
Anyway, you know what?
Why not do whatever makes you happy?
Because any second, bam! You can get hit
by a chunk of blue ice from an airplane
or get blown up into a million
pieces by some crazed killer.
Or you could mysteriously
break your spinal cord
and become, you know, paralyzed.
Yeah.
Is anybody investigating what
happened to Julian McCaffrey?
Nobody's buying his "I fell
down the hill" story, right?
He didn't file any charges, so
there's nothing to investigate.
Even if we wanted to,
remember that house he lived in? It's
probably been professionally cleaned.
You're right.
You're absolutely right.
Oh, that's Daniel.
He's a douche again.
Oh, shall we punish him too?
Believe me, his existence
is punishment enough.
Hey, Ella. What do we have?
Well, we still don't know why Sam's
body was tossed off the bridge.
Because the killer is a maniacal
monster who needs to be taken down.
Er... maybe.
But I did discover that the killer
pistol-whipped poor Sam before he died.
- Sounds like it could be personal.
- And aggressive.
And cruel.
And a mistake, because I
was able to recover something
from the gun marks on his face.
Gold flakes.
- Gold flakes?
- Mm-hmm.
In there? That's amazing.
Ah! Well, you know,
I'm just doing my job.
Do you get to be there
for the punishment too?
Er, no.
Golden gun.
It's unique and it sounds familiar.
Yes, Roger Moore's Bond films.
Perhaps our killer's Scaramanga,
the man with three nipples.
Maybe.
Ella, do you remember
there was a hitman...
or something who carries a golden
pistol. Do you remember that?
Ah, let me see.
Er... ooh, right here.
Greg Grabowski...
and goes by the nickname "Pony Boy".
Pony Boy? Stay gold indeed.
And you're never able to pin
him down because he's so good.
But if this wasn't a
hit and it was personal,
it would explain why he was so sloppy.
He sounds terrible.
- Let's go punish him!
- You mean, bring him to justice.
That's what I said.
Oh! That clears that up. Come on.
When I was a newborn demon...
I was smaller than my opponents.
But I was fast.
So I used my speed, kept low...
and always went for the major arteries.
With my first vanquished
foe on his knees,
I slit my blade across his throat.
I felt the heat from his
blood dripping down my face.
And then a stranger heat in my loins.
Okay.
When I mentioned that
the baby could hear
everything from inside the womb
I imagined introducing
him to things like
classical music...
and stories...
that aren't about graphic murders.
Why would you want to hear a
story not about graphic murder?
We can talk about that later.
- I have to go to work.
- Great.
Give me a second to get my knives.
Maze, sweetie.
You can't come to work with me.
I have to!
Do you know all the things that could
happen to you or your baby out there?
Er... heartburn?
You could get gunned down in
a drive-by shooting, Linda.
Or kidnapped by a cartel
who use women as drug mules,
not to mention what an angel baby
will fetch on the black market.
How comforting.
You said I'm part of this family, Linda.
So I'm going to protect you.
Maze, the people I am
seeing this afternoon
are a vegan chef who
compulsively shoplifts...
and a record producer who wets the bed.
- But I...
- Maze...
I don't need protecting.
What you doing?
Oh, hey. Er...
I paid off the cleaning
crew in Julian's house.
What? I'm looking for
something in his trash to prove
that somebody was there
the night he was paralyzed.
Well, I don't know about any of
that, but I can help if you want.
Lucifer's brand.
What did you say?
Er, nothing.
I, uh,
found what I needed.
Oh, er... Don't worry about
me, Dan. I can clean up.
Damn, these guys are huge.
We can take them, right, honey?
Of course I can, darling, I'm the Devil.
In that case, I hope
this guy we're after
is the biggest, meanest one there is.
We don't want that.
I do.
Makes it more satisfying
when Lucifer beats them up.
We don't beat people up in
the middle of the street.
Oh. Do we take them back
to Lucifer's penthouse?
Anyway. We don't beat
people up anywhere.
Unless they resist and
then it's Devil by TKO.
Don't worry, they always resist.
There's Pony Boy.
Look at those arms.
Let's not get carried away.
Greg "Pony Boy" Grabowski,
LAPD. You're under arrest
- for the murder...
- Okay.
- What?
What was that? I thought
they always resisted.
Look. I've been through
this a hundred times.
I'm just gonna wait for my lawyer.
Lucifer, you should torture the truth
out of him until his lawyer shows up.
Eve, that's not how this works.
Everybody calm down. Eve just
wants to see the devil do his thing.
And there is one thing
you haven't seen me do.
Tell me...
My little Pony Boy,
what is it you desire?
I...
I wish...
wish my boss had let me kill Sam.
- Oh.
- Hmm.
Sorry, darling, we can't
punish him after all.
The man's innocent.
Are you crazy?
Watching the devil
do this thing is so...
hot.
So you wished your
boss let you kill him.
Then who's your boss
and if it wasn't you,
who used your golden gun to do it?
Lawyer. Now.
I mean...
Turn around.
It's fun, isn't it?
Hey, Chloe.
I know that look.
You found something.
I hope so.
Hitmen are often paid
as corporate employees
through shell companies
to hide the money.
But it also sometimes means that
they get the corporate perks.
Like covering their gym membership fees.
So who's paying for Pony
Boy to get so jacked?
It looks like it all tracks
back to Jacob Tiernan here.
That paralyzed dude's dad?
Does this have something
to do with that case?
Tiernan's son shows up
paralyzed from the chest down.
Then this guy dies.
So it has to be, right?
I think Sam's bones were
broken before he was killed
in the exact same
spot that Julian's was.
Julian McCaffrey?
- Yeah.
- What does this have to do with him?
Maybe Tiernan thought that
Sam broke Julian's back.
Normally he'd hire Pony
Boy to do his dirty work,
- but it's his son so...
- He wanted to enact revenge himself
and borrowed Pony Boy's gun to do it.
- Yes.
- I'll get you the ME report.
Great.
Hey. Luce.
I did that.
I broke Julian's back.
Tiernan killed an innocent man.
What does that mean?
It means, my dear,
that now more than ever
that monster needs to be punished.
Mr. Tiernan, I don't know if you heard
but a drug dealer was
killed this morning.
What does that have to do with me?
Well, that's the interesting part.
He had the exact same
spinal injury as your son.
So it would seem that possibly
someone is out for revenge.
My son worked with a lot of bad people.
In fact, Julian wasn't
exactly a good person himself,
which is why I had to
excise him from my business.
You... you love your children,
but at a certain point
- you have to let them...
- Stand on their own two legs.
Mr Tiernan, do you know a
man named Greg Grabowski?
Goes by the colorful moniker "Pony Boy".
No.
Hmm. That's odd,
because one of your
companies pays his bills.
I have a lot of companies paying
a lot of people a lot of money.
I don't keep track of every penny.
You kept track of your
son, though, didn't you?
Which is why you consistently
bailed him out of jail.
Always getting him out of trouble.
He never learned, did he?
In fact, some might say it's your fault
he became a killer, a human trafficker.
A broken little doll.
My son had a lot of friends.
Maybe one of them decided to make
the piece of garbage
who crippled him pay.
Really?
Because I had a little chat with Julian
right before he shot a
police officer in cold blood.
He said that you were an
even worse person than he was.
Mm. That must make you a true monster.
Unless you have actual cause
to charge me with something,
this little chat is over.
Oh, I'm the devil, Tiernan,
I have all the cause I need.
Detective, I think it's time you left
so I can do what I do
best and punish this man.
Get out.
Lucifer. He will be punished.
Lucifer. Lucifer, stop.
Lucifer, do it.
Get out!
Detective...
leave.
Stop.
This isn't over.
Tiernan killed Sam,
but we have no proof.
So?
So Tiernan's gonna
double his legal defense
now that you've hulked
out in his office.
Devil is as devil does.
What about this other guy? Uh, Pony Boy.
Pony Boy already posted bail.
Or Tiernan posted it for him.
You're saying that we don't
get to punish anybody?
Honey... you promised.
Can we... give us a moment. Thanks.
What the hell is up with you?
I finally figured out
who I am, that's all.
Lucifer, this is not who you are.
I think Eve is a bad influence on you.
This has nothing to do with her.
It's who I am, I punish people.
So do I, but like I said, there is
a right way and there is a wrong way.
What makes you the
authority on right and wrong?
I'm a cop and it's the law.
Well, I'm the devil.
I ruled Hell.
Bad people were sent to me so
they could get what they deserved.
It is my job to do the same here
on Earth because when I don't...
When I don't, bad things happen.
That is why I broke Julian's back.
And that is why I won't let
Tiernan get away with it.
You broke Julian's back.
What am I supposed to
do with that, Lucifer?
It's not your place to
do anything about it.
Then why?
Why ask me to leave when we
were in Tiernan's office?
You were going to hurt him
and you wanted me to leave
because you knew it was wrong.
No. Because you've made it plainly clear
that you can't handle who I am.
Mr Tiernan, the cops are back.
- I have nothing more to say.
- I'm here about your son.
Thank you, Margaret.
He didn't just fall down that hill.
Someone deliberately broke his back.
And I know who it was.
Why haven't you arrested this man?
I don't have enough proof
to put him in jail...
but he needs to be
accountable for his actions,
and I know you're a powerful man...
a man who ruins his enemies.
I'm listening.
Look.
You could finally give him a taste
of the punishment he deserves.
What is this man's name?
Lucifer Morningstar.
Since we know the murder was personal,
I looked back over the autopsy report
and I was hoping we could
find spit or urine or something
we could use to track DNA.
It's amazing how many dudes do that.
I really don't get why.
Do you get why?
Anyway, no luck there,
but I did notice that one
of his fingers was broken.
Still post-mortem,
but not from the fall.
It looks like someone broke
his finger to pry a ring off.
Probably whoever stole
all his money and drugs.
Mm. Mm-hmm. Yeah.
Er, you okay?
Do you think there is such
a thing as celestial justice?
Because if celestial justice does exist,
like heaven and hell,
then what we've been doing
here, say arresting criminals...
why even bother?
I know you're religious and I thought
you may have some thoughts on it.
Well, I was religious
- and...
- Oh.
...when I used to
believe in all that stuff,
I really thought that
I was doing my part
to uphold right and wrong on Earth
and everyone would get
their comeuppance eventually,
but we still needed to keep people safe.
But now I believe we
are all anybody's got
and if we don't hold people
accountable, nobody will
because heaven and
hell, they don't exist.
But what if they do exist?
- Say, the devil.
- He's not real.
Chloe, look at the Bible.
It is so full of contradictions.
Fine. Take the devil, for example.
The devil's supposed
to be pure evil, right?
But he started out as an angel.
You can't start good
and the turn all evil.
I mean, that's what
they want us to believe?
You're right.
He's an angel.
No, my point is that it's all bullshit.
I...
This is where I came with
the mother of my child
right after we found out that
we were going to be parents.
We both realized...
just how wonderful it would be.
All I see is weakness.
They're pathetic.
If you raise your son surrounded by
them, he will become like they are.
They may be flawed, yes, but so are we
and flawed doesn't mean weak.
Sounds like something
a weak person would say.
Amenadiel, I just want
the best for your child.
So do I.
I'm taking the baby.
No, Remy, you're not.
I'll never let you
find him or his mother.
Too late.
I picked up the scent this morning.
I've listened to you out
of respect, Amenadiel,
for what you once were.
But I'm convinced more than
ever of what I need to do.
Remy.
I won't let you take my child.
Try and stop me.
Oh, my. Maze!
What is it?
I thought someone was following me.
- Who?
- You. You are following me.
Why are you following me?
I'm protecting you when
you leave the house.
Don't you have anything else to do?
Like hunting bounty.
I cleared my entire schedule.
I am never leaving your side.
I don't need you to always be around.
I need you to back off.
But...
how else am I supposed
to protect our baby?
Our?
Maze, this isn't...
I just need some space. Okay?
Sure. Since we're here, do you
want to grab a coconut water?
I will never let you
anywhere near Linda or my son!
Who's gonna stop me? You?
There's only one way to find out.
Can't have anyone saying
it wasn't a fair fight.
I'm not going to let
you raise this baby here,
where everything special
about him will be leached away.
He will be special
because he's raised here!
With his family.
Funny, I thought I was your family.
You are my family, Remy.
But this is my son!
Earth hasn't made me weak, Remy.
It's made me stronger.
A true warrior admits their defeat.
So you'll respect my wishes?
I will... reluctantly.
But be careful, brother.
I still fear one day...
you'll come to regret your decision.
Hey, Linda.
So I'm just calling because
I'm a little worried...
about Lucifer, and
thought that you might know
what's going on with him. When you
get a chance, call me back. Thanks.
What's wrong with Lucifer?
Is he okay?
Yeah, Lucifer's okay.
I think he's just...
He's just going through
something right now.
Don't you always say that when
somebody's going through something,
that's when they need
their friends the most?
You know what? You're right, monkey.
But...
I'm just not sure that I'm the
friend that Lucifer needs right now.
You do your homework.
Could tie Tiernan to the
anchor of one of his ships.
- Mm-hmm.
- Or a million paper cuts
from his own hundred-dollar bills.
Great.
Oh, no, actually...
I know a man who owns an emu farm.
They're surprisingly
bloodthirsty animals.
Just pick a punishment and
let's go. What's the hold-up?
All in good time, my darling.
You know how satisfying delayed
gratification is in bed, right?
I think you're stalling.
What?
Because of Chloe.
Look...
I like Chloe.
I do, she's great.
But to be honest...
I think she's a bad influence on you.
Oh.
This has nothing to
do with the detective.
It's just better when
you punish them properly.
Lucifer...
I just want you to be the
best version of yourself.
You know?
That devil I met in the garden.
I held myself back for so long
and I can see you doing the same...
because of her.
I just think she might be a
little too involved in your life.
That is preposterous.
Hi, Lucifer.
Who's this?
That is the detective's offspring.
You have a piano up here?
Yes, but no! Please!
Please don't touch that. I
don't know where you've been.
Look at all those books!
Yes, emphasis on the look...
Whoa, a pony.
Be careful with that, that
was a gift from Napoleon.
- Do you have a pet?
- Yeah... No, not really.
You have stairs to get to your bedroom.
Like a princess.
Like a what?
How dare you?
You have a hot tub on your balcony?
No! Please don't jump
on that, it's Italian.
This is the coolest place ever!
Does your mother know you're...
Does your mother know you're here?
Yes?
Well, what are you doing here?
I came here to make sure you're okay.
My mom said you needed a friend.
But it looks like you already have one.
Hi.
I'm Eve.
Hey. Trixie ready?
Trix, Dad's here.
How's the case going?
We know who the killer is but...
we don't have proof.
Who is it?
Er, Julian's dad, Jacob Tiernan.
Jacob Tiernan.
What, he killed somebody?
He thought that Sam was the one
who broke Julian's back, so...
- Simple revenge motive.
- You're sure about that?
I mean, I didn't think
he was capable of...
- of that.
- Trix.
Trix?
Come on.
Dan.
Dan!
Yeah?
- Trixie snuck out and went to Lucifer's.
- What?
Well...
We've got to go find her.
Now.
Where do you live?
Here.
- Where are you from?
- Far away. I came here for Lucifer.
Keep the commentary to yourself, lady.
- Have you ever been married?
- Yes, it didn't work out.
- How come?
- We weren't right for each other.
- What do you do for work?
- I don't.
Pretty much just get to be me.
Well, that's kind of cool.
- Favorite color?
- Red. What's yours?
I'm asking the questions.
Would you excuse me whilst I do
something less mind-numbingly boring
like color-sort my suits?
Are you the kind of friend
Lucifer needs right now?
I hope so.
I care about him very much.
Oh, my... Lucifer!
I didn't think there'd be
anyone else here, but...
can't have any witnesses.
Oh, please...
Let's go! Let's go!
What are you?
Tiernan sent you, didn't he?
Yeah.
Where is she?
Where's Trixie?
She's safe. She's through there.
Mommy! Daddy!
Sorry.
Monkey, you're okay.
You're okay.
I love you, honey.
I hope you know I would...
I would do anything to
protect that little urchin.
I know.
I also know what you're
thinking of doing to Tiernan.
Especially now.
And you, detective.
Don't you want to punish him?
He almost killed your child.
Yes.
I do, yeah.
But I'm gonna do it
by following the rules
because...
I believe in right and wrong and...
and deep down I think that...
you do too.
You're the devil.
But you're also an angel.
I'm not sure that I am an angel anymore.
What do you mean?
After I killed Pierce when
my devil face returned...
I never checked to see if
my wings were still there.
I still haven't.
Afraid that they're gone.
For good reason.
Well, you know...
I think you should look.
Maybe you'll be surprised
at what you find.
The police are done.
Thank you.
Thank you for Trixie.
You're welcome.
We're going to get this guy, right?
I mean...
we've been looking for
the worst of the worst.
Here it is.
You're right.
It's time for Tiernan to
get what he deserves, but...
I need to do this on my own.
It's important to me.
Okay.
You know, I...
I only want us...
you...
to be happy.
We have you dead to
rights on attempted murder.
So if you don't help us take down
who really killed Sam Zofrelli...
Well. It was your golden
gun used on the murder
so you might be looking
pretty damn good for that, too.
Look, I love Julian.
That's why I wanted to
be the one to kill Sam.
But Julian's an idiot.
He gets into trouble all the time...
owed Sam a bunch of money.
Is that why Tiernan thought Sam
was the one to break Julian's spine?
Tiernan wouldn't give Julian
any money to pay back Sam.
So Julian had to give
Sam whatever he could,
his car, his watch,
family heirlooms.
Family heirlooms?
Yeah.
It pissed Tiernan off,
but he still loved the kid.
He's his son after all.
But even after all that,
Julian still couldn't come up
with enough to pay back Sam.
Right, so after Julian's
spine was broken...
Tiernan thought Sam must have
been the one who did it...
asked for the gun and
then got revenge himself?
Too bad somebody else crippled Julian.
What do you mean?
Tiernan found out Lucifer did it.
That's why he sent me to kill him.
We thought that Tiernan
was upset because
of Lucifer's behavior in the office.
Where did he get the idea that
Lucifer was the one to break his back?
No idea.
All right. You said
family heirlooms, right?
Would that also include a family ring?
All right.
Have you heard from Pony Boy?
Not yet.
It's time to get to the jet.
Leave town for a while.
What the hell was that?
Hello again, Tiernan.
I told you this wasn't over.
Finally.
It's time for you to receive
the punishment that you deserve.
What about that ring?
No, the ring that Tiernan had
on had a family crest on it.
Do you guys really think he would wear
it after taking it off a dead body?
It was a family ring,
so I t think Tiernan saw it as
something that was taken from him.
So if we can prove that Sam had the
ring on his finger before he was killed
and that it's now on Tiernan's
hand, we can arrest him.
Before anyone else gets to him.
I think I've found it.
Yes, that's it.
- Taken before the night he was killed.
- Let's go get him.
Flanders.
I believe you're looking for this man.
I happened to be walking
past Tiernan's office,
and I overheard him
talking about leaving town.
As a concerned citizen, I felt it
was my civic duty to bring him in...
so he can properly face
the punishment he deserves.
Why did you do it?
Something made me realize I might
have gone a bit too far recently.
Hopefully it's not too late.
You looked.
You looked, didn't you?
At your wings.
I did.
You did the right thing, Lucifer.
It's never too late for that.
Maze?
What are you doing?
Giving you your space.
I know your heart's in the right place
and it makes me happy knowing
my son's Auntie Maze is in his corner...
but I have to ask.
Are you in love with me?
What?
I mean...
you do have that good things come
in small packages vibe about you.
But, no, we're just friends.
That's what I thought!
You know, Maze, I think you're
looking for something more...
than what this baby or I can be.
I think you're looking
for your own connection.
For a partner.
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Sorry, I didn't mean to startle you.
Oh, no, it's fine.
Working pretty late tonight.
Oh, yeah, I was just...
wrapping up.
Hey, Ella, do you...
do you ever feel just completely...
Lost?
Yeah.
You want to talk about it?
No.
No, honestly, not really.
- You want to talk about it?
- No.
But I just don't know...
what to do, you know.
Well, I don't recommend a downward
spiral into drugs and alcohol.
Tried that, did not help.
Detective Decker.
Thank you for coming.
I only came to tell you to stop
putting in requests to speak to me.
We have nothing to talk about.
I'm sorry... I don't have much time.
They're going to transfer
me back to Rome...
to be tried there.
Oh.
I can't say I'm sad to see you go.
There's something you need to know.
No, there is something you need to know.
You were wrong about Lucifer.
He is a good man.
One might say that he's even an angel.
Lucifer?
I came over as soon as I got your text.
It's late.
Is everything okay?
You have to help me, doctor.
I don't want to be a monster.
What's wrong?
It's my wings.
I hadn't checked them since
my devil face returned.
I was afraid they might have gone.
I was afraid what that might mean.
What that might say about me.
But earlier this evening I looked.
And?
They're still there.
That's good. Isn't it?
I need to warn you
about the prophecy.
Prophecy?
You see, I thought that the
prophecy was about you, Chloe.
But I realize now that
I could have been wrong.
If it's not you, then who else
could be Lucifer's first love?
I saw them.
It was bad.
It was really bad.
You know who it is, don't you?
Is she here?
I thought I could fix it so...
So I didn't hurt him. I stopped myself.
- So I don't understand why. Why?
- Why what?
I just need you to hear the prophecy.
All right.
When the devil walks the earth
and finds his first love...
Why are they still like this?!
...evil shall be released.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
www.tvsubtitles.net