- LUCIFER: Previously on Lucifer...
- Container went missing.
Security cameras were disabled.
What container?
The container.
Your return to the Underworld
has been requested.
Remind Dad
that I quit Hell because
I was sick and tired
of playing a part in His play.
CHLOE: There was a case, a
shooting on Palmetto Street.
Malcom got shot
meeting up with some gang members.
Paolucci thinks he took
the bullet like a hero.
I think he was on the take.
Now,
no one wants to work with me.
You give me what is mine!
Oh, God.
Who stole them?
They were yours.
No, don't!
LUCIFER: Someone's got them,
Mazikeen.
Someone's got my wings.
_
♪ Taste your fingertips ♪
♪ Bite-bite me while I
taste your fingertips ♪
♪ The feeling of your skin ♪
♪ Love give me
love, love, love, love ♪
♪ Now if we're talking body ♪
♪ You got a perfect one ♪
♪ So put it on me ♪
♪ Swear it won't take you long ♪
♪ If you love me right ♪
♪ We love for life ♪
♪ On and on and on ♪
♪ Now if we're talking body ♪
♪ You got a perfect
one, so put it on me ♪
♪ Swear it won't take you long... ♪
♪ Taste your fingertips ♪
♪ Bite-bite me while I
taste your fingertips ♪
♪ We love... while I
♪ The feeling of your
skin, love give me love ♪
♪ We love... bite me
while I taste your fingertips... ♪
What are you waiting for?
Hop in.
♪ Taste your fingertips ♪
♪ We love... while I
taste your fingertips ♪
♪ The feeling of you
skin, love give me love... ♪
(chuckles)
♪ If we're talking body ♪
♪ You got a perfect one ♪
♪ So put it on me ♪
- (chuckles)
- ♪ Swear it won't take you long ♪
♪ If you love me right... ♪
(laughing)
(gasps)
(coughing)
LUCIFER: Hello, Sergei.
Waters a bit rough, are they?
What-what the hell are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm going to brutally torture you
until you give me what I want.
My wings... where are they?
What wings? I don't even
know what you're talking about!
Why do they always
insist on being so difficult?
- (chuckles)
- All right.
(gasps)
As you can see,
I'm not playing,
so let's try again,
shall we?
My wings, please.
Look, man, why would I take your wings?
I don't even know who you are!
I'm Lucifer Morningstar.
And you, you small-peckered fool,
are Sergei Bok, a known smuggler.
You move just about anything
you can get your trashy Euro hands on.
Please, man!
I don't have 'em!
I swear.
Okay? I don't know
what I'd do with a pair...
Maybe if I hit him a few times?
Though I hate to say it,
I'm not sure violence is the trick here.
I'm beginning to wonder
if this human stain is
actually telling the truth.
No! He's scum.
He'll say anything.
Maybe it's not him, it's us.
Us?
He's the fifth man we've
accosted this week.
Perhaps we're... dare I say it...
going about this wrong?
(sighs)
It may be time to seek
the help of a professional.
(sighs)
Oh!
Maze!
(gasps)
(coughing)
Hey.
I don't know that you
want to be here right now.
DETECTIVE: There she is.
Yeah. What, do I hate a
"hate me" sign on my face?
If only it were that simple.
It's about Malcolm.
What about him?
They guy's been in a coma for months.
His wife decided to pull the plug.
Malcolm's dying today,
and you're still
investigating him for corruption.
So, what, they hate me even more
now that I won't put a halo on his head?
Maybe stay away
from the precinct tonight.
Cops are staging a living wake here.
Anything else?
It would make everyone's life easier
if you would close your investigation.
You know, Dan, I
thought we were actually
making progress there for a second,
but once again, look
who's on Team Everyone Else.
I'm trying to protect you.
From what?
Catching a criminal or hurting your rep?
It's not about any of that.
It's about Malcolm's family.
If there's an open
investigation calling for his dismissal,
it can cost them his benefits,
his pension, all of it.
So, what, you want me to just drop it?
Just turn my back on
everything I stand for?
No.
I'm saying if you want to
do something about it,
then do it now.
You have 24 hours.
Or let it go and let his family move on.
Is this really what you
do in your spare time?
How fascinatingly morose.
Do you ever think of taking up knitting?
What are you doing here?
I'm here because I could
really use your expertise.
You're not busy, are you?
Actually, shocker, I am busy.
And it's really not a good day
for... your... Luciferness.
Hmm?
Here's an idea.
- Call next time.
- No, no, no.
Hold on.
Now, I'm not one to get into
the feels, usually, but...
you seem genuinely distressed.
You okay?
Do you want to... I don't know...
chat about it or something?
Sex is always on the table.
(scoffs)
You never quit, do you?
(laughs) No.
I'm simply offering an ear.
Come on.
(sighs)
Remember the Palmetto
case I was telling you about?
The case that's been consuming you,
causing people to despise you,
call you names... I even quarreled
upon occasion because of it?
No, doesn't ring a bell.
(chuckles)
Well, they're pressuring
me to drop the case,
assume the party line,
and say the guy died a hero.
My spidey sense tells me
dropping it's not what you want, is it?
I want the truth.
Well, then seek it out.
You're a police officer.
You don't need anyone's permission.
Hmm.
That's decent-ish advice.
I know. I'm quite good.
Anyway, now we've helped you, my turn.
See, I'm working a
sort of case of my own.
And it seems that I've...
Well, hit a bit of a snag.
A case?
(chuckles) Um...
What kind of case is it?
Well, the nature of the investigation
isn't important.
I'm strictly here for
professional advice.
What do you do when
your case hits a wall?
Mmm.
What do I do when I get stuck?
Yes.
Well, I grab a pair of fresh eyes...
someone who's not gonna be
afraid to be honest with me,
even if it's not what I want to hear.
Hello.
That's a brilliant idea.
Yeah.
It kinda is.
So...
maybe if you help me,
I could help you.
(door creaking)
Could...
And Bob's your uncle.
Right.
What are we doing here, Lucifer?
I like to come here from time to time.
Dip my toes in the sand,
breathe the ocean air,
walk down memory lane.
(chuckles)
You see, five years ago,
when Maze and I abandoned Hell,
I landed right here on this beach.
This is where I flipped dead old Dad
the grandest of birds.
And had Maze sever my wings.
And why are you telling me this?
Honestly, why summon me here at all?
Surely it's not just to reminisce.
(chuckles)
I've asked you here because
those same wings
have been stolen.
And I need your help to get them back.
Sync & corrections by Somnath Yadav
join me @somnath66/
- Your wings are missing?
- (chuckles)
Sorry, is there an echo?
Isn't that what I just said?
What exactly am I
supposed to do with that news?
Use your angelic powers
to soar around the city and find them.
I mean, really,
what good's an angel
if he can't help a brother out?
Am I right?
Lucy,
since your grand departure from Hell,
I've been the one that's
had to patrol the gates,
I've been the one keeping damned souls
from slipping loose... a
job, by the way, that I loathe.
- I didn't ask for that.
- But those wings
out there in the human world?
Lucy, they're too powerful.
A piece of divinity.
Humanity can't handle them.
And if they fall into the wrong hands...
Then people might die? Yeah, I get that.
Just saw a chap toss
himself off a building
after a mere peek at them, so
if you're done telling me things
I already know...
will you help me or not?
You tell me something.
If you truly hated the wings,
why'd you hold onto them all this time?
(chuckles)
- That is none of your business.
- It's a sentimental move, Lucy.
Especially for someone that was trying
to leave their life behind.
Please. Here we go.
Maybe deep down you realize
you never should've cut them off.
And maybe that's why
you left yourself an out.
Yeah.
So are you done?
Pretty words, but no.
They're my property. I want them back.
Simple as that. If I can avoid
an earth-shattering
tragedy as well... bonus.
You wanted free will.
You wanted accountability.
Well...
fix your own damn mess, for once.
(chuckles) I've been thinking.
Your problem, my problem...
why not be each other's
fresh eyes and all that?
Hey, what do you say, quid pro quo?
Oh, so now you need my help.
Sorry, am I not enunciating today?
Yes, I've come seeking
your very generous aid.
First you have to tell me what
it is you're working on.
(chuckles)
I'm not sure you can handle it.
Try me.
Okay.
Uh, remember that container
that was so inelegantly taken from me?
The one I was convinced
- was hiding something?
- Yes, well, it wasn't just
nesting dolls that I was looking for.
There was something
else, something... personal
that was missing when we got there.
I knew it.
Lucifer, what was in there?
My angel wings.
(laughs)
(chuckles) Yeah, go on.
Get it all out.
(laughing) Okay, seriously,
what was in there?
Oh, you are serious?
Oh... okay, sorry.
Did someone make them for you?
Or are you big into cosplay?
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Sorry, I'll admit
I don't always get you.
But if this is really that important...
It is.
Okay, I will do what I can.
I will put out an APB on...
angel wings.
Thank you, and in return,
I shall donate my
services on Palmetto, all right?
Sure, we could use the help.
- (door opens)
- "We"?
- Hey.
- Ready to go?
Yeah, you weren't around to help,
so I recruited someone else.
The more, the merrier.
You're helping her?
I knew she wouldn't give it up.
And I couldn't let her go it alone,
so I'm here for the ride.
Hmm.
Cool.
The three of us working together.
Yes, cool.
What could be better?
♪ Bursting inside ♪
♪ It's getting harder to hide... ♪
So, this is Palmetto Street.
I'm sorry, why is he here again?
Uh, he helps me see things differently.
Yes, I've proved
myself quite useful, Dan.
So, how can we help you?
All right, I want to
reenact the shooting.
I want to figure out what I missed.
How's that gonna prove anything?
- Just humor me, thanks.
- (chuckles)
- Lucifer?
- Yes?
You will represent the seedy
criminal element.
Oh, I believe you mean handsome
- (Dan scoffs)
- And, Dan,
you will stand for Malcolm.
The tough as nails cop,
who wishes I would
leave this stupid case alone.
Ah, cute.
And I will play myself.
A chick cannot figure
out what the hell I saw.
So in the months leading
up to the shooting,
we were following a
French drug trafficker
Nikolas Aoudi.
Ooh, can I have a gun?
I feel like Nikolas would
definitely have a gun.
No...
Actually he was more of a hammer guy.
Liked to break fingers and arms.
- Okay...
- Some legs and teeth.
Right. Can I have a hammer, then?
Somehow Aoudi kept evading the LAPD.
I arrested one of his
guys, thought he was gonna flip.
Then suddenly he changed his tune.
The only cop who spoke
to him was Malcolm.
So...
one night, I tracked him here,
sneaking in through the side door.
And I hid behind this glass.
I could see them.
It was Malcolm and
Aoudi and his bodyguard.
They, they looked like
they were making a deal.
Malcolm was holding cash.
Hold on.
(grunts) Ooh, is that enough?
CHLOE: A bribe, maybe.
I'm not sure.
But I leaned forward to
hear what they were saying.
- (glass rattles)
- And accidentally,
I made a sound.
I-I could feel it.
He saw me, but he didn't react.
He just went back to his conversation.
And that's when the shot went off.
(gunshots)
It didn't take long before bullets
were flying everywhere.
I braced behind the door,
and that's when I ran in.
Aoudi and his man were dead.
Malcolm was on the floor, bleeding out.
There was nothing you could do.
It doesn't make sense.
Excuse me?
Aoudi would have no
desire to kill Malcolm.
Trust me, if there's one
thing I know, it's desire.
I mean, if Malcolm were indeed corrupt,
he'd be Aoudi's golden goose.
It'd be quite dumb to shoot him.
What if someone else was here?
The cops searched the
place up and down, Chloe.
There was no one else.
Look, you may not want to believe it,
but what if...?
I was wrong.
(cell phone ringing)
Espinoza.
Uh, yeah.
Okay, I will let her know.
Did you really put out
an APB for... angel wings?
Maybe.
Well, it looks like they got a hit.
Excellent!
Right, my turn.
I still can't believe
it that the wings are...
Real? Exquisite? Divine?
It's okay to say it.
I was gonna say, "For sale."
So, anything else the
FBI can tell us, Agent Pitts?
The wings... along with
a bunch of other crap
people think is
real... are being pawned off
at a black-market antiquities auction.
An auction?
Held under the veil of a
charity event at Crimson Hall.
Saints' teeth?
Holy napkins?
Oh, a piece of the cross?
They've got my wings in
absurdly fraudulent company.
Yeah, unlike the wings, there's
no way those are real.
Exactly, it's insulting!
Putting my wings on the block
like some chintzy accoutrement.
All right.
Well, you can take
comfort knowing the auction's
already set to be raided tonight.
So the FBI are gonna snatch my wings?
When we get a chance to
pounce on the bad guys, we take it.
The FBI is taking lead.
Figured you might
be after the same guys.
And we have jurisdiction.
Okay, so how do we get the wings back?
After the raid?
As long as you can
prove the wings' provenance,
you'll get it back in 30 days.
- No problem.
- 30 days.
Yes, no problem, no problem at all.
Right?
(quietly) Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
(elevator bell dings)
(laughs)
Come on out, Amenadiel.
So what happened to going it alone,
lying in my own mess and such?
Or did you just want a
front row seat to the action?
I assure you, Lucifer,
I take no pleasure
in following you around.
But this is far too
important to let you screw up.
Ah, so you just came to help?
I came to ensure the wings
get back where they belong.
Which is where exactly?
You mean besides on your back?
Oh, surely, my fine-feathered friend,
you don't expect that to happen.
They belong in the
Heavens where they were created.
If you don't want them,
that's where they'll be.
Fair enough.
Considering we're on a clock now,
I could use a wingman.
What do you mean?
The FBI's raiding the place.
So if we don't get the
wings, humanity finds divinity,
so on and so forth... you know the rest.
Well, we can't let that happen.
Right, so you can join.
Provided, of course, you can keep
that angelic ego of yours in check.
I don't have an ego.
Sure you do, but I'm encouraging
you to get off
that high horse and learn a
thing or two about humanity.
Though it appears that
you've picked up a fashion sense.
So that's, uh... (sighs)
I miss the dress.
(beeping)
Hello.
Private party.
(stammers) Honey, not vinegar.
Yes, excuse me, I understand
this event is very exclusive.
But, uh, surely you've got room for just
two more?
Unless you got business here, scram.
It's funny you
should say that, actually.
Perhaps I do have
something that might interest
those keen on religious relics.
Right this way, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Did you catch all that?
CHLOE: (sighs) I can't
believe I agreed to this.
I thought you were helping me.
I am helping.
We went to Palmetto, right?
We went over everything that happened.
- And found nothing.
- Exactly.
Now I want to show you
who your case is about.
(sighs)
This is who's on the
other end of this case.
Not a monster.
Not a villain.
But a grieving family
trying to say goodbye.
(groans) She saw us.
What is she doing here?
I'm sorry, Mel.
She's not, she's
not looking for a fight.
(scoffs) Are you kidding?
A fight?
She...
You have no right.
What do you want from us?
(sighs)
I'm-I'm so sorry for your loss.
(scoffs)
Just go.
Please, just...
(door closes)
Carmen?
It's like nothing I've ever seen.
Congratulations, Mr. Morningstar.
The Catholics and the
Satanists will be clawing for this coin.
With any luck, we may even
have a bidding war on our hands.
Wouldn't that be fun?
Who would've thought,
eh, the devil's coin,
- worthy of so much love?
- Put a bunch of believers in a room
and... pardon the pun... but
sky's the limit. (chuckles)
(chuckles) That's very good.
If I didn't know any better, I would say
that you don't
respect your buyers' faith.
Oh, quite the contrary.
I respect my customers' faith very much.
But I don't have to
share in their beliefs
to profit from them. (chuckles)
So I take it you're not a believer then?
I'm a man that
believes in one simple divinity,
the almighty dollar.
(laughter)
Humans.
Am I right? (clears throat)
I have to admit,
I love being the bearer of bad news.
Oh? Do tell.
The coin's not for sale.
I simply used it to gain entrée to you.
Then why are you here?
Someone stole my wings.
About six feet, glow
with the light of God.
So if you'd be so kind as to
deliver them, then we can be
on our way without any...
unpleasantries.
Funny.
That's not how this works.
- (guns cocking)
- (chuckles)
Oh, you men don't know
who you're dealing with.
Those guns don't frighten us.
In fact,
I dare you to shoot.
Brother...
Go ahead.
See what happens.
And there's that angelic
ego I was talking about.
I'm sorry, uh... You were saying?
Gentlemen, please... (laughs)
Don't mind my brother.
He's just a bit... simple.
We meant no disrespect, truly.
I thought you told me
you wanted your wings back.
I do. But this is
hardly the way to go about it.
Give me one good reason
not to finish this right now.
LUCIFER: Because you misunderstood me.
I'm more than happy to buy the wings,
like everyone else, with cash.
A whole boatload of money.
If you truly worship the dollar,
then I'm your ticket to divinity.
Happy bidding.
(sighs)
Thank you.
♪ Everybody knows
when, ah, tell me again ♪
♪ Fatten up the pig and,
baby, let's pretend ♪
♪ That I could see the
joke at the beginning or end... ♪
LUCIFER: It's funny,
isn't it, how all it takes
to unite the faiths
of the world is a bit
of illegal consumerism.
Mmm.
What I'd like to know
is since when is the Prince of Darkness
scared of some insufferable human gun?
Well, since I, uh...
I bled.
- What do you mean, bled?
- Yep.
Don't know how it's possible,
but on top of everything else,
seems I'm dealing with a
bit of a mortality sitch.
Hence: ixnay on the unsgay.
What are you grinning about?
I'm just realizing the
gravity of what you're saying.
That I'm allergic to lead projectiles?
That even if you don't choose Hell,
all I have do is wait for some
pitiful thug to end you
and right back to Hell you go.
You hadn't put that one together
yet, had you, Lucy?
You just made my millennium.
(chuckles)
CARMEN: Good
evening, ladies and gentlemen.
I'm Carmen Grant
and I humbly welcome
you to our Evening of Faith.
(applause)
Tonight we shall behold items
that prove the miraculous is real.
There is a power we can't see,
but its light burns
bright in the priceless artifacts
that have traveled from around the world
and, dare I say, Heaven and Hell,
to find their way to you!
(applause)
Without further ado,
I would like to introduce
you to the first item up for bid...
the Lost Chains of St. Paul!
According to tradition,
St. Paul was imprisoned
between 61 and 63 AD.
While some pieces are on
display at the Papal Basilica...
or so they say...
these are the missing links.
Paul's wrists were too
thick to fit in those chains.
I know. That man never could
pass on dessert, could he?
He should have been the Saint of...
Honey cakes?
(laughing)
Those are clearly fake!
- What?
- Shh!
Shh.
Ooh. Tough crowd.
You don't know the half of it.
How did I know you'd come here?
Because I'm admirably consistent?
How did you even get in here?
Oh, I've got news for you, pal.
You're not the only
one with a little mojo.
Mmm. Touché.
And you're welcome, by the way.
I came here to warn you.
In about five minutes, the
FBI's gonna storm this place,
so we have to go now.
But we were just getting started.
"We"?
Oh, that's right. You
haven't met, have you?
Allow me to introduce
Amenadiel.
My brother.
Well, come on,
don't look so shocked.
Um...
I just didn't
expect your brother to be...
so... handsome.
AMENADIEL: We're all
full of surprises, it seems.
I never expected my brother
to change careers as he did.
But I'm definitely beginning to see why.
Lucifer, your brother got
all the charm in the family.
Okay, that's enough of that.
It's unsettling to
see you two get along.
CARMEN: Next up.
(crowd exclaiming, applauding)
The wings of an angel.
(whispers) They're gorgeous.
MAN: Freeze! FBI!
- (crowd gasps)
- MAN: What's going on?
Everyone, stay where you are!
Don't move!
Stay where you are.
BODYGUARD: Mr. Grant.
Nobody move.
Come on.
Stop! Freeze!
Where'd he go?
A little help.
Please.
(exhales)
Thank you.
They're fake.
I telling you, I saw him come in here.
(indistinct radio transmission)
(whispers) There was a secret door.
I see you got your wings.
Thought you'd be happier.
These aren't my wings.
Whose wings are they?
Someone with a warped sense of humor.
- I don't...
- They're a knockoff,
a sham.
I mean, it's good
work, I'll give them that.
Probably would've
fooled just about anyone,
save perhaps the actual
owner of the wings.
The actual owner... being you?
Yeah, they must've been switched out.
It's no coincidence that my
wings are stolen one day,
and then Carmen's selling an
exact replica a week later.
No, this is some serious foul play.
I-I'm sorry to hear that, sincerely.
But there's something at Palmetto
that I need to take care of, so...
Are you coming?
Didn't you hear me?
My wings are still out there.
I need to find them.
If you want to run off to
Palmetto, be my guest,
but no more role-playing for me, thanks.
So I came to save your ass,
but just because these wings
aren't the ones you wanted,
that's it? We're done?
So much for quid pro quo.
Ah.
You sure you don't
want to chase after her?
Maybe I can ask Father for
some rain and make it a moment.
All right.
So what's our next move?
Well, I'm afraid this is where
I leave you, brother.
What I'm about to do
is the Devil's work.
I thought we were
finally done with all this.
(sighs) I was done.
I even started believing I
was crazy like everybody said.
I never said you were crazy.
Yeah. It's okay.
I would've thought I was, too.
But, you know, I got to thinking.
Lucifer pointed out
that it made no sense
for Aoudi to shoot his
inside man, right?
Right.
But no one else was there.
No one could've shot Malcolm and
fled without me seeing them.
- Now you're making my point.
- Because
there was no obvious exit.
But maybe,
just maybe... hear me out...
there was a secret one.
Chloe, you are stabbing
hard at something
- that's just not there.
- There's got to be an explanation
for what I saw, Dan! There has to be.
What do you need me to do?
- I don't...
- (creaking)
What was that?
(creaking)
Looks like it leads up to the street.
Hey.
What is it?
A 999 key.
LAPD-issued.
Malcolm had his on him.
- Wait. Are-are you saying...
- Yes.
Another cop was here.
- I was right.
- Chloe,
- this could mean a lot of things...
- It means
a cop knew
this secret passageway existed, Dan.
And chances are,
whoever it was shot Malcolm, so...
Yeah. But why?
That's what I got to figure out.
No.
That's what we need to figure out.
(doorbell rings)
It's...
you.
That's right, me,
Lucifer bloody Morningstar.
Do you mind if I come in?
You, Carmen,
slightly more difficult
to identify, aren't you?
No phone, no bank account,
home registered under one
of your many aliases.
Seems wings aren't the only
thing you falsify, eh?
- I can explain...
- I'm still moved by your words.
"I'm a man that
believes in one simple divinity,
- the almighty dollar."
- You don't understand...
No, I understand. Perfectly.
A lifelong atheist,
you took one peek at the wings
and something changed in you.
The great white light was revealed
and a believer was born,
one who couldn't
part with real divinity!
(exhales)
Oh, no.
Mounting my wings,
like some decorative stag head.
(sighs)
Shame on you.
It wasn't my fault.
Someone tipped me off.
Excuses, excuses.
"It wasn't me, it was
the biker that did it."
I thought he was bringing
me a sculpture.
Were you disappointed?
I didn't know what they were.
I never would have done
it if I had any idea
what I was actually dealing with.
Please, please.
You can't take them away.
I can't live without them.
Perhaps you don't understand.
(growling) They're mine.
Now, before I deal with you,
I have just one
burning question on my mind.
Who tipped you off?
(chuckles dryly)
I knew you'd come.
Of course I'd come.
It's my duty to return the
wings where they belong.
Is that all?
(chuckles)
After everything that
you've been through...
bleeding, searching,
reaching to the high heavens for help...
now that you finally have your wings,
doesn't part of you
long to assume your form?
Get back to where you belong?
(sighs)
Not exactly.
What are you doing?!
Well, ruining your plan, it seems.
It was you, brother.
You tipped Carmen off, and
you orchestrated the theft.
Because you left me no choice.
(laughs)
Well, clearly you were desperate.
I mean, you were
willing to let a human die
and unleash the wings upon the world
just to remind me who I was.
(laughs) To fool me
into desiring the wings
and the hellish throne they accompany.
Well, do you know what?
It almost bloody worked.
But destroy them?
Why?
Well, you were right.
Severing the wings was a half measure.
I did leave myself an out.
A rip cord back to the life that
dear old Dad chose for me.
But I don't need it now,
because, in case I haven't made
myself abundantly clear,
I'm never going back to Hell.
But, uh...
A for effort.
I'm sure Dad will give you
a big gold star for trying.
(bellowing)
(laughing) That's
right, hit me, brother.
Go on, again.
Become like me.
Become wrath.
Fall as I did!
(laughs)
Come on.
(chuckles)
You never were much of
a closer, were you, eh?
Can't stand to get your hands dirty.
(chuckles)
This is far from over.
I'll do whatever it
takes to get you back to hell.
He was like a brother to me.
And for the last eight years,
he was the best damn partner
that I could've asked for.
(sighs)
You know, I-I remember
one time that he...
What in the hell...?
What part of "not
welcome" does she not understand?
Easy, Anthony. Easy.
You got some nerve, Decker.
(sighs)
I'd like to say a few
things about Malcolm.
He was a hero,
who got shot doing what
all of us do every day,
by putting himself in the line of fire.
I can't take back
the things I've said.
But I can promise
not to let his life...
or death... go in vain.
And for any pain that I've caused...
his family or otherwise...
I'm sorry.
I'm closing the case against him.
To a good cop.
To Malcolm.
ALL: To Malcolm.
I hope you're right about this.
Trust me, if we're gonna
find a dirty cop,
it's best they
don't think we're looking.
(piano plays Johnny
Cash's version of "Hurt")
I cleaned up your mess on the beach.
I'm here to stay, Maze.
(sighs)
And I truly hate to disappoint you,
but... well, this is
where I have to be now.
And I know, even with
all the sex and drugs...
and more sex,
this isn't what you bargained for.
And I know you made a vow, but...
But nothing.
I am with you, Lucifer,
from now until the end.
We're a team, right?
Of course.
Now... (sighs)
you should get some ice.
Yeah.
(sighs) Hmm.
♪ 1:00 a.m. ♪
♪ You're invited... ♪
What happened?
Hmm? Oh.
(laughing): Sorry. This, yes.
Just a little, you
know, squabble with my bro.
Nothing serious.
(sighs)
I don't...
I don't like how we left
it at the auction.
Yes. Yes, I...
I agree.
You definitely could
have handled things better.
(laughs)
And I supposed, you know, I...
- Sorry. What was I saying?
- (laughs)
(sighs)
Look, I know how
much it sucks being alone.
And I can't pretend to understand
why the wings meant so much to you.
(sighs)
But if we're really friends, it...
it should be enough
just knowing that they did.
The wings are old news now.
(chuckles, clears his throat)
Earlier they were all
you could think about.
Now you just don't care?
Well, in my search for the wings,
I realized what they actually were.
A relic worth exactly
what someone was
willing to pay for them.
What can I say?
I've moved on to
bigger and better things.
So, what changed?
I don't know.
Huh.
Or won't say.
(laughs)
Well, how'd your
Palmetto thing go anyway?
Hmm? Did you find the
answer you were looking for?
(sighs)
I found something.
Oh. Well.
To our equally enigmatic futures.
♪ And take a breath ♪
♪ Roll it until there's
nothing left ♪
♪ Look in my eyes... ♪
- (steady beeping)
- ♪ And breathe into me... ♪
(sniffling)
(crying)
(sobbing)
(loud, droning beep)
♪ Breathe into me ♪
(crying)
♪ Breathe into me... ♪
(rhythmic beeping)
What's going on?
What's happening?
(laughing) Oh!
- Seriously?
- Malcolm?
(laughing) Malcolm.
♪ Taste my breath ♪
♪ Do you like it?
Sync & corrections by Somnath Yadav
join me @somnath66/
www.tvsubtitles.net