- Previously on Lucifer...
- CHLOE: I figured out that you're
the one who grabbed the Sinnerman.
- I told you, I did this for us.
- For us.
I had your back on this,
and for whatever reason,
you still felt the
need to go behind mine.
I just read the crime scene
report, and holy burrito bowl!
Lopez, just stop talking!
MAZE: It was weird
seeing you and Amenadiel so chummy.
I don't want you two getting together.
LINDA: I understand.
I can see why Lucifer's
so affected by you.
It's because you're special, Decker.
LUCIFER: What if the Sinnerman
was the one working for someone else?
The world's first murderer, marked by God
and doomed to walk the Earth
alone for a tortured eternity.
It's quite the moniker.
Wouldn't you agree, Kane?
[PIERCE SIGHS]
Thanks for the drink.
Figured it's the least I could do.
After all, I am the reason
you're leaking all over my floor.
[SCOFFS]
Well, gosh, we have so much
to catch up on, don't we, Kane?
Or would you prefer Mr. Kane?
Make it sound official?
Let's just stick with Pierce.
Very well.
Why all the games, Pierce?
- No games.
- Oh, really?
Now you'll claim your arrival
- on my doorstep's simply coincidence?
- No.
I'm the one that had you knocked
out and left in the desert.
I see.
That's all I did.
So you're gonna blame everything
else on your eyeless stooge?
He wasn't a stooge. He
was my right-hand man.
Until you shot him dead.
Excellent way to repay
his loyalty, by the way.
He went rogue.
I have no idea why he did what he did.
That's why I had to take him out.
You know, for an immortal,
you really do bleed a lot, don't you?
Yeah.
I'm still human. I still feel
all the pain that comes with death.
It's just the wounds heal.
- Oh, sounds like a bitch.
- Yeah, well, I don't have to tell you
what sort of sick sense
of humor your father has.
Which is why I'm surprised
that you're working with Him.
Well, there's no sense
in denying it now.
I know
you gave me back my wretched wings.
I know you took my devil face.
So tell me, what did
He offer you in return?
I would never work for your father.
And I had nothing to do with
your wings or your devil face.
I don't believe you.
I don't care.
[GROANS]
Now, after getting stabbed
and killing the closest
thing I had to a friend,
I've had a long day.
Where do you think you're going?
[GROANS]
You can't just walk out on me.
Or what? You'll kill me?
[GROANS]
I'll tell everyone who you really are!
Go ahead.
They don't even believe
you're the Devil.
[SCOFFS]
[YELLS]
Maze, what the hell was that?
Testing a new blade.
Making sure it's kill ready.
It is.
Maze, you can't just throw
knives at Trixie's door.
It's dangerous, and now we have to pay
- to have this fixed.
- Relax.
I got it covered.
Trixie's already working on
another one of her alien drawings.
[KNIFE SCRAPING]
Is that why you've been putting
up all of Trixie's artwork?
- To cover up the damage?
- What?
Kid's got to make cash somehow.
Seriously, Maze?
You live in a house with people.
Is it too much to ask for
just a little consideration?
[GASPS] This is that human thing
where you're mad about something else
but you're taking it out on me, right?
[SIGHS]
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to snap at you.
I'm just, I'm-I'm upset about
what happened with Lucifer.
Ah.
After everything he did... Betraying me,
kidnapping a prisoner
right under my nose...
He hasn't even apologized yet.
[LAUGHS] And?
And what? It's not funny.
I trusted him enough to
break the rules with him.
He didn't care what happened to me.
All right.
Look, you're upset.
I get it.
But you have to understand, Chloe,
you're never gonna change Lucifer.
He is who he is.
Yeah.
["WATCH 'EM FALL" BY
BEASTS WITH NO NAME PLAYING]
♪ Yeah, watch 'em fall... ♪
[CAMERA CLICKING]
MAN: I-It was so dark,
we couldn't see anything.
I thought it was just stupid
kids goofing around again.
MAN 2: These transients
keep coming through
here to get to our beach.
We can't stop them.
We put up signs, but
they just ignored them.
And now they're committing murder.
I mean, what kind of
monster would do this?
That's what we're gonna figure out.
Excuse me, please.
CHLOE: Hey, morning.
What do we got?
Uh, a male vic, 24 years old,
known as Manny "The Moondog" Taylor.
Moondog?
Yeah, he's a pro surfer.
Tops of the circuit three
out of the last five years.
And, man, if you only saw what
this kid could do. [EXHALES]
Wait a minute. Are you surfing again?
Uh, I'm trying to get
in the water before work
as much as possible,
but you know how it is.
Yeah, only so many hours.
Yeah, that, and I'd never
be as good as this kid was.
CHLOE: So, blunt force trauma
to the head is cause of death, Ella?
Nope.
No? Okay. Then what is?
Choking.
Like on a chicken bone?
Or did someone else do it
with their hands, or...?
Surf leash.
From his own board?
Not his own board. No DNA.
Ella.
Are you okay?
Uh-huh.
Hey.
All right.
Well, I guess we're looking
for another surfer, then.
Yeah, I'll start digging into
- Manny's personals.
- Wait. Hey.
Let's keep this quiet, keep
the press from pouncing.
- Yeah.
- LUCIFER: It's okay, Detective!
I assume you got held up with
that needy offspring of yours
and simply forgot to
call, but no matter.
I'm here.
Actually, I chose not to call you.
Okay.
Well, whilst I'm sure there's a
perfectly reasonable explanation
for that, there's
something very important
I need to discuss with you first.
- Oh. Okay.
- Um...
I need your help investigating someone.
What?
Someone very clever and
cunning, but they're lying to me,
and it's imperative I get to the truth.
You came here to get my help?
- Very much so, yes.
- My help?
Are you having a senior moment?
No. No, I'm not having a senior moment.
I'm finally accepting you
for what you really are, which
is an egomaniacal narcissist!
But...
the only thing I can do...
is control how I respond.
By helping me?
By working without you today.
Time to go home and be with
the person you love most.
Yourself.
[LUCIFER LAUGHS]
Detective!
Also Download Other Tvseries For Free At
www.Flashtvseries.Tk
LINDA: So Kane from the Bible
is alive.
Yes.
Is he dangerous?
Oh, probably. I mean,
we are talking about
the world's first murderer.
His own brother, no less.
Mm. And if anyone can
find out what he's up to,
it's the detective.
I just...
I don't understand
why she won't help me.
May I remind you that
you did break her trust
and kidnap a man
while working on a case together.
Well, technically, we
kidnapped each other.
The point is... perhaps it would help
if you saw Chloe's
perspective for a change.
I mean, friendship is a two-way street.
Yes, but right now, mine is clearly
the more important lane.
Okay, let's try a different tack.
Maybe, if you thought about
how your actions affected her,
she might be more
receptive to how you feel.
So what you're saying is
I need to make it all
about her for a change?
Exactly.
And then she can make it all about me.
Oh, that is brilliant, Doctor.
Yes.
Very good.
Should've seen that one coming.
MAN: What the hell was that, Manny?!
Hey, don't blame me 'cause you
cherry bombed your wave, dude.
I'm done with you.
You're dead, you hear me?!
You're totally dead!
Walk away.
This is "Dangerous Doug" Libby,
a nationally-ranked surfer
with a known history with Manny.
This fight took place a
week ago at Bells Beach.
Mm. It speaks to motive,
but there's no connection to the crime.
You can't get a search warrant
for something as flimsy as that.
At least, I wouldn't give it to you.
Oh.
You know, Doug is supposed to compete
at the Huntington Swell Classic later.
If I can get him to voluntarily
turn over his surf leash,
can you match that to the
wound on Manny's throat?
Sure.
Okay. I'll update the lieutenant.
You are not being your excessively
cheery self today. What gives?
Fine, don't tell me.
Pierce yelled at me yesterday.
He said that I talk too much.
So I'm trying to talk less.
If I fell apart every time a man told me
the he didn't like what I was doing,
I'd be in a million pieces right now.
But instead, I pushed through,
rose through the ranks,
built my own firm, and here I am.
In this entry-level D.A. job.
But he's like a hero of mine.
You need to get a thicker skin.
Stand up for yourself,
because the truth is,
nobody's gonna do it for you.
[BRIEFCASE SNAPS CLOSED]
Hey, Lieutenant.
Hey.
You going somewhere?
I put in for a transfer.
Only a few days left here.
Wow. That was fast.
What can I say? I got pull.
Uh, no, no. That's not what I mean.
I-I just mean, why?
This, uh, about what
happened with the Sinnerman?
It's about a lot of things.
I thought coming here
would fix some of them,
but nothing changes, not for me.
Well, maybe you should take
some time to think about it.
You know? Just, um...
Look, I know how hard it is,
and confusing it is to
deal with a shooting,
and, um, if you ever
need anyone to talk to...
It's done, okay?
Let's not make a big
deal out of this, Decker.
AMENADIEL: You know,
I just don't understand it.
I've never had a human illness before.
But sore throat,
itchy eyes, a fever...
Is it a cold? The flu?
It's chlamydia.
Excuse me?
It's a sexually transmitted disease.
Right, but I can't have chlamydia.
I'm an angel.
Not to worry.
A round of antibiotics
and you'll be back to your, uh,
angelic ways.
Now, the important thing
is to focus on next steps.
Do you know how you got it?
I have no idea.
Well, have you been engaging
in any risky sexual behavior?
Well, I did have sex with a prostitute.
But I...
didn't know she was a prostitute.
Uh-huh.
I've also been making
love to an amazing woman
who I have genuine feelings for.
But we have a mutual friend
that doesn't want us together,
and she is not one to
be trifled with, so...
It's, um...
complicated.
Right. Call all your recent partners,
even the ones before the prostitute
just in case it wasn't her.
They all need to be tested.
["GOOD FOR YOU" BY
APACHE RIFLES PLAYING]
♪ When I found ♪
♪ Somebody new ♪
♪ To put my ♪
♪ Time into ♪
♪ Yeah, love's a bitch ♪
♪ Come on, stick it out... ♪
Hello, Detective.
Lovely day for a bit of sunshine
and sand, don't you think?
Lucifer, why are you here?
Well, I realize that I have been remiss
in prioritizing you in our friendship.
So I'd like to make it up to you
by deeming today Detective Day.
What does that even mean?
Well, it means that
for the rest of the day,
everything that I do shall be for you.
Thanks, but I'm working a case.
Ah, now, I know
that you need to get close
to Mr. Dangerous Doug Libby.
But since you don't have a
warrant, you need to do so
without blowing your cover. Am I right?
Maybe.
Well, that's gonna be
quite difficult, isn't it?
Unless, of course...
someone signed you up
for the competition.
This might actually help.
Yes, I know. But wait!
There's more.
Now, since you're going in undercover,
why not do it with a little panache?
[LAUGHS]
Nice try. I'm not putting that on.
But I will keep the access pass.
Right.
- Uh, Detective?
- What?!
Well, you don't want to damage
that perfect skin of yours, now, do you?
So...
how should we get close
to this Dangerous Doug?
You do nothing. I'll handle this.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER P.A.]
CHLOE: Hey, there.
Dangerous Doug?
I just wanted to say hi.
I-I'm such a huge fan.
Well, aloha.
[LAUGHS] I'm, um, I'm
new to the circuit.
I joined down in San Diego.
It's nice to meet you.
Who's the sugar daddy?
What?
Oh. Oh.
[CHUCKLES] Him.
He's-he's just... He's my sponsor.
He's totally overbearing
and absolutely not needed.
Right.
So, anyhow, I just wanted to see
if maybe you'd want
to go surfing sometime.
I found this really
rad beach up in Malibu.
It's, um, called Carbon.
Oh, yeah, I've been there.
I know all the secret beaches.
Well, I just, I really
admire your style,
and, you know, I'd love
to check out your board...
- Is-is this your board?
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, yeah. Oh.
- This right here,
this is my Bonzer. She's great on turns.
Perfect for roundhouses.
She's insane in the barrel.
So, Dougy,
did you, uh, hurt yourself?
No. Why?
Looks like someone bit
it really hard here.
Did you hit someone?
Who'd you say you were again?
MAN [OVER P.A.]: Next up,
Chloe "The Detective" Decker.
Got to be kidding me.
You're a cop?
Sorry, Dougy.
LAPD.
LUCIFER: Sorry!
I'm afraid this is evidence, Dougy.
- Let go!
- Okay.
[LUCIFER SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES] See?
Detective Day.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Now, wasn't that refreshing?
A lovely day at the beach,
and you caught a murderer.
It's like the whole world
revolves around you, Detective.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
We still need to get a
confession out of Doug
or match the blood
on the board to Manny.
Well, whatever you need, Detective.
I am solely here for you.
Look, I know what you're doing.
Being the most selfless
devil you've ever met?
You're only helping me
so that I help you back,
which is actually worse
than not helping me at all.
So thanks but no thanks.
But, Detective, surely
you can appreciate
- a benevolent gesture.
- Save it.
Lucifer, I know this case
doesn't matter to you.
- That's not...
- Ready?
Yeah.
DOUG: He's dead, isn't he?
Yes, Doug. He's dead.
Oh, God. I can't believe it.
I'm totally a killer.
Look-look, you don't understand.
He-he just came out of nowhere.
All right, just calm down.
Take a breath and take
us through everything.
From the beginning, okay?
I was surfing, man,
and I caught this killer wave, and...
he just came out of nowhere.
I slammed into him with my board.
God, there was so much blood.
It was everywhere. God.
Anytime I close my eyes, I can...
can hear that awful sound.
He just wouldn't stop barking.
Um, I'm sorry. Did you say barking?
That poor seal. I killed him.
I killed the dog of the sea.
Hold on a second. You...
you think you're here
'cause you killed a seal?
Yeah.
Why else would I be here?
Well...
Whoa.
Manny's dead, too?
Oh. Pardon me.
Cream? Sugar?
Or do you take it dark
and bitter like your soul?
Uh... [CHUCKLES]
What?
Do you enjoy beating up on
your subordinates, Mr. Pierce?
Is that why you became a lieutenant?
[SCOFFS]
Have we even met?
Oh, Charlotte Richards.
I'm your new prosecutor,
and you are just that kind of bully
that makes me miss my old self.
If I wasn't on the road to
virtue and righteousness,
I would crush you like a cockroach.
I believe you. [CHUCKLES]
But, look, I don't
know what this is about.
I'm sorry if I offended you somehow.
Oh, I'm not the one you
should be apologizing to.
Ella Lopez
may be astonishingly
perky and optimistic,
but she doesn't deserve to have
her spirit crushed by anyone,
especially not a man who,
for some unknown
reason, she looks up to.
Hmm. Shame on you.
Ah, Detective, please. I
really need your... [SIGHS]
Ah, Detective Douche.
Daniel. Sorry. Sorry, old habit.
I think it's because I'm distressed,
and I need your advice.
- [SIGHS]
- Now, you've managed
to offend the detective
more than anyone,
to the point where she
actually divorced you.
Yet, you always seem
to bounce back. How?
- Okay, first off...
- Hmm.
Our divorce was mutual.
Mm-hmm. Right. And?
And it's not brain
surgery, man. Y-You just...
You got to find a way...
to be thoughtful without
getting in her face.
Like, this one time, I
made her breakfast in bed.
French toast, whipped
cream, homemade jam.
Man, she really loved it.
And, you know, maybe
if I had done more
things like that, sh...
Sh...
I wouldn't be standing
alone, talking to myself.
MAZE: This is the RX-5500.
World's most deadly hunting knife.
Made with Friction Forging,
it's so sharp it can
literally cut bone like butter.
And now...
I want you
to get what you deserve.
Oh, God.
[LAUGHS]: It's a gift, stupid.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
For being such a great friend.
Look, I really
appreciate how you handled
the whole me not wanting you
and Amenadiel to bone thing.
This is unnecessary, Maze.
Stop it.
Okay? You deserve it.
Look...
there's something I need to tell you.
[PHONE VIBRATING, RINGTONE
PLAYING THEME FROM PSYCHO]
What?
Uh-huh.
Yeah. Is that it? Whatever.
[SCOFFS]
Stupid Amenadiel.
Sorry. You were saying?
- Is everything okay?
- Eh, no big deal.
He's just whining
about having chlamydia.
[CHUCKLES]: Yeah.
Dodged that bullet, huh?
Yep.
Bullet dodged, all right.
[SIGHS]
Hey. So, forensics came back,
and I can't believe I'm saying this.
Blood on the board?
Definitely seal blood.
[SIGHS] Well, I did some digging myself.
Apparently there is
a Huntington surf gang
known as the Orcas.
Know what their M.O. is?
Using surf leashes to choke people
and scare them off their turf.
- Any confirmed murders?
- No, not yet.
But there's always a first.
Their leader, known as Wildchild,
has been picked up almost a dozen times
for battery, vandalism,
assault with a deadly weapon.
These guys do not mess around.
Okay, but if the Orcas
are from Huntington Beach,
what were they doing up at Carbon?
According to these,
the Orcas tag was
recently put up all around
where Manny's body was found.
So, I don't know.
Maybe they're expanding?
Okay, only problem is a graffiti
tag doesn't prove murder.
Right. We need leverage.
We need to force one of the
Orcas to roll over. But how?
These surfers are like a tribe.
I have an idea.
This isn't a good idea.
Trust me. It's gonna work.
♪ ♪
Okay, maybe it'll work.
CHLOE [OVER RADIO]:
Dan, do you see anything?
I see some Orcas,
but no sign of their big bad leader yet.
Don't let your guard down just yet.
Wildchild just pulled up.
Should be coming at you any minute.
Are you sure Epinoza's up for this?
He's fine. All he has to do
is get the Orcas riled enough
that they try and rough him up.
He yells the safe word, we
move in, it's a piece of cake.
Although, I don't know how I'm supposed
to get "surfs up"
casually in a sentence.
I mean, maybe we should consider
using a different safe word.
PIERCE: Good luck, Espinoza.
Copy.
All right, Dan, you're up.
Wildchild's on the beach.
How do I look?
You look like you're about to get
your ass kicked by a girl.
["HEART IS AN ANIMAL"
BY DEAP VALLY PLAYING]
♪ I ain't got no home ♪
♪ In my bag is everything... ♪
CHLOE: When you pick up your
jaw, remember that the Orcas
don't move a muscle
without Wildchild's nod.
So stay on task, okay?
Trust me.
I know how to tick off a lady.
No, Mazikeen, I don't think
the detective wants a knife.
I'm trying to be thoughtful here.
Hello?
[LAUGHS]
Well, someone's in a mood today.
What, as if the detective doesn't have
enough on her plate already!
Deary me...
Good thing for her she's got
a partner to pick up the slack.
["PYRAMIDS" BY NAKED GIANTS PLAYING]
♪ I know I can be such a jerk ♪
♪ I'll never come to be your baby ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
Right.
Now what do I do?
Okay, I've done everything I can imagine
to be helpful to the detective,
and I'm literally out of ideas.
Can you think of anything?
No. But you know what would help me?
You... scrubbing these test tubes.
I want them spick-and-span.
And, if you don't mind,
how about you do it
with a frickin' smile!
Are you feeling all right, Ms. Lopez?
This isn't me, is it?
Afraid not. No. Uh...
[SIGHS] I'm sorry, okay? I'm just...
I'm trying to practice
standing up for myself against Pierce.
And I've got, like, no
time to figure it out,
- 'cause he's leaving soon...
- Wait.
What do you mean Pierce is leaving?
Yeah. Didn't you hear?
He's about to transfer
out of the department.
[SIGHS] No. No, no, no.
Good job.
["HEAD LIKE A HAUNTED HOUSE" BY
QUEENS OF THE STONE AGE PLAYING]
Here goes nothing.
♪ Oy ♪
♪ Your head's like a haunted house ♪
♪ "Tutti Frutti" written
over the caption ♪
♪ Miss Diagnosis a-with a-the mostest ♪
♪ Cue the evil smile ♪
♪ Desperation can lead to madness ♪
♪ D-D-D-Degradation is a must ♪
♪ The ABCs of leprosy ♪
♪ Need a hand? Take mine. ♪
♪ ♪
PIERCE: I guess we finally
found Espinoza's true calling.
Pissing people off.
I might actually miss
making fun of that guy.
Maybe you don't have to.
I mean, you might find
this surprising, but...
Dan has become way
more fond of you lately.
And I-I think he
appreciates your quirks,
and I'm pretty sure he's gonna miss you.
He is?
Mm-hmm.
And so might... some others.
You know?
But point is, maybe
you don't have to go.
[DOOR OPENS]
Ah! There you are.
What, did you come to make
it "all about me" again?
Nope. It's all about him now.
'Cause he's crazy if he thinks
I'm letting him leave town
without finishing our conversation.
Give us a sec, will you?
[SIGHS]
Keep an eye on Dan, will you?
After all, this is a sting.
You know, a sting?
[SIGHS]
[DOORS CLOSE]
I want answers.
[LAUGHS] You want answers?
- Mm. [CHUCKLES]
- Okay.
[CHUCKLES]
Fine.
Go ahead.
Do your thing.
What?
- Ask me!
- Oh.
Very well... Kane.
What is it that you desire?
I want...
to die.
What?
To die? I...
What does that have to do
with coming here, or me?
It has nothing to do with you.
And everything to do with her.
But... why?
I don't understand.
What does the detective have
to do with wanting to die?
I've walked this Earth
for thousands of years.
I have seen everything,
I have done everything.
I have watched
everything I've ever known
turn to ashes over and over again.
It's almost like you're in...
Hell? Yeah.
And I've been searching
for a way out forever.
Keeping an eye on
every celestial on Earth
and what they're doing.
How and why they seem to come and go.
So imagine my surprise when I find out
there's a detective who
somehow made the Devil bleed.
For the first time, I had hope.
Maybe she could do for
me what she did for you.
Then finally you'd be free.
Yeah.
Then why kidnap me?
Because in order to test my theory,
I needed you out of the way.
So I hired someone to knock
you out when Chloe was close.
Then you sprouted wings
and came back early,
and screwed up the entire plan.
So I had to think on the fly.
Hold on.
The shooter at the ranch?
Yeah.
You let him know you were coming?
Hoping he'd react the way that he did?
You put the detective in danger!
And even then, with Chloe
right beside me, it didn't work.
So that little bit of hope I had?
It's gone.
Oh, boo-hoo.
[SCOFFS]
What about everything
else that happened to me?
Honestly, I don't know.
You're telling the truth.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Stage one's complete.
But I got to tell you, I
think these guys are all talk.
I've pissed every
single one of them off,
and no one's moved yet.
Oh, hey, guys.
What's up?
Dan?
Dan, are you all right?
Wow.
I guess that means surf's up.
I said, surf's up.
Did I just knock something loose,
or are you always this lame?
Well, you didn't think that a...
that a punch was gonna
scare me off, did you?
No.
Should've just walked away, kook.
I guess that's, uh...
that's how it went
down for Moondog, huh?
What'd you say?
I-I said that must have been
what you did to my boy Moondog.
Before he died.
Doesn't make any sense.
I mean, there must have been a reason
my wings appeared at that moment.
There has to have been.
Maybe, but it wasn't because of me.
I lost audio on Dan. What's going on?
Is that blood?
Well, I mean, that could mean
any number of things, couldn't it?
They couldn't have
gotten far. He's injured.
What in the hell are they doing?
It's a paddle-out ceremony.
WILDCHILD: When you told us
Manny was dead, I was stunned.
'Cause Moondog was like one of us...
A free spirit who wanted
to be one with the ocean.
At least now we know he is.
Go ahead.
Say something.
Uh...
Manny was...
a great guy.
And he meant
so much to...
a lot of people,
which is why
I came here today to find his killer.
I thought it was one of you guys.
Why would you think that, man?
'Cause he was strangled by a surf leash.
And the Orcas' tags are all over Carbon,
which is where his body was found.
That's crazy.
Yeah, maybe, but I saw it myself.
We don't go up to Carbon.
Those private beaches
are all blocked off.
Those rich snobs make it
clear we're not welcome there,
so why bother?
The ocean's a big place.
[SIGHS] Now, enough of that.
Let's take this moment.
For Moondog.
ALL: Moondog.
[WHOOPING]
DAN: I'm telling you guys, I believe them.
Why? Just 'cause they
put flowers in the water?
No. Because they
didn't know I was a cop,
and their motive's all but vanished.
I think someone's trying to set them up.
I mean, they don't even go up to Carbon.
It's too much of a hassle.
Sloth... truly one of the
world's most deplorable sins.
If you want something,
you have to be willing
to go the extra mile.
[IMITATES TRUMPET FANFARE]
What do you think?
I'm particularly proud
of the new filing system,
complete with a "Sexy Victims" pile,
"Obvious Killers" pile.
Oh, and "Boring Crimes" pile,
to be ignored, of course.
Cannot even. Cannot even.
Should have gone with the French toast.
As if it wasn't bad
enough you betrayed me,
nearly costing me my job,
almost getting Dan killed...
I mean, did you really
think I was dumb enough
to help you just because
you tried to clean up my desk
and actually made it worse?
I mean, what even is that?
It's me.
Are you that self-absorbed
that you don't realize how
your actions hurt people?
Hurt me?
- Detective.
- And I can only assume
that you asked Pierce for help, too,
which is nuts, by the way.
But I want to make one thing clear:
you can just stop with
this selfless charade,
because I am never going to help you
with this investigation of yours.
Oh, I don't need your help anymore.
Then why are you still here?
Because this case matters to you.
Therefore, it matters to me.
We're... we're partners, Detective.
[SIGHS] Next time, you
want to just start there?
Next time. So we're...?
[SIGHS] Okay.
[SIGHS]
"Hot Suspects"?
An entire folder for graffiti?
This is gonna take me
forever to re-sort, you know.
No, wait, w-what are you doing?
It took me ages to line up
these right angles.
Holy crap. That's it. You did it.
Okay, Detective, I get it.
You don't like the new filing system.
- But this is a bit excessive.
- No.
The Orcas. Remember how they said
that they never go up to
Carbon because it's private?
California has no private
beaches, which means...
Someone must have put
the signs up illegally.
And look here.
One person was cited dozens of times
for posting at Carbon.
To you, Detective.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey! Hey.
What do you think you're doing?
This is private property.
Didn't you see the signs?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I must have missed those.
Did you happen to see them?
No.
You know, someone must
have taken them down.
I don't know who you two think you are,
but I'm calling the police.
What, you mean like those police?
The beach signs you posted
are illegal, Justine,
and you know what that
helps with? A search warrant.
I wonder if the officers will find
anything of interest in there.
Yes, I wonder. Maybe a surf leash
used to strangle a
young surfer, perhaps.
I don't know what you're talking about.
This is insane.
Oh, come on, tell us the truth.
Did he steal from you?
Hmm? Did he owe you cash?
Or perhaps it was some kind of
sexual liaison that went awry.
Really, I must know.
What the hell is wrong with you people?
You come to my house
and accuse me of murder?
This isn't your home, Justine.
This beach doesn't belong to anyone.
But that was the problem, wasn't it?
You are wasting your time here.
Manny came here to surf, you
had enough, and you snapped.
No, that's not true.
Well, you say that, Justine,
but the police officer up there
holding a surfboard says yes.
[CHUCKLES]
Sorry. You were saying?
You don't get it.
I paid for this land.
I even put up signs, but they trampled
this whole beach like it was their own.
They trashed this whole area,
and I just couldn't take it anymore.
I-I had to send a message.
And that's why you framed
the Orcas for Manny's murder.
JUSTINE: If people were scared enough,
then finally they would stay away.
Hold on.
So you're saying your
brazen act of violence,
it wasn't personal at all?
Manny was just a means to an end.
You're under arrest, Justine,
for the murder of Manny Taylor.
After all that, I could really
use a glass of champagne.
Chee...
[SIGHS]
He is who he is.
LINDA: This sneaking around,
I can't do it anymore, Amenadiel.
[SMOOTH JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'm so relieved to hear you say that,
because I feel the same way.
- You do? [SIGHS]
- I do.
You see, I realize
that I don't want to hide
our relationship anymore.
Well, that's not exactly what I mean.
I'm not sure if we should be...
intimate together at all.
Is this because I have chlamydia?
Uh...
No. I mean... I mean, it doesn't help.
I mean, I can't believe
you slept with a prostitute.
First off, I didn't know
she was a prostitute.
Secondly, you had sex with my brother,
the biggest whore on the planet.
How do I know you didn't
give me chlamydia?!
- Okay, how dare you?
- How dare you?
[PHONE VIBRATING]
[LAUGHS]
Uh, it's my doctor.
What do you know?
False positive on the chlamydia.
So, I guess we fought for nothing.
Well, it's not for nothing, Amenadiel.
I mean, yes,
I'm relieved we don't have... chlamydia.
I don't think we should be together.
I don't understand.
I feel like I'm being
a bad friend to Maze.
It doesn't matter how much I like you.
I can't date my friend's ex anymore.
But I do... really like you.
And I really like you.
♪ ♪
Lopez, you got a second?
No. Me first.
I talk a lot, okay? I know that.
But most people seem to like it, okay?
And-and what's more
important is I like it.
Okay, so even if you hate it,
which you shouldn't,
but-but even if you do,
it doesn't give you the right to
yell at me the way that you did.
I-It was rude
and unprofessional, and-and
I think you owe me an apology.
You're right.
I was in a bad place,
and I took it out on you,
and there's no excuse for that.
I'm sorry.
You were in a bad place? Really?
Is there anything I can
do? D-Do you need a hug?
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Sure. Why not?
You're gonna miss me.
[TIRES SCREECHING IN DISTANCE]
[CAR APPROACHING RAPIDLY]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Where do you think you're going?
I didn't figure you for
the sentimental type.
Oh, believe me, I'm not.
I'm here because I finally figured out
why my father returned my wings.
And as it turns out,
it had nothing to do with me at all.
It was about you.
How many times do I have to tell you
I had nothing to do with your wings?
I know, but my father did.
He wanted to stop
you defying Him, and
He used me to do it.
You said yourself
you needed me out of the way.
And since my wings ruined
your kidnapping plan,
it seems I was a means to an end.
So what?
It means my dad screwed us both.
But perhaps there's a way
for us to screw him back.
How?
By killing you, of course.
I thought we went over this already.
You can't die, I know.
But I promise you,
if you stay,
I will find a way to
end your infinite misery,
if it's the last thing I do.
What makes you think you can do that?
Well, you may have
crossed paths with God,
but you've certainly never made a deal
with the Devil before, now, have you?
["BETTER THE DEVIL YOU KNOW"
BY ANIMAL FICTION PLAYING]
What say we change that?
♪ Better the devil you know... ♪
What do I have to lose?
Well, hopefully,
your life.
♪ Walking in ♪
♪ Walking in the shadow. ♪
Also Download Other Tvseries For Free At
www.Flashtvseries.Tk
www.tvsubtitles.net