Previously on Lucifer...
What do you desire?
I want her to choose me.
I never told you what
I want. I want you.
So you thought I wouldn't
find out your mark is fake.
Maybe not tonight, but
I am coming for you.
Neither I nor Lucifer have the power
to get anyone into Heaven.
I'm going to Hell.
Well, I was hoping
that you might be able
to help me out again.
Any chance to get in
His good graces, I'm in.
I know you're not trying
to freak Chloe out,
but you're getting in her head.
- Let's elope.
- I can't marry you.
I'm sorry, Marcus.
- Oh, no ring.
- No ring.
Hey.
You know, I'm really glad
that you told me how you felt.
Oh, I don't know.
All that unresolved sexual tension?
It was kind of fun.
They're gonna burn the house down
if we don't get out there.
I made the batter, Dan.
Oh, yeah?
Well, sweet, because the
waffle king has arrived.
Step aside, my lady.
Good morning, Micah.
Thanks for your help.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Is it the same nightmare?
Except this time, you were in it.
So...
are you going to tell Chloe now?
Tell her what?
Uh, everything.
What we talked about in your penthouse
before she got engaged?
When you said, "I
want her to choose me."
Right. Yes.
No, no. No need.
She broke it off with Pierce, so I win.
Yes, I know that they broke up,
but just because she
didn't choose Pierce
doesn't mean she chose you.
And just because she un-chose Pierce
doesn't not mean she didn't choose me.
Point is,
no need to rock the boat.
I mean, we all know
how the detective gets
when you push her.
Plus, you know, she's on the rebound.
- Those are excuses.
- I think
it's best if everyone involved
just goes back to normal.
Easier said than done, Lucifer.
Yes, you may be right.
Maybe I should do normal
rather than just say it.
Huh? Help speed things along a little.
Ah. Another nugget.
Thank you, Doctor.
Yep.
Back to normal.
Is that really Forest Clay's wife?
Chloe.
Before you say anything,
I just really want to apologize for...
the event that should not be named.
- The what?
- The bachelorette party
from hell. I-I got caught up.
- I acted selfish. Just...
- Ella, it's fine.
- And...
- Is that someone playing piano?
I think so.
At a crime scene?
You look familiar. Have we met?
What?
Then you ask if I like to play cop.
And I say, "No, I like
to play in general,"
Detective, except you were on
the other side of the piano.
That's right, yes. That's
what we said when we first met.
- Yeah.
- What are you doing?
I'm reminding us both of
a life less complicated.
You know, before all that...
Lieutenant-shaped nonsense.
So we can go back to normal.
For example, I'm sure you
remember this little ditty.
Come on, take the top line, Detective.
Don't be shy.
Lucifer. For once,
I agree with you, and I
would love nothing more
than for things to go back to normal.
Oh.
As long as it means we
can get back to work.
Yes, absolutely.
A mystery waits to be solved.
Onwards, Detective.
Oh, anyway,
I just really want to apologize
for ruining your engagement, Chloe.
You know, I-I made it about me
when I should have been
listening to your needs.
You know, what I need is to move on.
Agreed. There's no point
dwelling in the past,
so let's all move on
by moving even further back, shall we?
I mean, they're not breast implants,
- but in a pinch...
- Oh, oh, oh.
No, no, no. No, no, no. Whoa, whoa!
- Whoa... oh!
- Oh!
No, no, no. Please
stop. Please stop that.
- Thank you.
- Why? What, they're not evidence, are they?
'Cause I wouldn't be the
carefree rogue of yore
if they weren't.
Not evidence.
- Just priceless historical artifacts.
- Ooh.
Okay, this baby right here
is from the World Series.
Everyone remembers Gibson's home run,
but Clay...
pitched a shutout in Game
2 that was like, boom!
Take that, bitches.
Hmm.
Wait, do you not know
who Forest "King" Clay is?
- No idea.
- Cy Young Award.
World Series MVP.
Beloved American legend?
Is that lock broken?
Ella, you think this
might be a home invasion?
Yeah, I know. I thought
that, too, but unis said
that it didn't look
like anything was taken.
Was Devon home alone?
No. Forest was here, too,
but medics took him to the
hospital for a head injury.
Apparently the killer
knocked him unconscious.
Boom!
Take that, bitches.
Lucifer, what are you doing?
Oh, right. You're smoking pot
because you smoked
evidence that one time
next to that suspect's car.
Oh, you remember. Yes.
And the time at the teen rehab center.
Is it taking you back? It's
taking me, well, somewhere.
Can you...
Guys.
I've got a casing.
Oh, well, that is perfect, Detective.
My shenanigans leading
to a break in the case?
That is quintessential Deckerstar.
And the eye roll. Now you're getting it.
We did it, Charlotte.
We split up Pierce and Chloe.
Yay.
Sorry.
Truth is, I don't feel any different.
And if Hell is definitely based
on your own guilt,
then I'm still screwed.
Look, we did a good thing.
And it's important to
celebrate the tiny victories
- along the way.
- Right.
But how will I know when it's enough,
Amenadiel?
How will you know?
Well, we're very different, Charlotte.
I'm an angel.
I'll know when my wings are back.
What about until then?
Aren't you just as mortal as I am?
Well, I su... I suppose you're right.
If I were to die right now, I'm...
I'm not even sure that
I would go to Heaven.
If that's the case,
then there's definitely no hope for me.
That's where faith comes in, Charlotte.
Hope in the face of hopelessness.
But faith?
Angel or not, what I'm hearing
is that you're pretty
much as clueless as I am.
Maybe we're not so different, after all.
My God, it's Forest Clay.
Who's that?
Ah, it's just some famous athlete
whose wife was killed.
That's Forest Clay.
Oh, I didn't have you pegged
as a sports fan.
No, from my nightmares.
My Hell loop.
If his wife is dead, he did it.
He's the killer.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I was in the kitchen,
eating leftovers.
I saw a reflection on the fridge,
and I thought it was Devon.
But when I turned
around, all I saw was...
a gun, a-a mask before
I was hit in the head.
I woke up on the kitchen floor,
and I ran to Devon.
But she was, uh...
There was so much blood.
I-I...
I couldn't stop the bleeding.
You don't have to do this right now.
No, I...
I want to.
Did you see anything that
could help identify him?
No.
I don't understand who
would do this to Devon.
It was him. Forest killed her.
- Why do you believe that?
- 13 years ago,
I was an associate at Wheeler Law.
I'd only been there for
a few months when my boss,
Ben Sr., shows at my place
in the middle of the night.
He handed me a duffel bag.
Told me simply
to incinerate it.
He said it was for an important client:
Forest Clay.
Well, what was in the bag?
I don't know.
He told me not to open it
or to ask any questions.
And honestly, I didn't want to.
Here's the thing, though.
There was dried blood on
the outside of that bag.
I'm certain of it.
Yes, but it's quite a leap to thinking
Forest killed someone
then or now, Charlotte.
After years of working
at that firm, I know
how they operate.
Deep down,
I know what I helped
cover up was murder.
I believe her.
Really?
- Mm.
- Why?
Well, which quintessential
response would you like?
The obscure enigmatic one
or the blunt nonsensical one?
How about the truth.
Well, when Charlotte had her
mini-death, she went to Hell.
Forest haunted her Hell loop
and now is haunting her nightmares...
Which, sidebar,
Dan is also a part of,
so things are heating up there.
Oh, well, that sure is nonsense.
Oh, don't worry. The
detective won't believe me.
See? It's classic us.
Look, I know it sounds far-fetched,
and what Lucifer just
said is flat-out insane.
- Eh.
- Anyway,
if Forest killed someone 13 years ago,
the odds that he killed
again are not unrealistic.
Please, just look into it.
I will do what I always do,
which is investigate everyone involved.
But until I get a new lead,
I will start with Forest.
Textbook, Detective.
Very good.
Brother, what are you doing here?
Personally, I'm avoiding
the, uh, boring forensic part
of the case, like I normally do.
But you don't day drink.
Something Charlotte said made me think.
Oh.
Maybe celestial beings and humans...
Luci, maybe they aren't that different.
What, are we talking in bed?
'Cause we all know my
skills are preternatural.
But I suppose you, on the other hand...
I'm talking about the rules
of Heaven and Hell, Luci.
It's all based on humans' subconscious,
what they think they deserve.
What if that applies to us as well?
Right. That's enough for you, drunky.
No, listen.
When I first lost my wings,
I thought Dad was punishing me.
And then I thought that
you were somehow my test,
that in helping God's most
wayward soul, that I would
somehow find redemption.
But, Luci, I've just been guessing.
Dad never told me any of those things.
Since when does Dad
ever tell us anything?
That's exactly my point, brother.
What if He wants us to judge ourselves?
So my wings, your wings,
your Devil face...
Brother, what if
we're the ones who control all of it?
Brother,
that is absolutely absurd.
Dad holds the reins. End of story.
Because if we do have control,
why don't you just pop
your wings out right now?
Hmm? Excuse me.
We might need some room
here. Go on. Be an angel.
Listen, I'm not sure.
I-I still haven't figured that part out.
Well, I'd stop trying if I
were you. It's exhausting.
No, actually, on second thoughts,
ponder needlessly, 'cause it's
what you normally do, isn't it?
No financial scandals,
no personal accusations.
The only nefarious thing Forest
ever did was steal a base.
This guy's as squeaky
clean as they come.
Well, someone is
a dirty little liar.
I was checking out
Forest's medical report,
and something didn't add up.
He said that the killer knocked
him out with a gun, right?
Yeah.
Well, bam!
Or should I say,
no bam?
- Hmm?
- If a cut
is caused by a blunt object,
there's a presence of tissue
bridging within the wound.
Plus, there'd be pretty major bruising
if it was caused by something
that knocked him unconscious.
- But there was neither.
- So what caused the wound?
That right there, my
friend, is an incised cut
caused by something sharp.
Bottom line, Mr. Clay's nose
is as long as a Dodger Dog.
He lying.
Maybe Charlotte is onto something.
Careful, Mr. Clay.
Physical activity may not
be wise after, you know,
being hit on the head.
Detective, hi.
What's this about?
Well, Forensics looked
through your medical report.
You weren't hit with a gun.
Well, maybe I didn't see it right.
It happened so fast. Maybe it was...
Maybe I should just
jump to the old chestnut
where you tell me what you desire.
I just don't want anyone to find out.
What, that you killed your wife?
No, no, no. I... Th-That
I wasn't even there.
Ah.
The night of Devon's murder...
I was with someone else.
Ooh. A mistress.
What was her name?
Mia Hytner.
I bartend at the West
Hills Country Club.
Okay. And is that how you met Forest?
Yes. He came in a lot, even
though he hardly ever drinks.
- Ugh.
- Anyways,
before I knew it, we were...
Hitting a home run?
Digging into the dugout?
Slamming it out of the park?
So you confirm that you
and Forest were having an affair
and that he was at your apartment
the night that Devon Clay was murdered?
- Yes.
- And how did he hurt
- his head?
- Things can get a little...
wild...
in bed with us sometimes.
That night, Forest fell
onto the nightstand,
and he shattered the lamp.
That would explain the sharp
cut that Ella described.
Yes. And furniture-breaking sex
doesn't exactly fit with
Forest's saintly image.
- And explain why he lied about it.
- Mm.
Try not to judge Forest
too harshly.
He wasn't the first
to cheat on his marriage.
He would never tell you this,
but Devon had been having an
affair with her CEO for years.
Was she, now?
- Thank you.
Only one way to sneak up on a demon.
Let her think she's sneaking up on you.
You see, I knew
it was only a matter of time
before you found my new digs.
Killing me
won't send you home.
Keep talking.
The only way you can get to Hell
is if Lucifer flies you down.
And the only way he'll do that
is if we destroy his life on Earth.
That's why framing
Lucifer for your murder
was the perfect plan.
Until you weaseled your way out of it.
Well, I have a new plan. Or, rather,
same plan, different victim.
Who's the new sacrificial lamb?
God's favorite son.
You want me to kill Amenadiel?
Not exactly.
I want you to bring him to me.
Alive but weakened.
Throw me a soft pitch.
I'll kill him.
You want your mark back.
Exactly.
There's no better way to piss off God
than killing his favorite
son. I get what I want.
Then we frame Lucifer,
and you get what you want.
- It's a win-win.
- Why do you need my help
if you're the one who
has to do the killing?
Well, Amenadiel's angelic
powers might be gone,
but he still managed to kill
me nine times when we fought.
Now that I'm mortal...
there's no do-overs.
I mean, come on, you're a demon.
He's an angel. This is what you do.
Unless your time on Earth
changed you more than I thought
and you're not the merciless
badass you used to be.
Nothing's changed.
I'm in.
Devon was the heart
and soul of King Clay.
I can't tell you how hard it's been.
Emphasis on the "hard."
- Excuse me?
- We have reason to believe
that you were having an
affair with Devon Clay.
That's crazy.
Look, I get it.
Being with a married woman,
knowing she could
never leave her husband
because of some stupid company,
his giant face staring down
at you all day. I
mean, it can be torture
working side by side with somebody
that you have feelings for.
Especially if you have to deny
those feelings, squash 'em.
You know, it can be unbearable.
Yeah.
It sounds awful.
But that was not the
situation with me and Devon.
We were just putting in a
lot of hours at the office.
We have to hit the shelves
before the knockoffs do.
Corporate espionage is a real thing.
Actually caught a spy casing
this place just the other day.
Really? Did you press charges?
Unfortunately, no. He ran off
- when security approached him.
- Did it occur to you
that he might be stalking
Devon and not your sneakers?
No, God. Do you think...
I think I'm gonna need to see
all of your security footage.
Yeah. Right this way.
Dr. Canaan.
Pleasure.
My office is right this way.
I really hope you
understand just how grave
the incident was. You're
in experienced hands.
The firm handles cases
like this all the time.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
How many cases of misdiagnosed
chlamydia are there?
You'd be... surprised?
I'm not going anywhere.
- Get out of my way.
- Excuse me one moment.
Not until I talk to Wheeler!
- Ben!
- Charlotte, what-what's going on?
When I left this firm,
you asked me why.
The truth?
It's because I found out
that there are real consequences
to what you're doing here,
what we did here.
You tell yourself
that you're defending the innocent,
upholding some oath,
but you're pretending.
All of you.
Everything you conceal,
every lie you tell,
it adds up.
You're just as guilty
as the criminals that you represent.
Hell is real.
And, trust me, all of you are going.
You need help, Charlotte.
And so do I.
Where the hell is security?
Thank God.
I don't think God's on your side, Ben.
It may be too late for us,
but at least I'm trying to fix things.
Maybe you can try, too.
Oh.
My apologies for the
interruption, Dr. Canaan.
Shall we continue?
Oh, I'm sorry, but I don't
think this is the firm for me.
Old password still good?
Sure is.
Got him.
Four separate times,
as a matter of fact.
But our facial recognition
software's coming up with squat
because of his hat and sunglasses.
Average height,
average build, no
visible scars or tattoos.
I mean, even his shoes are so boring.
Mm, no wonder he's
stealing sneaker secrets.
I'll go back over the footage
tonight. Maybe we missed something.
You Dan Espinoza?
How dare you.
Hey, hey. Actually, uh, that's for me.
Whew.
- Ah. Well, this is like old times, isn't it?
- Thanks.
Let me guess, human head or bomb?
Wager, anyone?
Funny.
No. This is
for...
Charlotte.
Ta-da!
It's a waffle maker.
See,
I-I make waffles.
And hers... uh, iron is really old.
I'm, like, the waffle king?
- Is it weird?
- Very. But I'm glad
to see you're back to your
normal douchey ways, Daniel.
Well, it's between that and...
this.
That's pretty.
- It's a waffle.
- Oh.
- That's better, right?
- It's still weird,
but yes, women tend to prefer jewelry
over household appliances.
Not really sure Lucifer's
the authority on what women want.
This is amazing. See this?
These are nondisclosure agreements.
Forest Clay and...
14 different women.
Spanning two decades...
The last, Mia Hytner,
barely a week ago.
Question: How does this prove
that Forest is the killer, though?
Well, 300, 400 grand a
pop... I mean, no one spends
that kind of money unless
they're trying to cover up
something really bad.
Wait.
Joanne Foles.
June 22, 2005. That's
right around the time
I got rid of the duffel bag. I remember.
"24-year-old found
strangled in a motel."
No way the timing is coincidence.
Forest killed that
woman, and the proof of it
- was in that duffel bag.
- Yeah,
but not even one mention of Forest here.
Yeah, you're right.
I may know that Forest did it,
but I still can't prove
it because of what I did.
Hey, at least
we have the victim's name
now... Maybe that's gonna lead us
to some other proof.
Tiny victories, remember?
- Hey.
- Dan.
I can come back.
No, no. I should get going.
Thank you.
Hi.
Maze.
What are you doing here? What's wrong?
Everything.
It's all ruined.
I have no one, Amenadiel.
And I don't know how that happened.
Maze, I don't know what
you've been going through,
but it is never too late
to fix things.
You can always
be forgiven... that is in your hands.
And, um...
well, for what it's worth,
I will always be here for you.
Hello.
Hi, Lucifer!
Oh, perfect... you're
exactly where you need to be.
Who is up for a classic game night, hmm?
Well, actually, it's
a school night for her,
and I was just about to go over
- the King Clay security footage.
- Remember, all work
and no play makes the
detective... a shoe.
- Lucifer?
- Hmm?
This is... this is a little weird.
Well, if by "weird," you
mean you're transported
to a simpler, happier time, then agreed.
Uh, no, no, no, I'm afraid
that won't do... you landed
on the little question mark
last time, so come on, do over.
Mom's right, this is
weird... We can't play
the exact same game as
we did before, Lucifer.
It's not fun.
Isn't it?
Sorry, but...
I should finish my book report.
Yes, and I should get back to work.
But don't you want to
paint a unicorn on my cheek?
Well, hold on, wait.
- Um...
- There we go.
- Okay. What?
- Come here. Come here.
Lucifer!
What are you doing?
Here we go.
Wait.
Lucifer, stop.
You liked this before, didn't you?
Yes. I did.
It...
it meant a lot to me, actually,
which is why I don't understand
why you're doing this.
Are you making fun of us?
No. No, I'm trying to remind
us of how great we are together,
to help us get back to normal.
Right.
Well, uh, you know, I
thought I wanted that, too,
but...
maybe we can't.
Or at least maybe I can't.
Look...
right now,
normal, it just hurts.
Detective...
I-I think you should go.
Hey, I got something.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Okay, I cross-referenced
the times the suspect went to King Clay
with Devon's schedule.
Two of the four days,
Devon wasn't even there.
But guess who was.
- Forest Clay?
- All four times
the skulker was there...
Right on Forest's heels.
So what if Forest was the
intended target all along?
What if, what if Devon
just got shot by mistake?
Wow.
That is a great theory.
- Yeah.
- Uh, are you okay?
Yeah.
Well, I... I couldn't sleep last night,
so I stayed up all night
working, and, you know,
I drank a lot of caffeine. Like, a lot.
Was it because of Pierce?
No.
No. I... I don't think any of this
is really about Pierce.
I think if I'm honest with myself...
all of this is about Lucifer.
Lucifer's the... the reason
that I said yes to Pierce, and...
he's also the reason that I said no.
Wow, again.
I'm just so sorry that I got wrapped up
in the whole idea of
beautiful "Pecker" babies
that I forgot to check in with you.
Like... like, really check in with you.
- Ella, it's okay.
- Tell me
what I can do for you right now.
Uh, you can help me focus on work.
- You got it.
- Okay.
So, if Forest was the
killer's actual target,
what's the motive?
I think I know.
That's A.J. Agholor.
In 2005, he went to jail
for the murder of Joanne Foles.
But A.J. didn't do it.
Forest did. A.J.'s motive was revenge.
How did you figure all of this out?
This is a list of women that Forest
paid off for the last 20 years.
And look.
Joanne signed a $300,000 NDA on June 22.
She was killed on June 25,
- the same night I got the bag.
- Charlotte,
this could all be a
bunch of coincidences,
especially to a jury
full of Forest Clay fans.
Yes, but a lot of
coincidences is a pattern.
And here's the kicker.
A.J. got out of prison
just three weeks ago.
Motive and opportunity.
It all fits.
All right. We got to find this guy.
Where's Amenadiel?
I decided you were wrong.
Killing Amenadiel won't
get your mark back.
God isn't a drive-thru...
You can't just order what you want.
No.
You chickened out. Gone
soft, like I thought.
Know what? I'll do it myself.
Where do you think you're going?
How's that for soft?
We found this in your car, A.J.
It matches the casing that was
found next to Devon Clay's body.
Now, I don't think you
meant to kill Devon.
I don't. I think that you were
following Forest for weeks,
you broke into his house when
you knew he'd be home alone,
only he wasn't...
Devon surprised you. You panicked,
and you shot her.
You've been in prison for 13 years
for a crime you didn't commit.
It's understandable that
you would want revenge.
Yeah. But not for me.
For Joanie.
We were gonna get
married. She broke it off.
- For Forest?
- Yeah.
Only she didn't tell me
that was his name back then.
She was too scared.
Scared?
He used to hurt her.
She said she was gonna leave him.
Then one night, she calls
me crying, screaming.
Next thing I knew, I'm
going down for murder.
- When did you find out that it was Forest?
- When I got out of jail,
I went to go see Joanie's mom.
She told me that's who Joanie
was dating when she died.
Did she, or you, have any proof?
Mm-mm.
Damn.
More hearsay.
Ah, Charlotte.
Who's that?
He killed Devon Clay.
Long story.
So the detective caught the bad guy.
Without me.
All right, thank you.
Yeah, he's not the real bad guy.
Thank you.
I know you're gonna say
there's still no proof.
No, I wanted to say thank you.
Thank you for helping
me solve this case.
And I might have an idea
of how to solve yours.
Okay. Time out. Time out.
Geez. I won't go after Amenadiel.
You won't?
You're probably right...
it wouldn't work anyway.
I had to kill you before,
but now I just want to.
Okay, you could kill me,
sure, but Linda would die, too.
- You're full of it.
- Maybe I knew
you weren't gonna follow through,
so I needed a fail-safe.
Liar!
Call her. Tell her to
look out her window.
Now I'm...
really gonna kill you.
Hey, get me a beer, will ya?
Hello, Forest.
Charlotte Richards,
what are you doing here?
Oh, I just stopped by to tell you
that I know about everything.
Everyone, actually.
Stephanie, Diane, Jaylyn...
about every woman that you abused
and then paid off.
Most recently, Mia, of course.
She told me how you actually got
that cut on your head.
I told her how you were
getting rough again.
How you started to strangle me.
I tried to get you to
stop, but you wouldn't.
So I pushed you.
And you hit your head against the lamp.
How much do you want?
Money?
Well, a pattern
of domestic abuse going
back decades is pretty bad.
But murder?
Whew, let's see, carry the one...
Yeah, all of it.
Murder? What are you talking about?
Joanne Foles. Ring a bell?
You can stop pretending, Forest.
Cat's out of the bag.
Or rather, the bloody duffel bag.
Yeah, you remember giving
that to Ben Sr., right?
Well, see, hmm,
he gave it to his young
and hungry first-year associate: me.
And here's the thing, I kept it.
I thought it might
come in handy someday.
I'll get my check book.
Turns out I'm a pretty smart lady.
Not that smart.
Knock, knock. It's Lucifer.
Come to save the day.
Everybody stay calm.
Just get back and I mean it.
I mean it!
Forest, let her go.
Hey, I didn't mean to kill Joanie.
It was an accident.
I'm sick. I need your help.
Thanks for your help.
I am not gonna help you this time.
Hands up.
Let her go, Forest.
Was that enough of a
confession, Detective?
Yes. We recorded everything.
It's over, Forest.
Let her go.
Turn around.
Wow.
It's a good place to celebrate.
Yes, it is.
I have been coming here
ever since I realized
that this may be the closest
to Heaven that I'll ever get.
Hmm.
Me, too.
You know, I've been telling myself
that I've been doing God's work.
But, uh, if I'm honest...
I think I've been
doing it all for myself.
To get my Father to
give me my wings back.
But you know something,
Charlotte? I think, uh...
I think I'm the one
who took my wings away.
Great. We're both broken.
Yeah.
Well, I guess angels really
are just as flawed as humans,
or at least I am.
Hey, at least we have each other.
Tiny victories, right?
Tiny?
Uh, may I point out
that you just stopped a serial abuser?
A murderer.
Yeah, but that doesn't change the fact
that he hurt a lot of women.
No.
But because of you...
he will never hurt anyone ever again.
And I'm pretty sure
that you didn't do that
just for yourself, did you?
Maybe not.
Well done, Detective.
And, uh, point taken.
What do you mean?
Well, you put away not
one, but two bad guys today.
All without my help.
So it's become very clear that you...
well, you don't need me.
That's okay, Detective,
because with that realization
came another.
Hmm.
If you don't need me,
then we've been working together
all this time because you want to.
Because you choose to.
You did choose me.
You were right.
I've been trying to go
back to the way things were.
You know, playing our greatest hits,
because I've been avoiding dealing
with things in the present like...
how I feel about you.
I was afraid.
Afraid...
that you'd want me 'cause you've
only seen certain sides of me.
That if you saw all of me...
knew all of me,
you would run away.
Lucifer.
- Detective, it's true.
- No.
The other side of me is... it's bad.
It's monstrous, even.
But you wanted the truth,
and you deserve the truth.
Right now, I can't show it to you,
so I'm just gonna have to tell you.
Detective...
Chloe...
I am the Devil.
No, you're not.
Not to me.
Oh. Oh.
Let me turn this off.
Right.
Oh.
Oh, it's...
I'm so sorry. I have to take this.
Of course, no.
Yeah.
Detective, what's wrong?
Hey, just hold on, Charlotte.
I'm, uh, I'm gonna get help.
I already survived death once.
I think twice is asking too... too much.
No. You're gonna be okay.
Why did you do that?
Why did you jump in
front of me like that?
It wasn't for myself,
that's for damn sure.
Will you s-stay with me?
Yes.
Yes, I promise.
Let's go home.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net