LUCIFER: Previously on Lucifer...
- So how do you afford this place?
- It's my mother's.
LUCIFER: Your mother's Penelope Decker,
queen of '80s cheeseball sci-fi?
You have to introduce me.
So you're the doctor.
You're just as Lucifer described.
I like you.
CHLOE: Are we gonna
talk about what happened?
Our kiss.
It's kind of a big deal.
Chloe, I have a lot on my mind.
DAN: What do you want from me Malcolm?
MALCOLM: You're gonna go into evidence
and borrow something for me.
Are we done?
Not by a long shot.
AMENADIEL: Enjoying the life I gave you?
Do you want to go back?
Who do you want me to kill?
Lucifer Morningstar.
♪ Ah, ah, ah... ♪
You know, there's only one way
to pick the perfect strawberry.
Are you talking to me?
Yes, of course.
Why not?
Uh, most people think it's
just about the outside.
You know, the, uh, shape and the color.
But they're just like us.
Sneaky little devils, hiding
tasty secrets inside.
It's never the ones you expect.
But there's no way of finding out
what deliciousness is underneath
without giving it a little taste.
Mmm.
You like that?
Oh... God!
Really?
You have to bring him up now?
I mean, we were having a moment.
- Uh...
- CHLOE: Lucifer.
The hell are you doing?
Pardon me.
(stammering)
LUCIFER: Right, so what have we got?
Well, this is an interesting one.
Our victim's a 60-year-old male.
Collapsed in broad daylight.
No obvious
injuries, no sign of struggle.
- And the interesting part is?
- (clears throat)
This.
Based on the bloodshot
eyes and the closed throat,
looks like this guy was poisoned.
No, no, no, no, no, this is horrific.
Dead bodies don't usually affect you.
You know who this
is? This is Chef Javier.
Javier Arias, yeah.
Owner of Sol De Javier.
Did you know him?
Well, only by his work. I
mean, this chap was, uh...
an artist in the kitchen.
He made the most exquisite Mexican
cuisine I've ever had.
And now...
(sighs)
It's okay.
I'll never taste his
perfect tamales again.
So this isn't about the
man, this is about your stomach.
This is about a crime against
good taste, Detective.
Well, someone definitely
needs to be punished for this.
According to the grocers,
he came here every morning
after having
breakfast at his restaurant.
M.E. says that the poisoning happened
about 90 minutes before he fell,
which puts him
squarely at the restaurant.
Well, you can't think his
own staff poisoned him.
I mean, the man was a visionary.
With a hell of a
temper, by all accounts.
Everyone at the restaurant's a suspect.
We need to
interview all of his employees
and do a full sweep for toxins.
And find out whether he
wrote down his recipes.
♪ ♪
(indistinct radio chatter)
You smell that?
It's the last of Chef
Javier's brilliance gone forever.
I wonder if police recovered
any leftovers from his last meal.
Well, it was most likely poisoned.
Ah, well, it's well worth the risk.
Hi. So is this everyone that works here?
Yeah, that's everybody.
You think one of us killed Pops?
"Pops"?
What, are you his daughter or something?
Uh, no, that's what we all called him.
We were like a family here.
Well, hold on, so everyone
here saw him as a father figure?
Oh, this is much more interesting now.
Why is that?
Well, my dear
detective, this is patricide.
It's a tale as old as time.
You know, Oedipus, the
Menendez brothers,
Voldemort.
Okay.
Yes.
I know after what
happened to Father Frank,
you're mad at, um...
You can say it.
- God.
- My dad.
Sure.
I just don't want you projecting
onto this case.
There are so many
reasons to commit murder.
Don't let your, um, daddy
issues cloud your judgment.
No, no, no, I simply understand
what it's like
to want to escape the
clutches of a difficult father.
That's all.
Lucifer, not
everything's about your parents.
- (scoffs)
- Hey, Detective.
Yeah.
Your sister's here to see you.
Oh, no, no.
I don't... I don't have a sister.
So it can't...
Oh, no.
Hi, sweetie, guess who's back.
Oh, what a pleasant surprise.
Detective, you never told me
you had such a radiant sister.
It's 'cause I don't.
And who is this handsome devil?
No way.
Mom, this is Lucifer.
Lucifer, Mom.
Sorry, I'm a bit speechless, I...
Penelope Decker?
Well...
As I live and breathe?
The Vampire Queen?
- Yeah.
- (laughs)
Wow, are you a real vampire?
'Cause you certainly
don't look old enough
- to have a daughter this age.
- (laughs)
How old are you, Detective?
Honey, your new
friend is just delicious.
Oh, stop.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Oh, well, you know how exhausting
those convention circuits can be.
I just wanted to get home.
Mom, I mean here, at my job.
(gasps) Oh, well, you
weren't answering your phone...
- Uh, yep.
- so I called someone at the department.
I can be very persuasive.
Oh, you clever little minx.
Besides, it's all over the news.
Poor Javier.
Such a wonderful chef.
A woman of refined taste as well.
(laughing) I mean...
What happened to you?
So you think one of these
people might have done it?
- Yes, uh...
- Mom, can we talk about this later?
Well, sure.
What about a family dinner tonight?
CHLOE: Family dinner?
That's right, it's been ages.
Age...? We never had...
And, Lucifer, you have to come.
- No, that's really not necessary.
- LUCIFER: I'd love to.
PENELOPE: Oh, great!
Well, then I'll see you both
tonight.
I love you, pumpkin.
- (chuckles)
- Ooh!
Mama Decker.
- (sighs) Okay.
- Mmm.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
Crime scene?
Oh. Yes, of course.
Right, well, where do we begin?
Well, we know it was poison,
we know it was here,
so we have to go
through anyone and everyone
that could have had their hands
on Javier's last meal.
That's chefs, servers, bussers.
Even the dishwasher could have done it.
Oh, so many people,
so many reasons to kill Pops.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
WOMAN: I loved him.
Pops was like a father to me.
He was such a nice man.
Except when you made a mistake.
WOMAN 2: That's right.
Then he got upset, and he threw things.
He threw things... a lot.
- Where were you this morning?
- Here.
I'm always here.
Pops worked me to the bone.
A taskmaster, was he?
No matter what you gave
him, it wasn't enough?
It wasn't.
And I gave him a lot.
Ah, to the bone, indeed.
Did you have any altercations with Pops?
- Sure.
- All the time.
Nothing I did was ever
good enough for Pops.
And it never would be, would it?
Which is why he left you
with no choice but to take matters
into your own hands.
He was like a father to me.
He was like a father to me...
And how was he to everyone else?
Tough, but, ultimately, he was fair.
Uh, he cared about his people.
He was...
"Like a father to you."
Yes, we've heard that one before.
He was my father.
This is Javier's son, Junior.
I don't work here anymore.
I-I've been away a while.
I came over as soon as I got the call.
(chuckles)
I still can't believe he's gone, man.
Wayward son, are you?
Yeah, you could say that.
You and your father had
a strained relationship?
It's... it's complicated.
You know, I feel like the only thing
that made him happy was this place.
So let me guess, you tried
to follow in his footsteps?
Yeah, I trained as a chef, yeah.
And Dad was domineering, acted
like a god in the kitchen?
Lucifer.
You have no idea.
Oh, you'd be surprised.
I was never gonna live
up to him, so I just, I...
Rejected everything he stood for.
Yeah.
I gave up cooking, I hit the road...
Which is why I'm
curious about your return.
Was there something that you wanted
to do when you came back?
Uh, I don't know, like...
Oh, come now.
The prodigal son returns
to his overbearing father.
What could you possibly desire?
I wanted...
Yes?
To have one more meal with my dad.
(Chloe clears throat)
(sighs) So you just
got into town last night?
Yeah, I-I met Dad here for breakfast.
Did you notice anything
strange about him or the meal?
Anything?
Dad had them bring out our usual.
(chuckles) We were
actually getting along for once.
Uh, after we finished eating,
Dad left to do his pickup at the market.
We were supposed to meet
up later tonight.
Said he had something he
wanted to tell me, but...
So now that Dad's gone,
I'm guessing the restaurant goes to you?
No, I don't... I don't
deserve this place.
Dad knew that.
(chuckles)
Well, stay in town.
We may have more questions for you.
LUCIFER: Well.
Isn't that a coincidence?
Boy returns home,
and, conveniently, his
pops drops the next day?
(sighs) Lucky bastard.
Maybe.
Or maybe this is about something
more than anger,
which they all had,
but if Junior isn't
inheriting the restaurant, then who is?
LINDA: Well, I'm glad you
decided to come here,
but I'm not sure this is appropriate.
Why?
Well, Lucifer's your
boss and a client of mine.
I can recommend you to someone else.
No, I like you.
Look, you helped Lucifer,
and I need you to help me.
(sighs)
What seems to be the problem?
I'm stuck in a place I don't belong,
and I'm not going anywhere anytime soon.
I need to figure out
how to be more...
normal.
So...
"So" what?
Tell me what to do.
Well, that's not how this works.
Do I need to sleep with you too?
What?
Is that it?
Uh, no.
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
Really, I'm good.
What I can give you...
is my advice.
So... if we want to feel
more connected to our environment,
sometimes it's helpful
if we actively embrace
it and those around you.
That still sounds like sex.
Okay. I meant, uh, engage in
caring and meaningful relationships.
Making friends.
Forget it.
This was a mistake.
Mazikeen.
Wait. If you could...
What just happened?
♪ ♪
Something on your mind, partner?
What's the gun for, Malcolm?
Oh, you mean that gun you stole for me?
That gun?
I was wondering when you'd ask.
You know what?
I'm done playing your stupid games.
You want to tell everyone I shot you,
you go right ahead.
But I'm gonna put an end to
whatever you're planning.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, chill, Dan.
God, you went from zero to 100 so fast.
The way I see it,
I'm doing you a favor.
(chuckles) A favor?
Another man spends so
much time with my wife,
I sure wouldn't like it.
Especially knowing this
guy's so dangerous.
You want to kill Lucifer?
Why?
If I told you,
I promise,
you wouldn't believe me.
But before you go
growing any more balls, remember this...
(sighs)
You thinking about taking
another shot at me,
try to take me down?
Don't miss.
So you're Anne Martin, the sous chef.
You're Javier's number two?
ANNE: I mean, I guess I was.
I mean, I-I can't believe it.
I... I just saw Pops this morning.
He was fine.
And you cooked his last
meal, is that right?
So?
You know how many people
had their hands on that plate?
Well, this is your kitchen, Anne.
When Pops isn't here, you run the show.
And from what I understand,
you're not someone to
be messed with, so...
you really think
someone's gonna go behind your back?
I can't control what they do.
Who knows what kind of psychos we have?
Well, are any of these psychos
set to inherit the
restaurant, like you are?
I spoke to his estate attorney.
It's no secret Javier was
grooming me to take over.
He was my mentor.
Well, of all the reasons to
kill your father figure,
greed is truly the ugliest.
You think I killed Pops to
speed up my inheritance?
I would never do anything to hurt him.
He taught me everything.
He meant the world
to me. (phone buzzing)
LUCIFER: Well...
If you didn't wish your
dear old "Pops" ill,
what did you wish?
To surpass him.
Ah! So the student
becomes the master, eh?
What? No! It's not like that.
CHLOE: Preliminary tox screen came in.
The poison used to
kill Javier was mercury.
Oh.
So you cracked open a few thermometers
over brunch, did you?
Not the trick I'd
use, but clearly effective.
There was something
else in his system, too.
Can I see the inside of your arms?
Why?
Track marks.
Ah, so there was heroin as well?
Generous killer, aren't you?
Wanted to give him a
little high on the way out?
This is crazy. No. If you...
if it's heroin, you should talk to...
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I tend to have a rather
striking effect on women.
Come on.
Just let it all out.
Oh!
Okay.
Someone call an ambulance!
Well, I've never had that effect.
Do you still think she's a suspect?
We can arrest her now, if you'd like.
You know, once she's done
getting her stomach pumped.
What I want to know is...
did she ingest the same
thing as Javier by mistake?
Or was she poisoned, too?
Why did she survive?
Well, perhaps the killer
simply ran out of thermometers.
Who would have a bone to pick
with Javier and his number two?
Oh, I don't know.
Perhaps someone who was kicked
out of the family biz?
You mean Junior.
Well, he seemed like a
very troubled young man to me.
Yeah.
It's almost as if his dad just died.
Oh, and look who decided to
grace us with his douchedom.
Daniel...
Hey. Did you find something?
A Naomi Austen.
She worked as a hostess here
last year till she was fired.
She has two arrests
for heroin possession
over the last year alone.
Poor girl doesn't
learn her lesson, does she?
Naomi Austen.
That name sounds familiar.
Oh, okay.
So one of the cooks said
that she showed up two days ago,
and was yelling at
Javier and Anne, so...
I'll see if her P.O. has an address.
It's already in the file.
Look at you two, like Cagney and Lacey.
You don't care who you piss off, do you?
Not in the slightest, no.
(under breath) Oh, my God.
Oh, wait!
Um, Dan. Um...
So, uh, if you don't have plans tonight,
my mom is having this family dinner...
And you could really use a buffer.
Yeah.
Sure. Send me the details.
All right.
LUCIFER: Detective...
do you mind if we
make a stop on the way?
I mean, this shirt's more
of a loaner, really.
(buzzing)
(Chloe sighs)
Still no answer.
OJ... spoons, foil.
Looks like a junkie...
What do you think you're doing?
Well, I found
something far more interesting.
We don't have a warrant.
We don't have time for
warrants, Detective!
Look. Junior was here.
Junior was staying here?
He and Naomi must be close.
Yeah, well, they probably
chased the dragon together
after Junior killed his dad
and then sat and
looked at the twinkly lights.
Why have they still got
their Christmas tree up?
We don't know what happened.
Well, maybe something in
here will help clear that up.
Right. Uh...
Board shorts.
Don't know what more proof
you need that he's deranged.
We're not supposed to be in here.
Oh, come on.
(sighs)
So let's just search the place fast.
Oh! Well, well.
Lead the way, Detective.
All right.
(couple moaning in
pleasure, bed springs squeaking)
Oh... I... can...
can you hear that?
Yeah. And since when
has that bothered you?
WOMAN: Oh, God!
And dear old Dad strikes again.
- I mean...
- (giggles)
- It's not funny.
- It's kind of funny.
Well, that's easy for you to say.
You're not the one being
taunted, are you?
"Oh, God" this! "Oh, God" that!
He's popping up everywhere and
spoiling my favorite things!
I'd really hate to be in your head.
Well, why would you understand?
Your mother's absolutely delightful.
Oh, of course you think she is.
Oh...
Do I detect some angst?
She's like a child.
- Oh, and I bet it drove you crazy.
- Yeah.
All she wanted was to doll me
up and take me to auditions.
Would make anyone mad with rage.
She made everything about her.
So you could just murder her!
Sure.
But I didn't.
And you're still not
proving your point about Junior.
(sighs)
Fair enough.
So how did you handle it, anyway?
You know, besides taking your
anger out on criminals?
I don't know.
I guess I just always tried to
focus on something else.
This is...
weird.
Well! That painting
just became far more valuable.
- (door opens)
- Oh.
Hello, Naomi.
Who the hell are you?
Heroin inspector.
I'm afraid your spoons
aren't up to standard, so...
Hold on.
We have some questions for you.
NAOMI: You think I killed Javier?
Well, I don't. But she definitely does.
But she thought it
was the sous chef before,
so don't take it personally.
(Chloe clears throat)
The poison that killed
Javier was laced with heroin.
We know you use and we
know that you had a fight
with Javier and Anne
Martin two days ago.
Okay, I admit,
I went to see Pops a few days ago,
'cause Junior called me to tell me
he was coming back home.
I just wanted to make
peace with his dad.
Make peace? Why?
Because he didn't want us together.
- So you're dating Junior.
- We were.
A year ago, before he left.
And I thought,
maybe, when he came back...
But Pops never approved.
Well, I can't see why they're not fans
of your whole Kurt and Courtney vibe.
I tried to tell him that
Junior got clean on his travels,
but it didn't matter.
Javier said he would never support us.
I got upset.
What happened with you at breakfast?
Nothing.
I wasn't even at breakfast.
Junior wanted to see his dad alone.
I went to see my sponsor.
I've been having a
tough time of it lately.
All right.
Until we can confirm that,
we need you to come down to the station.
Why, pray tell,
did Junior want to see his dad alone?
He just said that he
wanted to make it right.
That all he needed to do
was confront his
father and settle things.
- (laughs)
- Hmm.
You don't think that...
He killed him?
Junior told us he wanted to
have one more meal with his dad.
It seems he did...
a rather final one.
Do you know where he is?
I haven't talked to
him since this morning.
CHLOE: APB on Junior's out.
We're trying to ping his cell.
I'm glad we're finally on the same page.
You know, ever since we met this kid,
you've had it in for him. Why?
Guess he's a bird of a feather.
Someone who had a shadow cast
over him his entire life.
Whereas I could never
escape from under mine...
he could.
I wonder how that feels.
(phone rings)
Decker.
No. No, you did the right thing.
I'm on my way.
Did they find Junior?
No. I gotta go.
But we've a killer to catch!
And we will. This is an emergency.
(knocking) Detective!
Come on!
Oh...
(tires squealing)
You've got to stop doing that!
(sighs)
Oh, no.
Nana says we're gonna be in a movie!
(scoffs)
PENELOPE: No, no, no.
So the babysitter called
and said that you let her off early.
Yeah, 'cause we didn't need her anymore.
We were just on our way
to our first audition.
Ooh, isn't that a thrill?
You didn't think to ask me about that?
What do you mean, "our" audition?
I am up for a new role,
and I thought it would be good
to play off of somebody.
Oh, okay.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
So you thought it'd be a good idea
to use Trixie as a prop?
A co-star.
Everyone's gotta start somewhere.
And isn't she the cutest
little lounge singer you've ever seen?
She looks ridiculous.
How can you exploit your
family for your next acting job?
You know, for someone who hated acting,
you sure know how to be dramatic.
You can't do this.
You can't push Trixie into this
the way that you pushed me.
You can't walk in here...
Like I own the place?
The place you're living in
rent free?
You asked me to stay here.
You have no right to take her...
Where is she?
She was just here.
Trixie?
Trix?
Trixie!
She's gone.
I've called her friends,
I've called our neighbors.
No one has heard from her. No.
All right, I'll call
you if I hear anything.
Dan hasn't heard from her.
Take a breath, Chloe.
She's a smart
girl... where would she go?
I don't know.
- She left and...
- (phone chimes)
What?
What is it?
She ordered a ride from my Uber account.
Where'd she go?
♪ ♪
♪ Caught like a
deer in the headlights... ♪
Is Lucifer here?
♪ Don't know where to go ♪
♪ Everybody sees right
through me... ♪
Who are you supposed to be?
I'm Trixie, his friend.
His friends get worse and worse.
Hate to break it to
you, but he's not here.
That's okay.
I'll wait.
♪ Don't you understand ♪
♪ All I ever wanted was
to be part of your plan ♪
♪ People, oh, people, I
thought you all should know ♪
♪ Swallowed all your medicine
♪ Your Zoloft and your blow...
So, what do you want with Lucifer?
He cheers me up.
I hate it when people fight over me.
What people?
My mom and dad used to a lot.
But this time it was Mom
fighting with Nana about how I look.
Which one wants you to
look like an old drag queen?
My grandma, I guess.
They're fighting over what
they want me to be when I grow up.
What do you want to be?
I want to be the first
president of Mars.
Or a zookeeper.
Mm-hmm.
I used to be a zookeeper.
In a way.
Really? That's so cool.
♪ I thought you should know... ♪
Is this a Shirley Temple?
♪ Don't you
understand all I ever wanted... ♪
Sure.
♪ People, oh, people... ♪
CHLOE: Trixie!
Thank God you're okay.
What were you
thinking, running away like that?
I wanted to see Lucifer.
But he wasn't here.
So I made a new friend.
What's your name?
Mazikeen.
But you can call me Maze.
(sighs) Thank you, Maze.
I didn't say you could.
Right.
♪ All I ever wanted was ♪
♪ To be part of your
plan, oh, oh, oh, oh. ♪
LUCIFER: How does it feel?
You know, to finally be free.
I mean, you're about to be arrested.
But, uh, at least you're free of him.
What are you talking about?
Your father!
You killed him. Tell me all about it.
I mean, is the air a little sweeter?
Is the sun a little brighter?
I didn't kill my dad, man.
Oh, come on... why return to dispose
of the murder weapon then?
The heroin.
Sorry, it's all gone.
Police took it away for testing.
Well, (chuckles) most of it.
"Heroin"?
No, I
came for this.
Ah-ah-ah-ah
Careful, Junior, you
don't who you're playing with.
What?
No.
(sighs)
My dad gave me this knife.
It's all I have left from him.
You're not relieved he's gone at all.
Why would I be relieved?
Because he was judgmental and cruel,
and he tried to force you into
being someone you're not.
And he's gone now.
So you can finally be your own man.
Oh, dear.
You didn't kill him, did you?
Of course not.
(sighs)
So, are you gonna arrest me or what?
Hi, Trixie!
I'm so glad you're back.
Listen, Nana needs to
explain something...
- Mom, let's just have dinner, okay?
- (knocks)
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Dan!
What a pleasant surprise.
- And you brought dessert.
- Of course.
So thoughtful as always.
So good to see you, Penny.
Something smells amazing.
- Mmm.
- Yeah, Mom.
Where'd you buy this
nice home-cooked meal?
Oh, there's no take-out tonight.
Lucifer
has provided the meal.
Wait.
Lucifer's here?
He and his friend have
been here a while.
- His friend?
- LUCIFER: Ah!
Detective! Just in time.
Uh, you remember Junior?
Of course.
Just wait until you taste his molé.
It is to die for.
- Lucifer!
- LUCIFER: Oh, get back!
Okay, monkey, surprise.
You get to eat
chocolate cake in bed tonight.
Why?
Does it matter?
Nope.
Junior, if you wouldn't mind.
(clears throat)
- Yes?
- So you brought
a guy who's suspected
of murder by poisoning
to cook for my family?
Well, if you arrest him,
he's just going to lawyer up, isn't he?
So why not have a nice meal
whilst you get all the
answers you need, hmm?
I'm certain he'll open up.
Why is that?
Because I convinced
him you'd hear him out.
After all, he's innocent.
Oh, you think he's innocent now?
Come on, Detective.
If you're not
satisfied with his answers,
you can always arrest him afterwards.
JUNIOR: I stopped eating meat
while backpacking through India,
so I had to get creative with my dishes.
This is my vegetarian take
on Oaxacan molé with a tart,
vegan crème fraîche.
- Sounds so exotic.
- Lovely.
I cannot wait to dig in.
- Mom, don't eat that!
- Why not?
She's worried it might be poisoned.
- You are?
- Oh, that's right.
Let's catch you up,
shall we? Um, I brought
Junior here tonight
because Detective Decker believes
that he killed his father.
- You do?
- What are you doing, man?
But I believe he was after
something far more foolish.
Reconciliation.
JUNIOR: That's right.
I didn't kill my dad.
Do you have proof?
Just my word.
Well, we might need something
more than that.
Oh, come on,
Detective, you said yourself
you may want to kill your mother,
but you don't do it.
Oh, so you want to kill me
now? Just because I put makeup
- on your daughter?
- No, because she thinks
thinks you're a child and forced her
to grow up too quickly.
Am I wrong?
You're way out line, man.
There he goes
leaping to her defense again.
You know, perhaps you two are closer
to getting back together than I thought.
- You are?
- No, we haven't decided.
Things are moving that way.
We just had the one kiss.
So you're kissing now?
Right.
Maybe that explains why
you won't have sex with me.
I'm sorry, what?
No.
You're juggling
both these handsome gentlemen?
I'm not juggling anything.
Well, trust me, honey,
you better do mething,
'cause you're not getting any younger.
However, what do I know?
Because I'm just a child.
If you don't like it, why
don't you stop acting like one?
(laughing)
You guys sound just like me and my dad.
We used to fight all the
time over the dumbest stuff.
That's why I left.
But no matter what I
did, I couldn't get away.
You know, 'cause every time
I cooked a meal or I
looked in the mirror,
there he was staring back at me.
That's a tad bit creepy.
Because he's a part of me, man.
You know, he may have pushed too hard,
and-and-and tried to make
me something that I'm not,
but in the end, it made me the man I am.
And I'm proud of who I've become.
Yeah, I came back home
so I could tell him that I was clean.
And I want to be a chef again.
And this meal?
Was what I was gonna
make for him to prove it.
Well, it looks
very good.
I didn't kill my dad.
All right, so either arrest
me or let me go.
Well, we are gonna need
you to come downtown,
and make a statement.
DAN: Please.
Let me... I'm happy to
have an excuse to leave.
Dan...
Don't go.
I wanted one reason to stick up for you.
Just one. Let's go, pal.
Well...
I have suddenly lost my appetite.
(sighs)
Absolutely.
I hope you're happy.
No, actually, I'm
extremely disappointed.
- Because you ruined dinner?
- No.
Because Junior's answer was
spectacularly unhelpful.
He didn't escape
his father because he turned into him.
I mean, that doesn't apply to me at all!
(sighs)
(clears throat)
So I cleaned up.
The food, I mean.
It wasn't quite the
same as Chef Javier's.
But I have to admit,
the boy can cook, so...
I see you're still working the case.
You were right.
Junior's innocent.
Well, glad you
learned something at dinner.
No, the lab called.
The heroin that we found at Naomi's
doesn't match the
kind that killed Javier.
So if Junior didn't kill his dad,
why use heroin?
To frame him, maybe?
Yeah.
I thought about that, too.
But the only person with
motive got poisoned herself.
Unless she knew exactly
how much to give herself.
Creating all the gruesome symptoms,
but without the finale, yeah...
But the restaurant was hers,
so why would she do it?
I don't know, maybe
Pops had a change of heart.
Decided to bring
Junior back into the fold
after he found out he'd
changed and was coming home?
Yeah, this is Detective Decker.
I'm calling about a
patient, Anne Martin.
Yeah.
An hour ago?
Yeah, thanks.
Guess who checked out against orders.
Well, I wonder where
our lovely sous-chef's
headed in such a hurry.
(chuckles)
LUCIFER: Bravo.
That's a brilliant hiding place.
No wonder the police couldn't
find it earlier.
What are you doing here?
Well, we'd ask you the same question,
but we already know you're
destroying evidence.
Because you killed Javier.
I told you, I would never
do anything to hurt Javier.
You seem genuinely upset.
Like you didn't want Javier to die.
You humans are quite the
paradox, aren't you?
You're always
killing your loved ones and...
Unless the poison wasn't meant for him.
You meant to kill Junior, didn't you?
What?
Oh.
Hence the drugs.
He'd die a grisly death,
and we'd assume he simply got a bad fix.
Oh, that is very clever.
Except you didn't realize
that Junior changed while he was away.
He stopped eating meat.
LUCIFER: Which is why his
father ate his food,
and you killed the man you love.
Ooh, a cruel twist of fate.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
So when we test
that powder in your hand,
you're telling me it's not gonna match
the poison that killed Javier?
That ungrateful kid did
not deserve this place.
He was given everything,
and he threw it all away.
But it didn't matter.
'Cause he was still the favorite.
Because he was
worthy of his father's love.
And he had a chance at redemption
until you ruined it.
Are you okay?
This place can't possibly be up to code.
We've got to get out of here.
Damn it, there's nowhere to go.
Oh, no, no, no, no, this
is not how it goes down,
not by a long shot, Dad.
Lucifer, if you have any ideas...
now's the time.
CHLOE: You can put me down.
LUCIFER: Right.
Happy now?
(Lucifer scoffs)
The Devil gets burned by fire.
Could this be any more ironic?
- (chuckles)
- Ah.
Does my pain amuse you, Detective?
A little bit.
And so does this.
(laughs)
You little rascal.
(indistinct radio transmission)
LUCIFER: Nice and tight.
Ah. Oh, thank you.
Anne was arrested a few blocks away,
so she'll be eating prison
slop for a long time to come.
Ah, her own personal hell indeed.
Thank you. For getting me out.
Well, couldn't exactly
rush out of there alone.
How would that look? (chuckles)
That's it?
No "thanks for saving me first"?
Is that what happened?
It's funny, it's all so fuzzy now.
Must be the third-degree burns.
(chuckles)
Can't believe it's gone.
We found out what your
dad never got to tell you.
He was gonna leave you the
restaurant all along.
If you even want it.
I think I do.
And maybe I could rebuild it.
You know, make it my own.
(knocking at door)
Uh, hang on, just a second.
Maze.
I'm surprised you came back.
I made a friend today.
That's fantastic news.
Who?
An eight-year-old girl who
wandered into the bar.
Well...
That's a start.
Perhaps the next one can
be of legal drinking age.
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing.
Yeah.
So are you... busy tonight?
♪ Now I don't even know ♪
♪ Oh, I don't even know... ♪
What happened to you?
Oh, it's, uh...
it's been kind of a rough night.
So I could use a drink.
Here.
What are you... what are you doing up?
I have an early flight.
And I didn't want to
leave without saying good-bye.
But you just got home.
Look, I know
I haven't always been the easiest mom.
I could be pushy.
Overbearing.
I am sorry
that you felt that you always
had to be the adult.
All I ever wanted
was for you to be happy.
I know.
And sometimes I think you
could just take a leap.
Hmm.
(chuckles)
Good night, pumpkin.
Good night.
♪ Yeah, we can go slow ♪
♪ I'm on my own again... ♪
♪ I'm on my own again ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
What's up, partner?
It's awfully late to
be calling a meet, huh?
You were right.
Lucifer Morningstar is
insane and dangerous.
And he deserves everything he gets.
Well, that works out perfectly.
(chuckles)
But I can't let you kill him.
Come on, man.
I mean, we talked about this.
You know, I go down, you go down.
Then I go down.
It's too bad.
(handcuffs clicking) I mean,
I thought we had
something really special going.
Go to hell. Come on.
(chuckles)
(grunting)
(laughing)
Go to sleep.
There you go.
(phone chimes)
Don't worry.
I'll answer for you.
♪ Love will find a way ♪
♪ I won't let ♪
- ♪ This thunderhearts ever break ♪
- (elevator bell dings)
♪ I won't be the same... ♪
Detective?
This is unexpected.
You said the door's always open,
and I'm walking through it.
Mmm.
Right, well, I was just on my
way out to meet the Brittanys,
but... I suppose
they can occupy each other.
Great.
Then have a seat.
Yes. Has something happened...
I'm guessing by the
looks of it... with Dan perhaps?
Mmm.
You mean Detective Douche?
(laughs) Yes, well, of
course that's what I mean,
but the bigger question
here is: why do you mean that?
We weren't even back together,
and he ended it with me tonight.
With a text.
I mean, what, are we in high school?
Well, we're
certainly drinking like we are.
Why don't you have a seat over here
and tell me all about it, hmm?
I just feel like an idiot.
I can't believe that I would
let myself care for him again.
I mean, why?
So I get hurt?
Um, no, because you're a kind person
who puts the needs of
others before your own.
It's a horrible irony that
my father invented.
But you don't do that.
You just take what you want.
Since the beginning of time.
That's nice.
(both chuckle)
Uh...
What's happening?
It would seem that I'm saying no.
But you've been trying to get
me into bed since day one.
Why are you saying no?
Well, frankly, my dear, I'm
as baffled as you are.
I mean, usually I'd leap at the chance
to fulfill my carnal desire, but...
(sighs) for some reason, I can't.
What am I doing?
Why am I here, drunk,
throwing myself at you?
This is so sad.
Well, it happens to the best, I promise.
But not to me.
I don't do this.
This is something...
my mom would do.
(chuckles) That's who'd do it.
Come here.
We don't all turn into
our parents, Detective.
(laughing) I mean, look at me.
I don't think I've ever been the
son that He wants me to be.
- I, uh...
- (snoring)
Oh, God.
♪ Amen... ♪
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net