Previously on Lucifer...
I'm really glad that
you told me how you felt.
The one man I've cared
about, I still gave him up.
That's how much I care
about our friendship.
Go to hell.
Chloe Decker, will you marry me?
Lucifer's the reason
that I said yes to Pierce.
He's also the reason that I said no.
Okay, you could kill me, sure.
But Linda would die, too.
I was afraid
that if you saw all of
me, you would run away.
Chloe, I am the Devil.
No, you're not.
Not to me.
I have been coming here
ever since I realized that
this may be the closest
to Heaven that I'll ever get.
Let's go home.
I'll never get to see her again.
I know.
I still can't believe it.
Well, at least you'll
get to see her, Detective.
Eventually. In Heaven.
But I... well, sadly,
she's gone somewhere
I simply can't follow.
You know I'm here for you, right?
And I you, Detective.
How's poor Daniel?
Hmm, about as good as you could expect.
He's throwing himself into work,
but so far we've come up empty.
No witnesses.
No security cameras up here.
Hey, Ella.
You have anything?
Uh, no, nothing yet.
I'm trying, I-I really am,
but there's, uh, no DNA,
no fingerprints.
Uh, bullets are nine millimeter.
Pretty common, so that's not helpful.
Who would do something like this?
Okay, everyone, I know this is hard.
But time is of the
essence. Lopez, I want you
to expand the search area.
Decker, build a suspect list.
Espinoza...
go home.
- I need to be here, Lieutenant.
- Dan...
you need to grieve.
I will grieve...
when it's done.
We're gonna find who did this.
I'm on it, Lieutenant.
Uh, Lucifer, hold back a second.
Have you spoken to Amenadiel?
- Why?
- Well, I know
he and Charlotte were close.
He might know something.
I can talk to him myself if
you have an idea where he is.
Well, I think I know
exactly where he is.
You do?
Yes.
I'm-I'm not following.
Well, it appears
that my brother got his wings back.
How is that possible?
Amenadiel had a crazy theory...
Or so I thought...
That everything that's happened to us,
him losing his wings, me gaining mine,
even my lost Devil face...
- And you believe that?
- Well, I didn't.
But I'm fairly certain
he's up in Heaven now
and took dear Charlotte with him,
so perhaps there's something to it.
You think Amenadiel's gone forever?
Well, who knows if he'll ever return,
now he's finally home
in the Silver City.
Okay. No Amenadiel. Great.
Excuse me?
It's one less thing to juggle
as we try to track down this killer.
Right.
Oh, wow.
The Sinnerman himself returns.
You know, the boys will be thrilled.
Everyone's ready to
get back to business.
I'm not back.
I just need something taken care of.
Any luck so far?
Well, I went through the list.
I found the perfect favor to cash in.
Should do just the trick.
Good work.
You okay, boss?
I've never seen you scared.
You're right, you haven't.
Because I've never been
scared of dying before.
Of losing everything.
But that doesn't make me weak,
it makes me more dangerous.
Yeah. Sure.
Okay, boss.
Uh...
What do you want us to do with
the woman back at your place?
I may still need her.
Keep her alive.
For now.
Don't worry.
My best men are on her.
Linda.
Wouldn't worry about
your friend, sweetie.
You got bigger problems.
She doesn't seem that scary.
My nose!
She broke my damn nose!
I hope Maze is okay.
- Why is that?
- Well, I had to book another sitter,
'cause I couldn't get a hold of her.
She's Maze.
I'm sure she's fine.
- Yeah.
- This is astounding.
Who knew Charlotte was
prosecuting so many cases?
I know, and she wasn't afraid
to go after the most
dangerous criminals.
That's our Charlotte.
Yeah.
Guys.
There's something you need to know.
Now, it's gonna sound completely crazy,
but I need you to hear me out, okay?
Of course.
What is it?
Try not to react.
If anyone realizes what we know,
our lives are in danger.
Okay. Okay. What's up, Dan?
I figured out who killed Charlotte.
- What?
- It was Pierce.
What are you talking about, Daniel?
Why would he do that?
Charlotte was investigating him.
She was? Why?
Well, that's the craziest part.
Pierce...
Pierce is The Sinnerman.
Dan, listen, uh...
I can't imagine what you're
going through right now.
- But this does sound a little...
- Insane?
Completely nuts? No, I get it.
I know what it sounds like,
Chloe, but do you believe me...
Daniel's right.
- Excuse me?
- Pierce is indeed The Sinnerman.
I mean, I don't know
if he killed Charlotte,
but he certainly seemed mightily
relieved Amenadiel was gone.
Wait, you knew?
Yes. He told me months ago.
- What?
- You knew?
You freakin' knew?
- Daniel, Daniel!
- You...
Daniel, like you said.
Please, be careful,
people are watching.
Okay?
Good? Yes?
This cannot be true. Can it?
I mean... if you knew this,
why wouldn't you say something?
I mean, I almost married him.
I tried to tell you,
but you wouldn't listen.
No, you said he's immortal,
and that is something
completely different.
Is it? If I'd told you he
was The Sinnerman as well,
- would you have believed me?
- I don't know, maybe!
Maybe, because that's
something that actually exists,
and not some metaphor
that you've made up.
I haven't made up anything, Detective,
I always tell you the
truth, no matter what.
Okay, ignoring
all the craziness, do
you believe me, Chloe?
I-I...
I don't see anything
in here that proves it.
Pierce wants to talk to everyone.
Charlotte Richards was one of us.
She fought tooth and nail
to make sure that our arrests stuck.
To make sure that the bad
guys stayed off the streets.
And now...
Pierce doesn't get emotional.
Now she's gone.
I don't like this. He's lying.
But we will find whoever did this.
We need to get justice for Charlotte.
If it's the last thing that we do.
He did it, didn't he?
He killed Charlotte.
It appears so, Detective.
And now he's overseeing the
whole damn investigation.
How do we take him down?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
How do we approach this?
You buy me five minutes in
interrogation with that dick,
- and I swear to you, I will break him.
- Dan.
You're gonna need to
get a hold of your anger.
I know it's not easy.
It's the only way that
we can bring him down.
Can you do that?
Yeah.
I can.
- I have no choice.
- Yeah, she's right.
Pierce is more formidable
than either of you realize.
We are talking about the
world's first killer, after all.
And you. No more of your metaphors.
- They're not metaphors.
- We need to focus on Pierce.
But when this is all done,
you and I are gonna talk
about everything that
you've been keeping from me.
Very well.
Great.
What's our first move?
Well, Pierce still needs
to cover his tracks,
so if I were him, I'd be
looking for a fall guy.
This was just found at the crime scene.
I totally missed the little bugger
in the first couple of canvasses.
I mean, thank God Pierce held off
on releasing the scene
until we did a third sweep.
We may have never found it.
Oh, I guarantee you wouldn't have.
Did you find any DNA on it?
Yeah and we got a match.
A guy named Steve Chamberlain.
That's one of the men that
Charlotte was gonna prosecute.
A hedge fund manager
that was using a charity
to embezzle money.
Sounds exactly like the kind of dirtbag
- who would do something this terrible.
- Hey, Ella,
there's something that I need you to...
There's something that you should do.
Okay, so if they found this,
at the scene, there's
probably more evidence,
so have the team do another sweep.
- You got it.
- We have a lead?
Yeah.
Uh, DNA at the scene points
to one of the criminals
that Charlotte was gonna prosecute.
That's great.
Well, keep me posted.
Let me know if there's
anything you need.
Yeah, will do.
Espinoza.
Uh, yeah, Lieutenant?
Thought I told you to go home.
Yes, sir, you did.
Well, if I were you, I
would still be here, too.
If there's anything you need...
I need... to catch the
bastard that killed Charlotte.
Good luck.
The improv's paying off.
Admirable work, Daniel.
For whatever good it does.
If we don't arrest Pierce's fall guy,
he's gonna know we're onto him.
But if we do, then we
lose the time that we need
to prove that Pierce is
really the one who did it.
Maybe not.
Think Pierce has gone back
to his Sinnerman network?
It makes sense. Pierce
needs to move quickly,
and there are thousands
of people in Los Angeles
that owe him a favor.
Well, maybe one of them
is in Chamberlain's orbit.
If we can figure out who
owes Pierce the favor,
maybe we can get him to flip on him.
It's a long shot, but...
Yeah, but it's the best
one we got so far, so...
Yeah.
I told you not to park under that tree.
You need to clean this crap.
LAPD.
Want to ask you some questions
about Charlotte Richards.
Yeah, sure.
Can we take this inside?
Nosy neighbors and all that.
Not sure why you came all this way.
I'm not answering any
questions without my lawyer.
We're not here about
the embezzling case.
Charlotte Richards was murdered.
What?
Yeah. And your DNA was found
at the scene of the crime.
I didn't murder her.
- We know.
- You got to listen to me.
I... You do?
You see, we think you're being framed.
And we'd like your help in trying
to find out who framed you.
Is this some weird reverse psychology?
What's your angle?
Never mind. I'm calling my lawyer.
If you do that, we can't help you.
Sorry, but this good cop,
bad cop, sad cop thing
isn't working on me.
Besides, a cigarette butt
is pretty flimsy evidence.
He's right. A good frame
job would need more.
Like the murder weapon.
- Where would you hide it?
- Nowhere,
because I didn't murder her.
If you did, where
would you hide the gun?
- In my desk.
- What, that one?
I don't... yes. That one.
You know, it's not gonna be
there, because I'm not a...
murderer. W-Whoa. That is not mine.
For the last time, we know.
Someone planted this gun here.
We need to know who had access
to this area in the last 12 hours.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Had a few friends over today, have you?
Oh, just a hundred or so.
I think we made a real
breakthrough today, Simon.
Thanks.
A-And I know you're right, Linda.
Not everyone's out to get me.
Yeah. Okay. Good.
- Are you here to kill her?
- No, no!
That's exactly what someone
trying to kill her would say.
No. No, I...
Maze, he's a patient.
See you next week?
What the hell happened?!
Are you okay?
Yes! I'm fine.
Good.
All right, we need to figure out
who would get a favor
from The Sinnerman.
Well, you did bring along
your own master of favors.
I could suss out who
needed one the most.
Dude, we don't have time
to go person to person.
Pierce is gonna start
wondering where we are soon.
Yeah, you're right.
We need to narrow down the list fast.
You know everybody here.
I mean, who would have a dark secret
that they would want erased?
Uh, everyone.
What? It's a charity event.
Ah, charity is the perfect way
for criminals to launder their images.
Donate a thousand dollars to distract
from the million you just filched.
He's not wrong.
That guy. Sweatshop abuse.
Him? Insider trading.
Her? Stole the idea for a
company from her own sister.
So it could be anyone.
Everyone here is guilty.
Which means The Sinnerman's
not very good at what he does.
Should've left it to the
professionals, namely moi.
- Y-You're right.
- Well, thank you.
No, I mean he is good at what he does.
If somebody made a
deal with The Sinnerman,
he's gonna make their skeletons vanish.
And no one would know
about their crimes at all.
Which means we're not
looking for a criminal.
We're looking for somebody
as clean as can be.
Dan.
Who hired you to frame your boss?
What? What are you talking about?
- Dan.
- You are innocent.
And that's a bad thing?
You're the only one who has
access to Chamberlain's office
and the only one with no dirty laundry.
Now, the woman I loved is dead,
so if you don't start talking...
Daniel, Daniel! Daniel, Daniel.
I understand your anger,
but perhaps a lighter touch
might help reveal the truth faster.
I mean, after all, this
young man did ask for a favor
from The Sinnerman,
so you must've wanted something
very badly, didn't you?
Yeah. Tell me.
What is it you desired?
I wished I never sneezed.
You interrupted me for
a stupid parlor trick?
Dan, it's not a trick.
I-I don't know what
it is, but it works.
Calm down.
What happened when you sneezed?
I...
I took my eyes off
the road for a second.
And... this...
this motorcycle pulled in front of me
at just the wrong time.
So you killed a biker
and then found somebody who
could make it all disappear.
I heard about a guy who gave out favors,
so I called him.
And the next morning I...
it was like it never happened.
But it did happen.
No matter how much time has passed,
every time I look in the
mirror, all I see is...
A monster.
And then this morning
he called in his favor.
How'd he contact you?
Would you recognize him?
I never saw anybody.
A burner phone showed up
at my doorstep this morning
and everything after was
handled through dead drops.
All right. We're gonna need that phone.
Okay.
We're running out of time.
Okay, so then we buy more.
We bring Chamberlain in.
We let him lawyer up so he doesn't talk.
And then what? Pierce
works with the pros.
There's a good chance there's
no evidence on the burner phone.
Well, perhaps it's time
we asked for some help.
Hey. I got your text. What's up?
I need something from you.
Of course you do.
I do, too, actually.
That's not what I meant. I...
Hey. Hey.
You have been through so much.
Okay?
You need to go home.
You need to take care of you.
We got the guy.
That's just it. I need you...
What's up?
I need you to do me a favor.
Something you can't tell anyone about.
Lopez, you want to come in or what?
Uh...
Hey, boss.
What is it?
Dan gave something to me.
Asked me to examine it,
but told me not to tell anyone.
What is it?
A phone?
That's it?
Yeah. I mean, he... honestly, he sounded
kind of crazy.
He was going on and on
about some frame job or something.
Huh. Well, what all did he say?
Uh, not much more than that.
He-he claimed that "people
might be listening."
I know, it sounds insane.
I-I know he's not in a great place.
I told him he should just
go home and get some sleep.
I'm-I'm really worried about him.
It's okay. I'm glad you
came to me with this, Ella.
But I don't want Dan
to get into any trouble.
He's not in any trouble. I promise.
Okay.
Yeah, it's me.
One of my officers is on to you.
I don't need excuses.
I just need you to take care of it.
Hello, Pierce.
It's time for a reckoning.
What are you talking about?
I know you killed Charlotte.
So, why'd you do it, Piercy?
Why kill Charlotte?
I don't know what
this is about, Lucifer.
We caught the murderer. I
don't know why you think...
The detective isn't here, which means
I'm invulnerable and you're not, so...
sit...
down.
Or I'll make you.
Lucifer...
For every lie, I will break a body part.
I didn't mean to kill Charlotte.
It was an accident.
I was trying to kill Amenadiel.
And that's supposed to
spare your life, is it?
You wanted by brother dead instead?
It's the truth.
But why?
God took my mark away.
I thought killing his favorite
son might bring it back.
Did you, now?
You know, when I first landed in Hell...
I'd just led a rebellion
against dear old Dad.
I failed.
Everyone hated me for it.
Myself included, I've come to realize.
I felt like a monster.
And then, when I
looked at my reflection,
there was my Devil face.
Your Father's punishment.
So I thought, but...
after speaking with a sneezy,
murderous driver today,
I realized I felt like a monster
before I became one.
I think I gave myself that face.
You actually believe Amenadiel's theory?
And what about your wings?
Well, I'd just saved Mum, hadn't I?
And I'd decided to tell
the detective the truth.
I felt better about
myself than I had in...
well... ever.
Maybe so much so that, deep down,
I felt like I wasn't a monster anymore.
What does any of this
have to do with me?
My curse was lifted when
Chloe fell in love with me.
Yeah. You see...
I don't think that's what happened.
You were willing to sacrifice
the one thing you wanted
to protect someone else.
For the first time in
your miserable life, Cain,
you were selfless.
And maybe, deep down,
you felt that you finally deserved
the mortality that you
so desperately desired.
You fell in love with
the detective, Pierce,
not the other way around.
She never loved you.
Oh, go ahead, hit me.
Yeah, be good to see
you break your hand.
You think you're not vulnerable
because Chloe's not here.
But guess what, you're
still very vulnerable.
Oh, please, do go on. I
like this desperate you.
You do have a weakness.
Mm.
You want to be good.
What?
- Help! Help, I'm being attacked!
- What on earth are you doing?
- Let go of me.
- Lucifer's trying to kill me!
No, no. What? No. No, no, no, no.
Let go of me. Let go of me!
Leave me alone! I
don't want to hurt you!
It's not me that you want!
Get off! Oh...
Get off of me!
So you just let him go.
You were supposed to
keep Pierce distracted,
not confront him in the
middle of the precinct.
I... overestimated my abilities
and underestimated his.
It's not his fault. I mean,
I wish I'd had a chance to
give Pierce a piece of my mind.
Thank you, Ms. Lopez.
When Dan asked me to
give Pierce that phone,
and told me the whole crazy theory,
I got to be honest, I had a
really hard time believing it.
Yeah, well, the fact that
you do, Ella, it means a lot.
Hey, we're O.G.
Okay, you ask me to
take a leap of faith,
I'm already jumping.
But, you guys, when I
handed him that phone,
that look in his eyes...
I just wanted to tear his
damn throat out right there.
Okay, so now what?
We have no idea where Pierce is going,
who's still loyal to him.
Hell, we can't even
go back to the precinct
to run this guy's fingerprints
to figure out who the hell he is.
Pierce has completely
reinvented himself before.
He'll do it again.
Disappear forever.
Which means our window is tight.
- What are you doing?
- I'm calling him.
- Chloe.
- Hey.
I-I just heard that
Lucifer attacked you?
Wha-What's going on?
What did Lucifer tell you?
That you're an immortal.
That, uh, you're Cain from the Bible.
Just a bunch of, uh, uh, crazy stuff.
It's all true.
Hey... Marcus...
are you okay?
I'm fine.
It's good to hear your voice.
Yeah, you, too.
Where are you? I'm worried about you.
Lucifer's next to you, isn't he?
Espinoza, too?
What? No.
You're a good liar,
but I know you, Chloe.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're here.
Ella, too,
and the guy you sent to kill Dan.
Chloe, I can explain.
You know what, I don't
believe a word you say.
Was anything that happened
between us real, any of it?
I did love you.
I still love you.
Life was a curse until I met you.
Since then, I've done whatever it takes
to stay alive for you.
All right, well, I want
you to do something then.
I want you to turn yourself in.
It's not happening.
Okay, we've got your guy here,
and he is gonna crack.
He's not gonna say anything.
He knows I can get to his sister.
Chloe, you need to know.
No, I want you to know.
One way or another, Pierce,
I am going to find you.
I doubt that.
It's okay. It's okay.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Maze, you need to rest.
No, I can't stay here.
Pierce is right.
Being on Earth...
around all these humans...
all these emotions, makes me weak.
You look like you fought ten people
and ran a mile to get here.
12 people.
Four miles.
My point is...
you did that... for me.
To save me.
Emotions...
emotions are hard.
But that's why they make you strong.
And this is...
This is the strongest
I've ever seen you.
Linda, I'm...
You don't have to say anything.
Your actions speak plenty.
Ah.
That's the thing.
Actions are easy for me.
That's why I need to say it.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
But I got to ask.
Is somebody really trying to kill me?
Don't worry.
You're safe.
Everything's gonna be fine.
I miss Charlotte.
So do I, Ms. Lopez.
I can't believe she's really gone.
And that Pierce would do what he did.
I know,
God works in mysterious ways,
and bad things happen for a reason.
But this many bad things,
I just...
I'm having a hard time
finding any reason.
Why would He do all this?
Well, I can't believe I'm saying this,
but I don't actually think
it's my Father's fault.
See, all this time I thought it was Him
pulling the strings.
I've started to realize that
we are the responsible parties.
It's quite devious of
Him, if you think about it.
We've no one to blame but ourselves.
Screw that.
I blame Pierce.
And, Big Guy?
You and I are on rocky ground.
We know about your sister.
Yeah? Then you know why I'm not talking.
If you cooperate, we can protect her.
You can protect her?
I'm tied to a chair in a penthouse
above a nightclub.
You, him,
you can't protect anyone.
Where's your safe house?
The walk-in closet?
That's what I thought.
Chloe, can I have a second
alone with him, please?
Can I leave you alone with him?
Okay.
Oh, God, listen, save
whatever threats you think...
A corrupt cop.
What?
That's what Pierce called me...
when we first met.
And it pissed me off when he said it.
Well, you know what?
He was right.
I have stolen evidence.
I've had someone killed.
And I never regretted
it for a split second.
So if you're wondering,
would I kill the guy who
tried to murder me in my sleep?
With the gun
that killed the woman I love?
What do you think the answer is?
My s... my sister,
Kelsey, she's...
all I care about... The only thing.
So, if you can prove to me
that you can really... and I
mean really... protect her...
I'll tell you whatever you want to know.
I... just...
His sister's address.
Once we can prove she's safe,
he promised he'd give
us everything we need.
Okay, Lucifer and I will go get her.
You guys, stay here, keep an eye on him.
Right, the sister's loft
should be right up here.
All right.
Detective.
This is all my fault.
What? No, no, no, you can't
blame yourself for Pierce.
No, you were right.
You tried to warn me about him,
and I didn't listen to you.
But... although, who could
believe anything you say?
Angels, demons, immortal men.
Detective, I always tell you the truth.
No.
You tell me your truth.
And I know
that all of these metaphors,
they're real for you.
But I think...
I think humoring them
has just encouraged you, and
that's on me, but I'm done.
Detective.
No more metaphors.
No more "devil" talk.
I've told you before,
you may think that that's what you are,
but... I don't see you that way.
Lately, I'm not sure I do, either.
All right, well, first things first.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Come on.
Okay.
Hello?
Kelsey, are you here?
Your brother sent us.
Are you sure?
- Okay. All right, thanks.
- What's going on?
I called in a favor to Detroit PD.
Had them run that
dude's prints on the DL.
Uh-huh. And...?
He's an only child.
There is no sister.
So that means that they're
walking into a trap.
Something doesn't feel right.
I wouldn't do that, Chloe.
You don't have to do this, Pierce.
Yes, I do.
And normally, I would just
skip town and reinvent myself.
But this time, I can't.
Not before I kill Lucifer.
What?
- Why?
- Because I know
that he'll never stop hunting me.
And I can't afford to spend
the rest of my days
looking over my shoulder.
But you don't have to die, Chloe.
Step away from him.
Detective, for once, I
agree with this imbecile.
Step aside.
No.
Detective.
Chloe.
I believed everything you said,
Marcus.
That you loved me.
That you did all of this for me.
Which is why I know
that you won't shoot.
You made me realize that
life is worth living.
And I will do anything to stay alive.
And if you get in the way of that...
Okay.
I believe you.
I don't want to die.
I can't.
Not without stopping you.
No! No! Detective!
What? No, no, no, no, no, no.
This... this can't happen.
This...
Finish it. Finish it!
No!
What happened?
You're safe.
That's all that matters.
We need to find Pierce.
I guess it's just you and me now.
Dan?
Hey, Chloe, uh, it's a trap.
Dan, I-I know.
I know.
We had to find out the hard way.
Pierce, he tried to kill us.
What? Are you okay?
Yeah, I am. Is she okay?
I-I don't know how,
but I am.
Or maybe I do know.
Maybe I've been avoiding the
biggest truth this whole...
I have to go.
Chloe, don't go in there without backup.
There's no point.
The detective's a
safe distance away now.
Ah, that's good.
I came prepared.
As I recall...
this can kill you pretty well.
A fair fight it is, then, Cain.
Someone's been working out.
I promised you...
that I would find a way to kill you.
I am a Devil of my word.
Is Chloe okay?
She's fine.
No thanks to you.
Now that I know I'm dying,
I don't know what I was so afraid of.
I'm going to Heaven.
You really believe that.
I told you, Lucifer, I don't
regret anything I've done.
Yes, but that was before you
killed Charlotte Richards.
No.
No, that was an accident.
Well, you pulled the trigger.
You ended her life.
You chose to kill her.
Oh...
Deep down,
you know you're a monster.
And that you belong in Hell,
where you will torture yourself
with that truth for eternity.
'Cause no matter what you tell yourself,
you can't outrun what you've done.
What you truly are.
And neither can you.
Lucifer.
It's all true.
Detective?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net