Previously, on Lucifer...
My dad screwed us both.
But perhaps there's a way
- for us to screw him back.
- How?
By killing you.
- Amenadiel's nice.
- If he were nice,
he wouldn't be sneaking around
behind my back with my friend,
and lying about it.
You know, don't you?
You're the ones who have been
lying to me about this fling for weeks.
I'd like to try and help.
You don't have to treat me.
I think I do. For both of us.
LUCIFER: In my quest to help you die,
I've done some research.
I've read every book,
I've analyzed every language.
LUCIFER: I'm completely out of ideas.
We can't rewrite history.
Detective, you're a genius.
You've just given me my idea.
LUCIFER: Once upon a time,
there were two
brothers... Kane and Abel.
They fought, as brothers
often do, over everything.
What's that supposed to
be? Are we shaking hands
or holding spiders?
[CHUCKLES] That's you and your brother
pummeling each other over a pet rock.
And here's you two scamps
tugging on both ends of a snake.
That's not how it happened.
Well, artistic license, my friend.
The point is that you were
always at each other's throats.
Until... [SNIFFS]
you fought to the death.
You killed Abel
and became the world's
first murderer.
Now, the part where my father marks you,
cursing you to walk
the earth for eternity,
- it's tricky to draw.
- Now, um,
I've heard this one
before... The ending sucks.
My point exactly.
We all know how your story ends.
But what if we change how it begins?
What if you never killed Abel?
What if we did...
this?
Clean slate.
That's impossible. How would we do that?
Oh, simple.
I shall fly down to Hell,
pluck your brother's soul,
and drop it into a vacant body.
This would make Abel technically alive,
and therefore not
murdered, and you innocent.
Wait, back up. My brother is in Hell?
Yes, of course. In fact,
he's our oldest tenant.
I knew it. Do you know how many
times I've tried to tell people
Abel is the asshat? No
one ever believes me.
Right, can we just
focus on my genius plan?
If we bring Abel back to life,
that would erase your crime.
No crime, no mark, no curse.
You'd be mortal and can finally die.
PIERCE: This one's good.
Oh, this one's even better.
Yeah, a bit past its
sell-by date, I'm afraid.
Wait till Abel wakes up in this body.
I never thought I'd say this,
but slow down, Lieutenant.
Time to lay down some
soul-dropping rules,
or what I think the rules are, at least.
You have done this before, right?
Not exactly, but based
on a sample size of, uh,
one crooked cop and one goddess,
I can only drop a soul into
someone who's recently died.
How recent?
The instant after death.
So we need a fresh one.
How are we gonna find that?
Hey, guys?
There's been an explosion
at a high-rise downtown.
There's one dead at the scene,
one on the way to the ICU.
Oh, that's promising.
- Excuse me?
- He means that's a promising chance
to question the witness at the hospital.
Mm. Yes,
where loads of people
are on the brink of death.
So you want to question
someone who's unconscious
and in critical condition?
The witness may
recover, have some intel.
- Can't hurt to check.
- Hmm.
Okay, we'll work the crime scene.
Lucifer, you coming?
Lucifer's coming with me this time.
Shall we?
♪ Such a pretty face ♪
♪ Straight teeth ♪
♪ Look baby, now you playing
in a different league... ♪
DAN: Bomb squad did their threat report.
Ruled it as a homicide,
handed it off to us.
Looks like the bomb came by messenger.
And, uh, an assistant opened
the package, triggering the bomb.
Huh. Is that the messenger?
Yep. Rest in peace, dude.
We tried to track who sent it,
but they covered their tracks.
One thing we do know
is that the assistant wasn't the target.
Package was addressed to her boss.
Producer Alexa Lee, she just
came in, she's pretty shook up.
All right. Let's go talk to her.
Where were you when the blast occurred?
At home.
My Tuesday session with Paolo,
my Pilates trainer.
You have any idea
who'd want to hurt you?
Any past enemies, grudges,
anything like that?
How much time you got? [SCOFFS]
Come on, this is Hollywood.
I get way more hate mail than fan mail.
Did any one threat stand out at all?
Uh, my assistant will know.
Bree Garland.
She deals with all my mail and...
oh, my God, did Bree open the box?
She's in the ICU.
But we haven't heard word yet.
Oh, no.
It should have been me.
Poor Bree.
LUCIFER: Bree Garland?
- She won't do at all.
- Why not?
Well, how much do you hate your brother
on a scale of one to ten?
One thousand, infinity plus one.
Right, well, if we pop
Abel into a body this young,
you could be stuck with
him for another 70 years.
That's a lot of quality time.
Copy, not her.
[SIGHS] No, what we
need is someone ancient,
someone at death's door.
- [HEART RATE MONITOR FLATLINING]
- Someone...
[CLEARS THROAT]
PIERCE: "Do not resuscitate.
97 years old,
no next of kin."
Perfect.
Yes, we'll put Abel in
this old coot. [GIGGLES]
He gets a second chance at life
and you get your chance at death.
Let's do this.
Right.
Enjoy the show, Dad.
[WINGS WHOOSH]
[HEART RATE MONITOR FLATLINING]
- [WIND WHOOSHES]
- [FEET THUD]
Right.
[HEART RATE MONITOR BEATS RHYTHMICALLY]
[SIGHS]
Any second now.
Any second.
You sure you did this right?
Well, I know I grabbed Abel down below.
- PIERCE: Did you put him in the right place?
- LUCIFER: Probably.
PIERCE: What do you mean, "probably"?
LUCIFER: Well, like I
said, I'm new to this.
But where else would I have dropped him?
- Did you screw this up?
- I don't know.
I mean, it's not like
there's an instruction manual.
Lucifer.
Where did she go?
Hmm?
Oh.
Okay, I see what's happened here.
It appears I may have
misplaced your brother's soul.
[CHUCKLES]
But in my defense, what were the chances
of this young lady expiring
at the exact same time?
Tell me you didn't put Abel in her body.
[SIGHS] So I make one teeny mistake.
Yes, it appears that Abel is
running around as a young woman.
But the point is, we did it.
Abel's alive.
What matters is, your curse is lifted
and you should no longer have your mark.
So come on, let's have a look.
The mark is still there,
which means I'm still cursed.
We failed.
[SIGHS]
Bugger.
- Other Best Tvseries also Available For You Just For Free At  -
-- www.FlashTvSeries.Tk --
He's a spry one.
Or she.
No sign of her anywhere.
I mean, him.
This is head-spinning, isn't it?
- We need to find him.
- Why?
You already figured out a plan "B"?
Another way Abel can help
remove your curse? What is it?
I don't know, but whatever
it is, it has to involve Abel.
Right. Time to call the detective.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
"Hey, Decker. We broke Abel out of Hell,
dropped his soul into the wrong body
and lost him. Now he's on the lam
in the body of the
victim from your case.
Also, I'm immortal."
There's no need to get snippy.
Fine, we'll do this on
our own under the radar.
Now, he's your brother.
Where do you think he'd go?
I don't know, we're
not exactly in touch.
It's been a few millenia.
You tortured him in Hell.
You probably know him better than I do.
[SIGHS] Barely saw him, actually.
I was more of a big picture kind of guy.
The good news is I do
know a demon or two.
Come on.
CHLOE: Who knew a producer
could have this many enemies?
Occupational hazard, I guess.
Yikes, check this out.
Look at that.
Huh.
"You're going to die."
- Hmm.
- I do believe we have a winner.
Hang on.
Look at the Gs.
It's the same handwriting.
Sent a few weeks back.
They were upset
about one of Alexa's movies, The Plunge.
"It's full of lies.
If you want the real truth,
read The Z Prophecy."
What is that?
Wait, Alexa made The Plunge?
Have you seen it?
[CHUCKLING]: Oh, man. A group of teens,
they have to travel to
the center of the Earth
to unclog this blocked-up magma.
Oh, man, does it get intense.
Mm-hmm. Whoever wrote this letter
wants people to read The Z Prophecy.
Wonder what it is.
DAN: "Visionary, Liam Wade,"
author of The Z Prophecy
and a whole bunch of other
conspiracy theories. Wow.
Seems pretty bonkers.
Check out his manifesto.
CHLOE: Look.
It's the same handwriting
as the letters.
Okay, we need to talk to him
and find out exactly why
he was threatening Alexa.
CHARLOTTE: Crap.
Old socks.
Moldy leaves.
If it tastes so bad, why drink it?
Well, I read that five doses a day
helps supercharge your memory.
I've also tried...
meditation, sudoku,
a lot of broccoli,
but no recovered memories so far.
Just flatulence.
I was hoping that you had some,
um, memory-jogging techniques.
Perhaps some mental
exercises I could do,
preferably, while I'm sleeping
because that's four hours a day
I don't need to waste
just sleeping. [CHUCKLES]
You do realize you can't win at therapy.
Oh, please, I can win at anything.
Let's start there.
Your desire to win tells me
you have a strong need for control.
Could we focus on
finding my lost memories?
Because that's what I'm paying you for.
Well, I think we should slow down
and focus on what you do remember.
You say that you keep reliving
the same thing over and over.
Is it like,
say, an endless, horrible loop?
One you weren't even
aware you were trapped in?
I know this is scary.
But it's where we need to start.
In your Hell.
No, that's the last thing I need.
And not what I asked you for at all.
Okay, well, it's not really
about what you think you need.
Or ask for.
I know you're used to being in charge,
but I'm the expert here.
You need to let me drive this.
Drive me crazy, so that you
can get me hooked on therapy,
and milk me for every cent.
No, thanks.
[EXHALES]
[MAZE MOANS]
Oh, God, Abel.
[CHUCKLES]
You never forget your first.
So you'll help us find him, then?
I'll tell you what I know
so you can do your own
grunt work for once.
Did you know that Abel
was the first soul in Hell?
Mm, an infernal guinea pig,
- so to speak.
- MAZE: We all learned to torture
by torturing him.
What'd you do to him?
[INHALES] Well, Abel
would be out partying,
and then, you'd show up.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't walk like that.
- Yeah, you do.
- Yes, you do.
Why was I even there?
You were the star of Abel's Hell loop.
No matter what he did, you'd
always show up, and kill him.
Over and over.
I was his torturer?
LUCIFER: Whilst this is
all very illuminating,
Maze, how do we find Abel?
Keep an ear out for someone
babbling in Sumerian?
[LAUGHING]: Oh, no, no.
He speaks in English.
And all the romance languages.
- [SCOFFS]
- Arabic, Mandarin.
I mean, he's a little dated,
and his Hindi needs work.
Wait, what?
Me and the other demons
would get bored, so we'd
switch up the Hell loop.
Okay? It would always
be you killing him,
but at different
times, different places.
He was a fast learner.
So, what you're saying is
Hell made him multilingual
and completely adaptable?
And we put him in the
body of a young woman.
[GROANS]
Smooth move, boys.
Hold on. If Abel's Hell
was constantly changing,
then this may just feel like
another Hell loop to him.
He may have no idea he's
actually alive again.
Do you remember where
he would start his loop?
- Yes.
- Hmm.
Do you know who he reminds me of?
[STOMPS FOOT]
[SCOFFS]
Total poon hound.
You want to know where Abel is...
ask yourself.
Where would
caveman Lucifer go?
Fancy a walk?
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, I don't believe in superstition ♪
♪ When you pull me in
I get a premonition... ♪
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Ladies, ladies.
Let's be fruitful, and multiply, huh?
Allow me to bless you with my seed.
[CHUCKLES]
♪ ♪
DAN: Would it kill this
nutjob to put in a driveway?
[SIGHS]
Right, Chloe?
Huh?
Chloe.
What? Sorry, sorry.
I'm distracted.
- It's just...
- Yeah.
Pierce, taking Lucifer.
I'm worried that it's
something I did or said or both.
Why?
What did you do or say?
Well...
uh, you know what? Never mind.
It's not Pierce, i-it's Lucifer.
When he started here, no
one wanted to work with him.
And I spent all this
time training him, and...
now that he's somewhat
of a decent partner,
Pierce just swoops in and grabs him?
Lucifer doesn't even blink?
- It's not cool.
- Right.
Possessive much?
Come on, I'm just
giving you a hard time.
So he's working with Pierce.
Lucifer's still your partner.
What?
What, do I got something on my face?
Oh, God, is there a spider?
Is it still there?
It's not a spider.
It's a sniper.
What?
Mr. Wade?
Please put down the weapon.
LIAM [OVER SPEAKER]:
This is private property.
Leave now.
Did you send this note
to Alexa Lee?
You read my message.
People are finally starting to listen.
DAN: Mr. Wade, um, we're here
because of a recent
attempt on Alexa's life.
Wait, why do you think I
would want to hurt Alexa?
Well, for starters, in the note,
you said that she was gonna die.
Yeah. Because she is.
She's gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
We're all gonna die if we don't act now.
I wasn't threatening Alexa.
- I wrote her a wake-up call.
- About what?
Well, I'm glad you asked, ma'am.
You see,
our planet's magma flows are blocked.
If that flow isn't released, soon...
[EXHALES]
big, molten apocalypse.
DAN: Right.
I saw the movie.
And now you don't believe
me, and that is the problem.
The Plunge made
the prophecy into a joke.
Her crappy movie made a mockery
out of a very, very serious issue.
I don't know, man, I kind
of dug The Plunge.
- [SIGHS]
- Seriously?
A jock, a nerd and a
princess save the planet?
I mean, come on.
It was fun.
[EXHALES]
Wow. [CLEARS THROAT]
Look. I hated Alexa's movie.
Okay? But I would never hurt her.
I-I actually kind of owe her.
Because guess who has
196 more Twitter followers
since The Plunge premiered?
Okay, if you didn't
attack her, then who did?
Alexa had a lot of enemies.
Big Agro, Big Frac.
The Bolivians.
The carnies.
Carnies?
Okay, we're gonna need
to search your property.
Extensively.
♪ Hmm, mm ♪
♪ You bring out the devil in me... ♪
ABEL: Mm.
Look at the bosoms on that one.
This is the land of milk and honey.
Hello, Abel.
I've been watching you, Abel.
I do not want to lay with you.
Or any other man.
It's not my thing.
Listen, I'm not hitting on you.
You're a pawn.
Brought here by forces
that you don't understand.
Now, I'm here to take you
back to where you belong.
Okay. Does "no" not mean "no" anymore?
I want one of these fine maidens
to warm my bed, not you.
Or any of the men who've been eyeing me
- like I'm some big hunk of...
- Abel.
Have you seen yourself lately?
Oh.
Are those bosoms mine?
So that's why none of those menfolk
heard a word I said.
Doesn't all this feel familiar?
Don't you sense what's about to happen?
Yes.
Every time I seek out
revelry, my brother arrives.
And what does he do?
He...
He kills me.
Over and over.
And there's nothing
I can do to avoid it.
I've tried everything.
Fighting him, running
from him, all in vain.
I'm trapped.
I can never escape.
You're right, Abel.
You can't fight him.
But I may have a way
out of this for you.
You want me to kill myself?
Well, I've never tried that before.
How many more strip clubs
are we going to search?
Why, as many as it takes.
What would I and therefore Abel do next?
Keep up the fun, obviously.
Well, we just spent the last half hour
wandering past billboards
of women's lingerie.
And your problem is?
"Problems," plural.
One: no sign of Abel,
two: we have no idea what we're
gonna do even if we find him.
Well, speak for yourself,
Negative Nelly, 'cause I think
I've worked out exactly
what we need to do.
- Wait, you have?
- Yes.
Well, Dad's an old
school kind of guy, right?
Eye for an eye, and all that?
You killed Abel, so in order to
make things truly even-steven...
- Abel has to kill me.
- Mm-hmm.
It does make sense.
So which way do you think you're headed?
Once you finally pop off.
Pearly gates or blazing inferno?
Be ironic if you went
to all this trouble
just to end up in a Hell loop.
I'd never punish myself like that.
Hell is all about your own
guilt torturing you, right?
- Right.
- Well,
my conscience is clear.
Oh.
Killing your brother
isn't the kind of thing
you just shake off.
Listen, Abel wanted
to kill me just as much
as I wanted to kill him.
Why do you think he's in Hell?
I'm just the guy who won the fight.
Hello.
Where would I and
therefore Abel go next?
Wherever she's going.
[KANE SIGHS]
♪ Well, I got to keep on walking ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm looking for a phonograph ♪
♪ That'll play out loud... ♪
Results from our samples came back.
Liam told the truth.
No trace of explosive
compounds on the farm.
- Or much else.
- Hmm.
Unless you count all the turkey jerky
he was hoarding for the apocalypse.
[CHUCKLES]
"Bolivian crime organizations"?
You're not taking Liam
seriously, are you?
Okay, don't laugh, but
I've been looking into
some of his theories.
Ring of evil carnies.
I'm calling it.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
All right. Ella got back
to me with her bomb report.
It was made from fertilizer
that's banned in the U.S.,
but guess where it's still being used.
Bolivia? No way.
Yeah. So I took a closer
look into Alexa's company
to see if I could prove
a Bolivian connection.
Uh-huh.
She's got a lot of
international financiers,
which is pretty normal nowadays.
But I highlighted the Bolivian ones.
Guess there was a grain of
truth in Liam's craziness.
We should cross-check that
list with the FBI and DHS.
I already did. These names are linked up
to the Bolivian drug cartel.
[COMPUTER CHIMING]
This is my contact from the TSA.
One of the Bolivian contractors
landed in L.A. this morning.
Wonder what he's doing here.
I know you can do it, Abel.
[CHUCKLES]
Wait. Who are you?
How do you know all of this?
- No!
- [GUNSHOT]
That's her.
[ONLOOKERS SCREAMING]
What are you doing here?
Where'd he go? I mean, where did she go?
I don't know.
[SIGHS]
I told you to stay out of my way.
And I told you Father
cursed Kane for a reason.
You actually thought that I would just
sit around while you two idiots
were raising Abel?
I've been following you, Luci.
So reckless, even by your standards.
[CHUCKLES] Well, I think it's
rather brilliant, actually.
Using the wings Dad
unfairly punished me with
to undo another one of
his unfair punishments.
Do you seriously not realize
just how dangerous
it is to anger Father?
Have you also forgotten that
He took away your devil face?
Precisely my point, brother.
I've got nothing left to lose.
Oh, don't be foolish, Luci.
There are so many things
that Father can still
take away from you.
Again with the fearmongering.
For the nth time, I'm not
going to just take Dad's abuse.
Cowering from Him is your jam, remember?
You know what?
It's not you that I am
trying to prove my worth to.
So think what you
will, do what you will.
I'm gonna find Abel and send
him back to where he belongs.
Oh, so we're just gonna let him leave,
so he can get in our way later.
No, no.
Next time, we'll be ready.
Bad news. Dead guy?
Bolivian cartel hit man.
What?
The Bolivian cartel
wants to kill Bree? Why?
Don't know.
[SIGHS] There's no keeping
this from Decker anymore.
Fine. I'll let you tell her.
Okay.
Okay? That's it?
What, you're not gonna
tear him a new one?
Come on, I've gotten
much worse for much less.
I'm not gonna yell at my boss,
even if he lost our witness twice.
Oh, because you've got
a soft spot for him?
Because I'm not an idiot.
Look, you're the lieutenant,
you call the shots.
But the next time you
want to steal my partner
to tail the target of my investigation,
you want to clue me in first?
Before it turns into a public gunfight?
Deal. Next time.
You said "target."
Are you thinking the bomb was
meant for Bree and not Alexa?
Well, maybe the Bolivians knew
that Bree always opened her boss' mail,
used it as a misdirect.
Well, I still don't understand.
Why does the Bolivian cartel
want a Hollywood assistant dead?
Did she neglect to pick the pistachios
off their quinoa salad?
Well, that's the missing piece.
So we should find out what Alexa knows.
- If I can have my partner back?
- Of course.
I'll track down Bree, I
need to find him before...
You mean her.
I need to find her
before the cartel does.
Mm-hmm.
So the bomb wasn't for me.
Well, the intended target
was your assistant, Bree.
Have you heard from her lately?
What are you talking about?
Bree's in the hospital.
She fled from the ER.
No one's heard from her. She
could be in a lot of danger.
I guarantee she is.
Well, how's that possible?
I-I was told she suffered
fatal internal injuries.
Yes, well, you could
say she's like a new man.
[ALEXA SIGHS]
Well, thank God, but
we need to find her.
We're doing everything we
can to make sure she's safe.
What? Oh, yes, yes, of course.
That, too, but I need her back so bad.
Do you know what it's like
to have someone take away
an assistant you depend on?
- Yes, I do, actually.
- [SIGHS]
I mean, I-I am seriously
lost here without her.
I-I don't even know how
to call out of the office.
Do you know how?
So you have no idea what kind of beef
these Bolivian associates of
yours may have had with Bree?
I don't.
Bree is fluent in Spanish,
so she dealt with those
investors directly.
And you didn't think to vet them at all
before you went into business with them?
Have you seen the films I make?
I can't afford to be picky.
Someone offers me money, I take it.
Okay, well, I'm gonna need to
see any documented interactions
you have with these investors.
- Absolutely, they're in there.
- Okay.
Oh, right.
Only Bree's fingerprint can unlock it.
Bree installed a biometric
lock on the file cabinet?
Seems a little paranoid.
What did she have to hide?
Two recent incoming
wires for 50 grand each,
- both from a South American bank.
- Bingo.
Shady side business
with the Bolivians it is.
So Bree was embezzling from
that useless boss of hers.
Huh, who can blame her?
Does loyalty mean nothing to you?
Alexa gave Bree her
first job in Hollywood.
She trained her.
You don't just ditch that
the minute some
big-armed, blue-eyed,
toned...
Bolivian drug lord comes around, okay?
Y-you, you don't, you don't.
Dan, if Bree bolted from the ER,
maybe she left some things
behind, like her phone.
Mm-hmm, which could hold proof
to her connection with the Bolivians.
That's good thinking.
I'm gonna check on that.
Okay, thanks.
All right, I'm gonna see if Pierce
had any luck finding Bree.
Oh, well, he won't need any luck.
He's got something far better than that.
Decker's right. You're cute.
But I'm mid-bounty
and I just got a lead.
So, if you don't mind...
Lucifer told me to tell you
this is exactly the opposite
of what Amenadiel wants.
I'm in.
Great.
- How do we find him?
- Well...
Your brother's a predictable one.
He always runs to food or boobs.
Usually boobs.
That's how we found him the first time.
Now he has boobs, that
might change his itinerary.
That's right, I totally
forgot about that.
[CHUCKLES] Is he hot?
Just tell me how we find him.
Well, every now and again,
the sucker would do
something I never saw coming.
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
Hello, Kane.
- And good-bye.
- [GUNSHOT]
[GROANS]
Just like that.
Yes! [GRUNTS] Finally!
Slayed you before
you slayed me! [GRUNTS]
Ashes to ashes,
you bastard!
[GRUNTS RHYTHMICALLY]
Enjoy it while it lasts, Abel.
How do you know my name?
And what is that supposed to mean?
[GRUNTING]
Thanks for the heads-up.
You said you wanted to die.
Make up your mind, cupcake.
And the mark is still there.
[SOBBING] Please, no. No, please.
Please.
Just make it quick, Kane.
Please make it quick.
No.
I need you alive, so
you can help me die.
Wait, what?
This has to be a trick.
You always kill me.
That was when you were in Hell,
where you've spent
the last few millennia.
Maze tortured you in the afterlife.
Your punishment was to get killed
by me, over and over.
MAZE: That's right.
You were trapped in a Hell
loop, but now you're out.
You're alive, brother.
[IMITATES EXPLOSION]
Turns out Abel killing
me didn't remove the mark.
Mm-hmm. Right, yes, I
got that from the whole
"you still being alive" of it all.
So much for making
everything even-steven.
It's now time for Plan "C."
[SCOFFS] I didn't realize we had one.
We don't.
But we'll think of something.
Okay, and how is
bringing your she-brother
into the precinct going to help?
Much as I'm enjoying his
Basic Instinct routine.
First things first, we have to make sure
the Bolivians don't kill him.
Bree.
I'm Detective Decker.
This is Charlotte Richards
from the DA's office.
Miss Garland, do you confirm
that you're waiving your
right to legal council?
Yes. Woman, I will waive
whatever you want me to waive.
Uh, Lieutenant said he had noticed
some PTSD symptoms,
so we should just kind of
roll with it if we can.
Don't take this lightly, Miss Garland.
It's a big decision.
Mmm. Not as big as my flock.
Do you know how many sheep I possess?
Enough for two wives.
Enough to feed our offspring
and our offspring's offspring.
LUCIFER: He fits right in.
Is it me, or is your
plan going down in flames?
It'll work.
Well, as impressive
as your flock sounds,
let's get back to the deal.
The terms are simple.
You share all the information you have
on the Bolivian cartel
in exchange for immunity.
And the full protection of the LAPD.
Yes, to whatever those words mean.
Now, let's discuss who is
going to lay with me first.
Uh, don't you want to read the
terms of the deal, at least?
What for? I've been
told you're very wise.
I trust you.
CHARLOTTE: Just like that?
You're going to let us drive this,
just completely give up control?
Mm-hmm.
Doesn't that scare you?
Not nearly as much as
the place I just escaped.
I would do anything to
avoid returning to that Hell.
If you'd been there,
you would do the same.
Charlotte.
Yes, sorry, we're good.
Great. Great. Okay, Bree?
- Mm-hmm.
- Come on, you're coming with me.
[SHARP INHALE] Mm, you smell good.
Well so much for her being
released into your custody.
We can't let him spend
too much time with Decker.
She'll figure out something's going on.
[SIGHS] Let me see what I can do.
It's time for you to go home, Abel.
It wasn't easy for me to track you down,
but you're not getting
away from me this time.
What the...
MAZE: Meet my punching bag.
Look familiar?
Mazikeen. What are you doing here?
What does it look like?
Keeping you out of Lucifer's way.
[SHOUTS]
I don't want to fight you, Mazikeen.
Who cares what you want?
So you worked here for two years,
it's still not ringing a bell?
No, but your backside is ringing a...
Oh, you poor, forgetful thing.
Thankfully, all we need
is your fingerprint.
Well, my finger goes wherever
the lady tells me it goes.
Hey, Dan. Did you have any
luck finding Bree's phone?
DAN: No.
Because guess who collected
her stuff from the hospital?
Alexa.
That's odd.
Yeah, right?
So, I dug deeper.
Looked into her Pilates alibi.
Get this: her class
is actually in the morning.
She rescheduled that day
for 2:00 p.m. exactly.
It's like she knew to
be out of the office.
She knew the bomb was coming.
- Who knew?
- Alexa.
What, and the Bolivians warned her? Why?
- Put it on speakerphone.
- [SIGHS]
Okay, maybe the Bolivians were
working with Alexa, not Bree.
Maybe Bree found out
what they were up to
and wanted to blow the whistle.
Well, that would explain
those incoming wires in Bree's account.
Cartel tried to pay
her off, silence her.
And when the nice way didn't work,
they tried the not-so-nice way.
Well, hopefully the proof is
behind drawer number one, so...
Wait a minute.
Why would Alexa send
us straight to the place
where we'd find proof of her crimes?
Makes no sense.
Unless...
it's a trap.
Bree, wait!
[CLICKS, BEEPS]
Don't move.
DAN: Alexa knew Bree would need proof
to turn her in, so she must
have rigged the file cabinet
that contained it. We
walked right into her trap.
If they move, the whole thing blows.
Call the bomb squad.
PIERCE: Decker, you need
to get out of there, stat.
I'm not going anywhere, Lieutenant.
What do you mean, you're
not going anywhere?
You need to get out of there, now.
Don't worry, I'm staying right here.
Oh, woman, your loyalty touches me.
PIERCE: What happened to
"You're the lieutenant,
you call the shots"?
CHLOE: There is an innocent victim
glued to a bomb.
"Innocent victim" is highly debatable.
Lucifer, Bree was trying
to do the right thing.
It's why the Bolivians
and Alexa want her dead.
I'm not leaving.
ABEL: Oh, my flock
is your flock, this I swear.
PIERCE: Okay.
No, no, no, o-opposite of okay.
PIERCE: If you're gonna stay, Decker,
I can talk you through defusing it.
It's safer than waiting for it
to blow up before the
bomb squad gets there...
Wait a minute. Wait,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Chloe, Chloe, think about this, okay?
Think about Trixie.
I am thinking about her.
And I'm also thinking that
Bree's a daughter, too.
Oh, come on.
So... [SIGHS]
what do I do now? What,
cut all these wires willy-nilly?
Damn movies. No.
You have to get into the box
and disconnect the trigger.
And, very carefully,
remove the blasting cap.
Ugh, this is madness.
PIERCE: Then toss it as far as possible.
Oh, you want her to toss an
explosive, that sounds safe.
If the cap goes off away from
the charge, it'll be harmless.
Lieutenant! I understand
why your priority
is to save your...
this young woman, but I
will not let you endanger
the detective's life in the process.
He's not endangering my life.
I am choosing to be here,
and if you're not gonna help,
you should probably just leave.
Well, we both know
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm your partner.
Okay, good.
Then listen to me... I'm
gonna need both my hands,
so please come help me.
Okay? Hold this.
I'll use this, and, uh...
All right.
[BOMB BEEPING]
[QUIETLY]: Easy...
CHLOE: Got the blasting cap.
And...
Okay.
I think that means you can
take your thumb off now.
[BEEPS]
All right.
And don't tell us
where you want to put it next.
MAZE: Up your butt!
[PANTING]
That's where I want to shove this.
And then, I'll press the button.
I don't even understand
why you're so angry.
So what if Linda and I got together?
You dumped me.
Remember?
No, it's not about that.
Okay? It's about the betrayal.
The dirty...
sneaky...
lies!
When will you understand
that we were trying to protect you?
And when will you understand
I don't believe you?
[SIGHS]
All right.
Fine.
[BOTH PANTING]
Well, come on!
Come on! It's no fun
if you just stand there!
It's about as much fun as watching you
break Linda's heart, I'd say.
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
Even this, you had to ruin.
[DOOR OPENS, CLOSES]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Okay, thank you.
Hi.
So, we were able to lift
one of Alexa's prints
from the explosive.
Oh, good.
Sounds like enough to
arrest her for murder.
And get her to flip on the Bolivians.
Apparently, she was using
her movies to launder money
for the cartel.
And that's what Bree
was trying to expose.
Shame. I mean, I had the perfect
title for The Plunge 2.
2 Deep 2 Plunge.
With the number two, each time,
- instead of... the word.
- Instead of the word.
Yeah, I get it.
It's funny.
- Yeah.
So...
[CLEARS THROAT]
I just wanted to say thank you, again.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Night.
Without me...
you wouldn't have been in
danger in the first place.
CHARLOTTE: I'm sorry about last time.
I'm a bit of a control freak.
Ah.
Really?
I hadn't noticed.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
So, what's changed?
Well, I realized
that you're right, you're the expert.
And I should trust you.
And as scary as that is... [SIGHS]
there's something much scarier.
I, um, I wake up...
smell coffee.
It's nice.
I have breakfast
with my family.
Uh, we're happy.
[CHUCKLES]
At peace.
And then, a man
walks in and shoots each of them.
Dead.
And I know this man because
he's somebody that I represented,
and I know that he should
be in jail, but he's not.
Because of me.
I just smile,
while my family is killed.
I don't move a muscle.
[SHUDDERING BREATH]
Because I'm the reason
that it's happening.
I'm the reason that he's free.
And then, I wake up.
It's a new morning.
I smell the same coffee.
Pour the same cereal.
And then, someone else walks in,
and shoots my family.
This time, it's a different person.
Someone else I set free.
And I just...
smile again.
And I die inside again.
Over and over, and...
I don't know what it'll take
to stay out of that place.
I'm trying my best.
But I don't know if it'll be enough.
Well, it's a very brave start.
♪ I don't believe in Satan ♪
♪ But he believes in me... ♪
Thank you for saving my life, Kane.
I suppose we're even now.
[SIGHS]
Yet, this is still there.
Hmm.
This whole time, you've
been in a kind of Hell, too.
You still are.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too, brother.
[EXHALES]
Your face is still the
face of my torturer.
Fair enough.
I guess we still need some space.
That, we can agree on.
♪ He's the master of deceit ♪
♪ I don't believe in Satan... ♪
Ah, that was quite civil, actually.
I know I promised to
help you end your curse,
but I'm afraid we need to
dissolve our unholy alliance.
Why?
The risk is too great.
I mean, I don't mind
putting myself in danger,
but the detective?
If she had died, it
would have been my fault.
But you're the Devil,
you always keep your word.
I do.
So I hope you understand how
difficult a decision this was.
And yet, oddly, the
easiest I've ever made.
Well, I'm not done.
Abel's how my curse started,
he's got to be the way it ends.
As long as he's alive,
I still have hope.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[KANE SIGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
[SIREN WAILING]
No!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net