- Previously on Lucifer...
- Uriel didn't just die.
I killed him.
Where's Uriel?
Oh.
You look really familiar. Have we met?
35 years ago, Father
asked me to come down here
to bless a couple who was
unable to have a child.
MOM: God put her in Lucifer's path.
Why are you so upset?
Because I just don't know if it's real.
Why is it that sometimes I'm immortal,
and other times I'm all too human?
Appears you make me vulnerable.
What's in that package is
far more valuable than drugs.
LUCIFER: You're a bad man.
DAN: Dr. Jason Carlisle.
He saved the dissertation
while an innocent college student died.
(shouts)
Freeze!
ELLA: We are talking
designer poison, here.
So, how do we get an antidote?
Well, that right there
is the tricky part.
Designer poisons need
designer antidotes.
LUCIFER: Detective!
It won't stop.
(tires screech)
CHLOE: Lucifer.
The bleeding stopped. You don't
have to drive like a maniac.
You've forgotten you've
been poisoned, Detective,
or has it already reached your brain?
Maybe it's just a
nosebleed. I mean, I-I...
How could the professor
have injected me?
I didn't get one of his flu shots.
What about when you went after him?
Well, I don't know.
I tackled him to the ground,
we-we struggled for a bit,
and, God, I guess if
he injected me somehow,
it would have to be just...
- Ugh.
- Oh, God.
Everything's gonna be fine
once we get to the hospital.
Okay?
We can't go to the hospital.
- What?
- Lucifer, going to the hospital
didn't help any of the other victims.
The only thing that's gonna save my life
is finding the antidote.
Otherwise, I'm...
All right. All right, very well.
(tires screech)
No judgments, guys, okay?
You said come right away,
so I came right away.
You're lucky I remembered
to put on pants...
eventually. So, what's up?
- Well, um...
- Well, we're worried
that someone else, um, out
there might be poisoned.
Oh, I doubt it.
I asked every hospital in
the area to report anything
even resembling a poisoning.
So far, haven't heard a peep.
Well, just to be sure,
let's, uh, let's go over
what you found at the
professor's lab, okay?
Check it out.
(whispering): Uh, Detective.
We should tell her.
(whispering): No, we can't.
She'll freak out. It'll get in
the way of the investigation.
I really don't think
this is a good idea.
ELLA: Are you guys done
having your whisper fight?
Uh, just make out already
and get it over with. Yeesh.
So... I did find
this syringe on the scene.
It had a tiny bit of poison
left in it, so, yeah, in theory,
someone out there may have been dosed.
- Hmm.
- Okay, but the other poisons
had corresponding antidotes, yeah?
Did you find anything
to match this one?
I did.
Problem is, dude destroyed
whatever was inside.
Dick move, right?
I mean, that's why I'm glad no
one's reported to any hospitals,
'cause without the antidote,
ugh, they'd end up just
like the other victims.
You know, first a bloody nose and then
- fainting spells, followed by seizures...
- We get the point.
...and then their guts
slowly start boiling,
like, literally boiling.
It's so gross and nasty,
and 24 hours later...
- bam, just like that, dead as a doornail.
- Got it. Thank you. Yes.
- You've painting quite the picture,
Miss Lopez. - CHLOE: Right.
Yeah, let's go over everything else
- from the professor's lab. Okay?
- LUCIFER: Mm.
Just to see if we've missed anything.
Okay? Sure.
Okay. So...
Here we go.
I got your text. What's so urgent?
Uh... this way.
Somewhere we can speak in private.
(grunts)
Was this part of Father's plan?
Hmm?
Answer me, brother,
before I rip your spine out
- and beat you to death with it.
- What are you talking about?
How long...
how long have you been manipulating me?
Mom told you about Chloe?
Oh, that she did.
And that you put the
detective in my path.
No, I didn't.
Father did.
I was just another pawn in His game.
I had no idea.
And the detective?
Is she simply another
pawn as well or is she...
Is she?
She doesn't know anything.
Listen.
Luci, we've been played like puppets.
Father has manipulated us both.
Don't you dare compare our situations.
All that I have ever wanted
to do for all of my existence
was make Father proud.
I thought I was doing
great works in His name.
Instead, the very first of His angels
was busy making you a little girlfriend.
Oh. Well, my heart bleeds for you.
We're on the same side here, brother.
Are we?
Then be honest with me, brother.
How deep does Father's plan go?
Is the detective's poisoning part of it?
Poisoning?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You really don't know?
No.
Then you...
...you can't help her.
(sighs)
I'm sorry.
(door opens)
There you are. I've been
looking all over for you.
Amenadiel.
Give us a minute.
I... have an idea.
I need to talk to you.
Okay, so the professor's
been using this Burt guy
(whispering): to smuggle in the poisons.
What, so you think that Burt
might have smuggled
the antidotes as well?
- Yes.
- All right.
Point me to his prison cell.
Perhaps some toilet
wine waterboarding or...
(whispering): Well,
he's already out on bail,
but the good news is, he
does have an ankle bracelet
so he can't get far.
(Chloe coughing)
Detective.
I'm fine. We should go.
♪ ♪
They think they can keep me down.
Me!
Well, screw them!
I'll party every night until the trial,
and then every day once I'm found...
ALL: Innocent!
("It's Tricky" by Run-D.M.C. begins)
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's right on time ♪
♪ It's tricky ♪
♪ It's tricky, tricky, tricky, tricky ♪
♪ It's tricky to rock a rhyme ♪
♪ To rock a rhyme that's
right on time, it's tricky... ♪
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
No. No, you can bump into me anytime.
Have we met before?
Weren't you at that beach party?
Yeah. Yeah, I wa... I-I'm stalking you.
(both laugh)
So, why don't you show me the bedroom?
You read my mind.
So...
oh.
Uh.
Y-You okay?
Oh... um...
Yeah, yeah.
No, no, I'm fine.
I'm fine. What were you saying?
Uh... yeah. Yeah, maybe another time.
No, that doesn't really work for me.
(chuckles)
(grunts)
(groans)
Hey, what the hell is this?
Hello, Burtrude.
Remember me?
(Burt screams)
You didn't hurt him, did you?
Physically, no, as I promised.
- Too bad.
- I did get him to talk,
but he didn't smuggle the antidote.
What? You sure?
Unfortunately, yes, but he
did provide me with a lead.
The professor hired Burt
through some middleman,
a chap named Dave Maddox.
There's a good chance
the professor got the
antidotes from him.
Oh.
- Detective?
- Oh, sorry.
- Wait.
- You okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Detective!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What the hell were you thinking?
I thought I was being quite responsible
bringing her directly to the hospital.
You mean after the two of you
- went off and interrogated a
felon on bail? - Well, of course.
It was much easier to
get her here unconscious.
You know how stubborn she can get.
It doesn't change the fact that...
CHLOE: You guys know
that I'm right here, yeah?
Hey.
How you feeling?
Fine.
Lucifer, I told you no hospitals.
How am I supposed to find the antidote
if I'm laying here... ow.
DAN: Shh.
We'll take it from here.
Yes. Yes, we will.
And we'll start by
following up on your lead.
Dave Maddox. Yes.
Thank you.
Is Trixie here?
She should be any minute.
I'll go check.
I don't want Trixie to get
scared seeing me like this.
Do I look okay?
You... you look heaven-sent.
(sighs)
♪ There's a dream they sell
you when you're young... ♪
(indistinct chatter)
Just... follow my lead and don't
do anything unless I say, okay?
If that's what it takes,
then you have my word.
Dearie me, these are atrocious.
What self-respecting artist
would actually display these?
Dave Maddox isn't a real artist.
To say the least.
All this is just a front.
See, criminals like Maddox,
they use art sales to
cover up money transfers.
They could demand
any price for a piece of art,
and in return provide whatever
it is their clients really want.
Can he provide an eye bath?
I'll need one after this.
There he is.
Remember what I said.
My word is my bond.
Dave Maddox?
We need to talk.
Just one moment, all right?
No, it's urgent.
It's about your other business.
Specifically, with
Professor Jason Carlisle.
LUCIFER: Help us get
the professor's antidote,
and we'll get out of your
children's art festival.
Can you just...
give me one minute? Yeah.
I... have no idea what
you're talking about.
DAN: Don't mess with us
- right now, man, it's my wife...
- Ex-wife.
My ex-wife's life is on the line.
(chuckles) You... so you're
trying to help your ex-wife?
Something's wrong with you, buddy.
LUCIFER: Maybe not the best time
to push that particular button.
Yeah?
If she's anything like my ex,
I say let her die.
(scoffs, chuckles)
(grunts)
(growls)
Now, see, I would do this myself,
but painting hand and all that.
You are making a big mistake.
MADDOX: You're right.
(scoffs) I can just find
something to hit you with!
Duh!
Right, I'm not sure what
lead I'm following here,
but am I supposed to
let them punch me, too?
What? No.
I screwed up. Okay, Lucifer?
I let my anger get the better of me
and now Chloe's gonna pay for it.
What, so this isn't some
elaborate game of bloody possum?
Of course not!
Oh, well, in that case...
(handcuffs loosening)
Wait, are you kidding me?
You could have gotten out
of those this whole time?
Well, of course I could.
Right, catch.
Why the hell didn't you stop them
from beating the crap out of me?
Because I promised you
I wouldn't do anything
without your permission.
Oh, right. Of course.
Right.
(handcuffs loosening)
- This is gonna have to...
- LUCIFER: Take a swing
and I'll shove that so far up your ass,
you'll have splinters in your stool.
Right.
Since torture takes too
long and Dan's already wasted
so much time, why don't we speed
things along and make a deal?
You have something we want.
What would you like in return?
Wait, what?
Quickly, now. What is it you desire?
I want...
Hmm?
I-I want someone to buy my art
because they actually like it.
(sighs)
Clients only buy my paintings because
they're forced to as
part of our deal, but...
I know they just throw 'em away.
And treat 'em like trash.
An insult to trash.
All I want...
more than anything, is just...
is to be treated like a real artist.
Really? That's it?
(sighs)
Well, miracles aren't my thing,
but I'm sure we can
come to an arrangement.
(sniffles)
(sighs)
The sacrifices we make
for the greater good.
What? You're not the
one that has to look
at this monstrosity every day.
Ah.
Here you go.
What is this?
It's the antidote ingredients
I gathered for Professor Carlisle.
Well, what about the formula?
What about it?
We need to know the amounts
of each ingredient he used.
If we get it wrong, it could be lethal.
The professor kept the
formula all to himself.
He liked to brag about
how the only place it
existed was in his head.
You'd... you'd have to ask him.
Yeah, well, we can't do that.
He's dead.
Oh.
Um...
you still want the
painting though, right?
Uh...
Amenadiel told me about your detective.
I'm sorry, son.
(scoffs)
I can't even go in there.
I'd have to tell her how
monumentally screwed she is.
(laughs) Or... or lie.
And we both know I can't do that.
Well, if it's any consolation,
you of all people should know
that the man that did this
is right where he belongs:
suffering in Hell.
You're right. That... that's it.
Well, I'm glad I was
able to comfort you.
No, no, Mum, you figured it out.
How I'm gonna save the detective.
Um, I'm not sure I understand.
I'm gonna pop down to Hell and
have a chat with the professor.
What? How?
Well, it's simple. (chuckles)
- All I need to do is die.
- (Mom gasps)
The plan is simple:
you kill me, I go down to Hell,
interrogate the professor,
get the formula and
then you bring me back.
Well, come on! Who's in?
This is a terrible idea.
I absolutely forbid it.
MAZE: I hate to agree with Her Highness,
but she's right.
You'd be on your own.
We both know
I can't go down with you.
Well, I went down and
came back once before,
it wasn't a problem.
That's because Father brought you back.
MAZE: And you didn't go
through any of the doors.
Once you do, you could
be trapped... forever.
Well, that won't happen, will it?
I'm the Lord of Hell,
for crying out loud.
You were the Lord of Hell.
You've been away
quite a long time.
You can't be certain
that this will work.
(scoffs)
(chuckles, sighs)
What do you think?
I think...
that I followed about half of that.
Do you guys do this a lot?
Like, celestial planning sessions?
AMENADIEL: Oh,
apparently not. Otherwise,
we would have had a meeting
about carelessly revealing
our true nature to a human.
- Oh...
- Which...
she has apparently known about
for a while and kept from me.
Yeah, well, turnabout's fair play.
Hmm.
LINDA: Okay, wrapping my brain
around this...
Lucifer, what makes you so sure
you'd go to Hell?
In case you've missed it, doctor,
I've been banned from Heaven.
There's no where else for me to go.
And you're sure there's
no other way to get there?
I mean... (scoffs)
I mean, dying?
Well, if anyone has a better suggestion,
by all means, speak up now.
Quite frankly, I'd prefer to Uber there.
But...
look, I am doing this
with or without you.
Well, I'm sorry.
Having spent millennia
in that terrible place,
I can't be part of you going back.
Not even for a moment.
Fine.
(sighs) Amenadiel?
Are you coming?
No, Mom, I'm gonna help.
Chloe, she doesn't deserve this.
MAZE: This is the craziest plan
I've ever heard.
I'm in.
Doctor, surely you have
some sensible advice.
Um, he's the Devil.
Nothing's really been sensible
since I found that out.
I will not help you
get trapped down there.
Not for some insignificant human's life.
(footfalls receding)
LUCIFER: Okay.
Now that party pooper's gone,
let's get started, shall we?
So, um,
what's my part in all of this?
Well, you went to
medical school, correct?
Many... many, many, many years ago.
Good. So you'll be the one
bringing me back from the dead.
Okay, who wants to kill me?
(scoffs)
LUCIFER: Ah, Daniel, there
you are. Have you gathered
the ingredients for the antidote yet?
What? No, I've just been
spending time with Chloe.
Besides, those ingredients are
useless without the formula.
Well, you might want to hop on it,
because I'm about to get the formula.
What? How?
Fairly certain you don't want to know.
Well, you... You do what you have to.
Ella and I will get those ingredients.
Right.
LINDA: This is crazy.
I can't do this.
Yeah, and neither can I.
These scrubs are so boxy.
Even I can't pull 'em off.
Scratch that.
I can pull off anything.
Yes, you're right. We can do this.
We can do this, right?
We have to.
- Chloe's life depends on it.
- This is it.
This is the room directly below Chloe's.
LUCIFER: Make sure no one
moves the detective.
I'll be in the room below,
but she needs to remain
in there for this to work.
Because being close to
her makes you vulnerable.
Well, killable, in this case, but yes.
So I keep her here until you're dead?
No, no, no. The entire time.
Even after you've already been killed?
Well, who knows what happens
if I become invulnerable
when I'm already dead.
There's a good chance
the doctor won't be able to revive me.
And we don't want me
to stay dead, do we?
That was a rhetorical question.
- Right.
And you trust me with this?
Brother,
you're the most stubborn,
bullheaded person I know.
If anyone can prevent the detective
from being moved, it's you.
Luci?
What? What?
Good luck.
Don't worry, brother.
It feels like a good day to die.
DAN: Ella?
You got a package from CDC.
How many more ingredients do we need?
Well, based off the list
from that middleman dude,
we've gathered all but one:
a chemical called ZX3.
Super rare, super illegal.
How rare?
Let's put it this way:
all my legal contacts
are out of this stuff.
Wait, you have illegal contacts?
You don't? Whatever.
Some street racers secretly
add drops of ZX3 to their fuel
for a super shady advantage.
How do you know that?
I used to steal cars.
It's not fun if you don't
drive 'em really, really fast.
Anyway,
I know where some black
market ZX3 is locked up:
a chop shop in NoHo.
Problem is, I'm not sure I can
get the owner to hand it over.
And we don't have time for a warrant.
Well, desperate times...
Call for a little B&E.
- Mm-hmm.
- Let's go.
- (monitor beeping)
- Right, so one zap
of this doohickey will stop my heart?
Uh, the defibrillator wasn't
made for that, but yes.
Not what I thought I'd
be doing with my day.
I'm gonna give you 60 seconds,
then restart your
heart to bring you back.
60 seconds? I've had
orgasms that last longer.
Time moves much slower
down there. Remember?
Yes, but we only get one shot at this.
What if you yank me out
before I get the formula?
60 seconds is already cutting
it closer than I'd like.
The brain only lasts
three minutes after death.
- (sighs)
- Or so I read.
Just now. Like, on the ride over.
Why am I doing this again?
Because you care about
saving the detective's
life almost as much as I do.
Now, come on!
I also care about your life, Lucifer!
Okay, ice to slow your
brain cells from dying,
and painkillers to, well, kill the pain.
Got it covered, thanks.
LINDA: Okay, Maze,
just like I showed you.
Yeah, got it.
(exhales)
Okay. You ready?
- I can't! You do it.
- No, no, no, no.
No, the deal was you kill
him, I bring him back.
- But you're the doctor!
- And you're the demon from Hell!
Goodness sake.
- (thump, then flatline)
- Whoa!
Oh, my God.
He's dead.
He's really dead.
(echoing footsteps)
Who are you?
I'm Amenadiel.
I'm Lucifer's brother.
He, uh, asked me to watch over your mom.
Like a guardian angel?
(chuckles)
I like your necklace.
Thanks.
I, um, I like yours too.
A bad man did this to my mommy.
Why are there bad people in the world?
I really don't know.
There might be bad people in
the world, but you know what?
There's a lot more good people in it.
Really?
Yeah.
Like all the good people
helping out your mom.
Like you?
Well, I'm, uh...
I'm trying to be good.
I think you're good.
♪ ♪
(softly): Yes.
About bloody time.
(crow caws)
MAN: Help!
Help!
Hey, hey, man,
I'm tra... I think I'm stuck.
Hey, can you help me?
I think my arm's stuck.
Just take my...
What?!
Hey, man, I'm trapped!
You can't leave me here!
Hey! Help!
- Coward.
- No. Killer.
- No.
- Murderer.
- (crowd yelling indistinctly)
- WOMAN: Monster.
- Killer.
- Coward!
- No, you don't understand.
- (crowd yelling louder)
I had no choice.
Leave me alone!
- Please!
- Coward!
No!
Professor Jason Carlisle.
Remember me?
It keeps happening. Over and over.
It's like I'm in Hell!
There's no "like" about it.
What is this?
This is a torture of your own making.
Fueled by guilt.
With a little bit of
flair thrown in for fun.
Please.
I need to get out of here.
How do I get out?
Well, it's quite simple,
you can't.
- What?
- Not until you no
longer believe you deserve it.
And I have never seen anyone
pull themselves out of here.
Oh, God, no, no, no.
- No, no...
- However,
perhaps making some
amends for your misdeeds
might do the trick.
Anything. Please.
How do I make amends?
Well, before you so
rudely ended your own life,
you poisoned a detective.
Someone who I care about very much.
There's still time to save her.
So, if you give me the
formula to her antidote,
perhaps your guilt might be alleviated.
Yeah?
(panting)
Tick tock, Professor!
There.
The formula.
Does that make us good?
(soft chuckle)
You tell me.
(sighs)
I didn't think so.
No.
No, please!
No!
No! No!
Where's a resurrection
when you need one?
Could really use my
flask right about now.
(distorted piano playing)
(door creaks)
(eerie piano version of
"Killing Me Softly" playing)
(plays off-key note)
I never could play as
well as you, brother.
Uriel...
I...
I know.
It's a lot to take in, isn't it?
I don't...
(laughs)
I-I don't understand, Azrael's blade,
it should've destroyed
you, not sent you to Hell.
You don't deserve to be here, brother.
You're right, I don't.
But you do.
(gasps)
You think it's that easy to let go?
Think again, brother.
(knife unsheaths)
(Lucifer yells, Uriel grunts)
No. No, no, no, no, no,
no, what's happening?
What's happening?
I need to save the detective.
But you just can't
help yourself, can you?
(Lucifer whimpers, knife unsheaths)
You have to believe me,
I didn't want this.
And yet...
(yells)
(flatline)
60 seconds! Clear!
(thump, flatline continues)
I thought you said
this would work, Linda!
Shh! Clear!
No, no, no!
What was I thinking?
This was always a terrible idea.
You know, we are not cat burglars.
We are totally gonna get caught.
"Cat burglars"?
What are you, an old-timey desperado?
I'm just saying we're a
little out of our element.
Speak for yourself.
Yeah, I noticed.
Where'd you learn to
pick a lock like that?
My grandma.
Wow.
And what exactly are
we looking for again?
- MAN: Hey!
- (rifle cocks)
You picked the wrong place to rob.
(yells) I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I can't make it stop.
"It?"
As if you had no part in it.
I don't! I didn't.
I-I don't want this!
Look at you.
So pitiful.
Stuck in the very Hell you once ruled.
Trapped by your own guilt.
And while we're pointing
out how lame you are,
you didn't even follow up
on that thing I told you.
What I whispered in
your ear before I died.
What?
"The peace is here"?
The peace is here.
I... I thought that was just nonsense.
The... the final ramblings
of a dying brain. I...
Unless you're saying you found
peace in that moment, brother.
Oh, Luci, Luci, Luci.
You should know better than that.
I'm all about patterns,
predicting the future.
My last words were a clue.
A clue? A clue to what?
Well, you're the one who has
to figure that out, aren't you?
After all,
I'm just in your head.
I'm just a manifestation of
your own guilty conscience.
Speaking of... (Lucifer
whimpers, knife unsheaths)
(yells)
- Ouch.
- (panting)
No. (panting)
I hope you didn't leave any
- unfinished business up on Earth...
- What?
...'cause you're never
getting out of here.
(monitor alarm beeping rapidly)
What's happening?
Doctor just paged us. She's in V-tach.
I don't know.
- Let's go wait outside, okay?
- Crash cart's on its way.
It's okay, I'm gonna stay with your mom.
Go with the nurse.
(nurses talking indistinctly)
DOCTOR: Go ahead and
turn her on her side.
Crash cart standing by.
NURSE 2: She's seizing.
MAZE: This isn't right.
Something's wrong in Hell.
What?
He's stuck.
Trapped in one of those cells.
That's why we can't revive him.
Okay, so then what do we
have to do to bust him out?
Someone needs to go down
there and pull him out.
I'd go, but I can't.
Why not?
Demons don't have a soul.
If I die,
I just... die.
Okay, that's definitely
a discussion topic
for another time, but right
now, every second counts.
And I can't believe
I'm saying this, but...
- what if I go?
- What?
You? What makes you think
you'd go to Hell and not Heaven?
There are things you
don't know about me.
- No. No way.
- But Maze...
MOM: Send me.
MAZE: Well.
Look who decided to show up.
I'll go down and get him.
You said you'd never go back.
Yes, I have a paralyzing
fear of the place.
But I would face a thousand
Hells to save my son.
Ever since I escaped,
Hell's been constantly
trying to pull me back.
It's only my resistance that allows me
to fight its pull.
So, I just...
won't resist.
So, how do we do this?
It appears
that we need to attach
these little wires
to the skin... (grunts)
(body thuds)
Maze!
Oops.
♪ ♪
NURSE: She's still in V-tach.
- DOCTOR: Midazolam, four milligrams.
- Yes, Doctor.
(monitor alarm beeping rapidly)
DOCTOR: Thanks.
Get it in that line.
NURSE: I got the IV.
- (monitor beeping stabilizes)
- There we go.
Okay.
We need to move her to CT.
I'll call them.
Sir. You need to move.
I can't let her leave.
We're trying to save her life.
So am I.
Security.
Security!
DAN: I can explain.
Just... lower the weapon.
MAN: Yeah. You better explain.
Before I shoot you for
busting into my place...
Ricardo! Tranquilo, okay?
No seas estúpido.
Lower the gun.
W-What...
Ella?
What are you doing here?
You know this guy?
Only since birth.
Dan, meet Ricardo, my idiot brother.
- I'm not an idiot.
- ELLA: Sorry.
Thieving, cowardly, neglectful idiot.
- This is your brother?
- Yep.
Then why didn't you
just ask him for the ZX3?
'Cause after I moved out here
to keep an eye on him,
he totally ghosted me!
I get it. Okay?
You want to keep your
law enforcement sis away
from your shady shenanigans.
Watch. He's gonna try and
say he doesn't have any ZX3.
I don't have any ZX3.
We're not here to bust you.
DAN: Yeah, man. We're the ones
- who are breaking and entering.
- Exactly.
- Totes illegal.
- Come on, Ella.
You know better. All right?
I can't take any chances.
Ricky.
The ZX3's for a friend.
Without it, she's gonna die.
And I really don't want her to die.
Follow me.
I hate you.
I love you, too.
(Uriel grunts, Lucifer crying)
I-I know. I know.
Hurts you more than it does me.
Please, please, forgive me, brother.
I had no choice.
Do you really believe that?
No.
(yells)
Lucifer!
Mum?
(panting)
What are you doing here?
I'm your rescue party of one.
You don't belong down here.
Not anymore.
But look.
Look what I've done.
Lucifer, this Uriel isn't real.
I wish he was.
I so badly want to see my son again.
But he's just a part of your Hell.
(yells)
- (screams)
- MOM: No.
You were... you were
just trying to save us.
This isn't your fault.
It's mine.
I am to blame for all of this.
Ever since...
ever since I returned, I've been...
I've been manipulating you.
Stoking your anger against
your Father in hopes
of using you against Him.
But...
...but I've just made things worse.
I pushed you and that human closer,
knowing it would crush you
when you learned the truth.
And now look at us.
Stuck in this prison
while Chloe is dying.
Chloe.
No. I killed Uriel because
I had to. To save you.
To save the detective.
And I need to save her now.
Mum. Mum? We need to leave.
Mum?
Why would we leave?
Uriel is right here.
We can stay.
Be a happy family.
I've missed you so much, Mother.
Mum?
Mum.
Mum!
Come on. You pulled me out of my guilt,
there's no time to get
stuck in yours. Come on.
- Come on!
- Please, don't abandon me.
- Not again. Please.
- Mum. Mum.
MOM: No...
No. Lucifer...
No, please.
- Shh.
- Uriel!
My sweet boy!
- LUCIFER: He's not real.
- MOM: Lucifer!
My sweet boy.
♪ Come here ♪
♪ Approach ♪
♪ Appear ♪
♪ Daddy, I'm alone ♪
♪ 'Cause this house
don't feel like home ♪
♪ If you love me, don't let go ♪
(flatline tone sounding, thump)
(flatline continues)
♪ No ♪
♪ If you love me ♪
♪ Don't let go ♪
♪ Hold ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Hold on to me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a little unsteady ♪
(thump)
- (gasps)
- ♪ Hold ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Hold on to me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a little unsteady ♪
♪ A little unsteady ♪
♪ Mother ♪
♪ I know that you're tired ♪
♪ Of being alone ♪
♪ Dad, I know you're trying ♪
♪ To fight when you feel like flying ♪
♪ But if you love me, don't let go ♪
♪ Hold ♪
♪ Hold on ♪
♪ Hold on to me ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm a little unsteady. ♪
(inhales, exhales)
Well.
Look who's back.
You didn't die after all.
That makes one of us.
I heard you saved me.
Well...
much as I'd like to take all the credit,
this one was a... a team effort.
You know, this whole
poisoning thing has just...
...really put a pause on everything
that's been going on
with you and I, so...
should we just pick
up where we left off?
I think, right now,
you just need to focus
on feeling better, Detective.
Would you have someone bring Trixie in?
Yes. Yes, of course.
And we'll talk.
We'll talk later, yeah?
(door opens)
(sighs)
MOM: How is the detective?
She'll be fine.
And...
what about the two of you?
(laughs)
Well, it was never real, was it?
Lucifer, I am so sorry.
Father brought her into existence
- just to put her in my path.
- Yes.
The whole thing's been a sham, Mum.
Long con.
And I fell for it.
You can't blame yourself.
This is all His doing. And
He should be punished for it.
Oh, make no mistake, I plan on that.
I mean, how can I
trust anything, anyone,
now that I know He
might be behind it all?
Well, you can trust me.
Can I, Mum?
- Yeah.
- You're as bad as He is.
Worse, maybe.
At least He doesn't pretend to love me.
Lucifer.
I do love you.
(laughs)
I went back to Hell for you.
I helped save the detective, for you.
Doesn't that count for anything?
It's too little too late, Mother.
You set out to break my heart. Well...
mission accomplished.
- Lucifer...
- No.
No more manipulations.
This feud that you have
with Father, I refuse
to be caught in the middle any longer.
I am tired of being a pawn.
So, no more.
I'm done.
Lucifer.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ When your heart is a stranger ♪
♪ And you know you
didn't treat it right ♪
CHLOE: Hey.
It's me again.
Voicemail 337.
(laughs)
Obnoxious, right? But, um...
It's just that you... you
haven't been picking up,
or returning my calls, so...
uh, I'm on my way over.
So, hide the strippers.
Um...
Yeah, um....
I just hope you're okay.
♪ Giving it up ♪
Okay.
Bye.
♪ Now you're just turning the knife ♪
♪ Giving it up ♪
♪ Now you're just rolling the dice ♪
Lucifer?
Are you here?
♪ Counting on doing it right ♪
♪ Giving it up ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
Lucifer?
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh. ♪
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net