Previously on Lucifer...
AMENADIEL: Those wings
out there in the human world,
Luci, they're too
powerful. A piece of divinity.
MAZE: You know exactly
what's causing your vulnerability.
Chloe Decker is the one I
should be throwing knives at.
LUCIFER: Demon daggers
forged in Hell don't
count. We all know those prick.
What do you want from me, Malcolm?
You're gonna go into Evidence
and borrow something for me.
What's that?
This is my Pentecostal coin.
I suppose you could use
it to get out of Hell.
It's all yours if you don't shoot me.
AMENADIEL: You sent your
demon to kill me.
(grunting)
If only you'd done what was asked
of you, I'd still be home!
(grunts)
Enough! You both used me. Here.
(clang)
Kill each other.
Evil is here. Evil is here.
DAN: "Morningstar." Whoa.
Somebody could be
doing this on his behalf,
or maybe he's
involved in a different way.
LUCIFER: You did this.
You killed those people.
- I did this for you. Aren't you happy?
- Why would I be happy?
CHLOE: The last place the
preacher was seen was near LUX.
- Put your hands up.
- (scoffs)
Lucifer
Morningstar, you're under arrest.
Come on, Detective.
You can't seriously believe I killed
that pathetic malcontent.
It doesn't matter what I believe.
That's all that matters, Detective.
Put your hands in the
air and surrender yourself.
(laughing)
This isn't funny, Lucifer.
Isn't it?
(laughs) I think
this is the grandest joke that
I've heard in all my time.
(laughs) The best part is it's on me!
(laughing)
Come peacefully.
We'll go to the station...
No.
We won't.
(sighs) What are you doing?
I'm accepting my role in all of this.
All of humanity's sins are
the Devil's fault, right?
I mean, I thought you knew
different, but I was wrong.
You're just like all the others.
So,
why not add one more murder to the pile?
That's not what this is, Lucifer.
Come on. What are you waiting for?
You wanted your bad
guy. Well, here he is,
gift-wrapped just for you!
Don't take another step.
You!
Newbie.
Come on. Riddle me with bullets,
so you can go home, drink
an ice-cold beer,
and feel better about yourselves!
Don't shoot him. He's unarmed.
Oh, you don't know
that. Maybe I have a gun.
Hands in the air!
Do it!
Don't!
(panting)
(wind blowing)
OFFICER: What just happened?
(sighs)
Search the area.
He can't have gotten far.
(thunder rumbling)
(panting)
Can we not tell anyone
you just carried me in
your arms like a baby?
What were you trying to
accomplish in there?
Uh, a good death?
Or at least a nice and messy one.
But then you had to come and
ruin everything, like always.
(groans)
Why'd you swoop in and stop it?
Wouldn't let someone else send
me to Hell, is that it?
Well, guess what,
brother, you don't need to kill me,
because I'm done here.
I've had my fun on Earth, and...
(sighs)
there's no reason for
me to stay anymore.
You win.
I'll go willingly.
Please, just...
take me back to Hell.
No.
(sighs)
(camera shutter clicking)
Hey. What happened to Lucifer?
You didn't hear?
What happened to him?
He disappeared. He's on the run.
OFFICER: Ow.
Let me see that.
Have you ever seen a knife like this?
Yeah. Uh, I'll take it to the station.
Careful. It's crazy sharp.
Great.
Hey.
I need to talk to you.
I know this is gonna sound crazy,
especially after what just happened,
but I think Lucifer is innocent.
Chloe, Lucifer got into
a fight with the deceased
just a couple hours ago. We both saw it.
I know. Just hear me out.
Okay? Just pretend you
don't know Lucifer.
- I already like it.
- Our suspect
is a club owner who likes to
tell people he's the Devil.
You're not really selling his innocence.
He's a man who embraces
desire, lives by his passion.
Now think about the
body. The guy was executed,
single bullet to the head.
There's no passion behind this.
- This isn't him.
- Then it's a frame job.
Who would want to set him up?
- I don't know.
- OFFICER 2: Detective,
we may have found the murder weapon.
Okay. Test it for prints and DNA.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thanks.
Lucifer's prints are
gonna be on that gun.
- You don't know that.
- I do.
And I also know you're right.
Lucifer's innocent.
What?
Chloe, we have to talk.
Somewhere else.
You don't want to take me back to Hell?
The one bloody thing you've
wanted this entire time.
(chuckles) Did I punch you
in the head too hard?
Maze was right, Luci.
We used her.
And Malcolm. People have died
because of us.
Because of you, you mean.
Yes. Because of me.
Right.
Brother, somehow I lost
sight of the bigger picture,
of the cost of my actions,
and just how truly selfish they were.
But, Luci, my eyes are wide open now,
and I need to make this right.
Do you know, I think this
side of you's actually scarier
than the angry one.
I need to find Malcolm,
and I need to send him back to Hell.
Will you help me, brother?
(sighs)
One last bit of
punishment on the way out.
(thunder rumbles)
It sounds like fun to me.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
Ah, there's nothing like a
fresh shirt after a rainy rooftop.
What is that smell?
(groans) Tropical musk candles.
Gosh, the sacrifices you
made pretending to be a therapist.
Yeah, I like that scent.
- Of course you do.
- Okay,
can we please just focus?
Now, what's your plan to find Malcolm?
My plan?
- Yeah.
- Well, I thought you were
the expert at plotting murder.
Or not so expert, considering
I'm still alive.
Which is why I brought us here,
so that we could come up with a plan.
Right. Well, it sounds
more like you want me
to do all the heavy
lifting. So how's this? Step one,
travel back in time and
not make such a mess of things.
You know, I'm suddenly
reminded of why I wanted you dead
in the first place.
Luci, what is your problem?
Oh, good question,
Doctor. Well, you see,
the thing is that my
brother has been trying to kill me
and now he wants to work with me
but we can't seem to get along,
mainly because he's an egotistical twit.
Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry,
Dr. Canaan. I didn't
realize that you were in session
with a... Lucifer?
(scoffing) Oh.
I can't believe this.
You're stealing my patient.
Uh, not exactly.
Actually, you may be just what
we need, my dear doctor.
I deserve that.
You lied to me.
I don't even know you.
You shot a man in cold blood.
I shot Malcolm to protect you.
Everything I saw at
Palmetto, it was all true!
You let them think I was crazy.
- I never intended...
- You let me think I was crazy.
I'm sorry.
You don't get to be sorry.
If I could take it all back, I would.
You can't take it back!
I know.
But you can make this right.
How?
Prove Lucifer is innocent.
Where are you going?
Lucifer thinks I abandoned him.
I need to find him.
LINDA: So you're-you're brothers?
Unfortunately.
LUCIFER: And we're having a terrible
time working together.
But because you've been so
helpful with me, Linda,
hopefully you can help fix our problems.
Listen, I know this must be a shock...
Are you even a real doctor?
(laughing) No, of course he isn't.
Gosh, if he had any
clue about human nature,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Oh. You dare criticize me?
Luci, you're arrogant,
you're selfish, all you do is
- think with your penis...
- Oh.
LUCIFER: Oh. Which, of
course, you would never do, would you?
How's Maze, by the way?
Dr. Martin, will you please
tell him to shut up
and just listen to reason?
Oh, if by reason, you
mean a deceptive load
- of bull...
- Enough!
You lied to me about being a doctor
so you could manipulate Lucifer,
who is actually
your brother.
Somehow.
Do you realize
the ethical position you've put me in?
(chuckles)
And you, let me guess,
you were gonna make a sexual joke
about putting me in a position.
That's true, yeah.
Because everything's a joke to you.
And yet, for some
reason, I take you seriously,
even when you insist on
clinging to these ridiculous metaphors...
Heaven, Hell, angels, devils.
- Actually, they're not...
- Trust me,
you don't want to pick that fight.
You claimed you came to L.A.
to reinvent yourself, yet every time
I think you come upon a
moment of realization,
you go the exact
wrong direction with it.
I did... Ho-Hold on. You're
right. I did come to L.A.
to start a new life, didn't I?
And now Malcolm's on the run.
He's gonna need to
start a new life, too.
- No, see, you're doing it again.
- LUCIFER: New I.D.,
bank account, passport.
I know just the person to go to.
Oh.
Damn, you're good.
- Yep.
- (door shuts)
(Chloe clears throat)
Where's Lucifer?
Even if I knew, I wouldn't tell you.
You've never liked me.
Why?
Because every day was a party.
Every sin, every desire L.A. offered,
we took part.
And then he met you.
So you think it's my
fault that the party's over?
That and the fact that
you're hunting him down like a dog.
I don't think he killed the preacher.
I need you to help me find
him before another cop does.
So where would he go?
- You know him better than anyone.
- These days
it seems you know him better than I do.
So where do you think he's going?
To get punishment.
Which means he's going after Malcolm.
Then maybe he hasn't
changed that much after all.
If he gets to Malcolm first,
he really will go down for murder.
You can't come with me.
You said you needed my
help finding him, right?
I don't see anybody else backing you up.
Byron was a nice guy, a handy guy.
He fixed my toaster once.
Not a BLT goes by I
don't think of Byron.
LUCIFER: Excuse me!
Yeah, sorry to
interrupt the riveting eulogy,
but I'm here to see
the funeral director.
Hello, Neil. Remember me?
In a bit of a rush,
unfortunately.
Whereas this poor chap, well,
he's not going anywhere, is he?
Sir, please wait until
after we're finished.
This is disrespectful.
Uh, no, this is disrespectful.
I mean, this whole
show... who's it for, really?
Eh? Not him.
He's not hearing any of this.
Would you back me up, please, bro?
He is right.
See? Trust me, he should know.
No, it's for you, isn't it?
It's a selfish way
for you to all feel better about
yourselves about how much
you ignored this poor sod in life.
Oh, did you choose this suit?
Mr. Morningstar, this way.
Oh, you do remember me?
Feel free to carry on.
You have no right disrupting
this funeral.
- This is my business.
- Yes.
Your least profitable one.
Your main source of income
is creating new identities,
which is why I came to
you five years ago to get
my proper papers and all that.
And I did great work
for you, Mr. Morningstar.
- So why are you doing this?
- Well, if I know you're the best,
then Malcolm Graham does, as well.
(sighs) The cop.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, he needed it to be done fast,
but said he'd need time to
get his hands on the 100K.
Where would a homicide
detective get that kind of money quickly?
Mm, look at you, Sherlock.
(sighs) He mentioned an old associate.
Tommy, I think.
Great. We'll do a search
for every "Tommy" in Los Angeles.
What's another thousand years?
No, no, no, no. An old
associate of Malcolm's, you say?
I think I might know just
the person who can help us.
Rhymes with "douche."
Thanks, Neil.
I wish I had my knives.
You're not gonna need 'em.
I never need them.
LAPD! Malcolm, if...
Oh.
Hello?
Anyone here?
(scoffs)
Looks like Malcolm likes to shop.
You cops must make a lot of money.
You hiring?
We're not, and we don't.
I have no idea how he
can afford all this stuff.
Well, if you don't make good
money, why do you do this job?
'Cause I get to shoot people,
which is something you
should keep in mind.
(laughs) No really. Why?
'Cause I hate it when people
get away with things they shouldn't.
And you like to shoot people.
Yeah.
Huh.
And to think I almost killed
you in your sleep that one time.
Wait. What?
(door creaks open)
(gun clicking)
(gunshot)
(panting)
Oh, now I know why he
likes working with you.
Malcolm, it's the police!
Stop firing and put the gun down!
WOMAN: He's not with you?
Please tell me he's not with you.
Sorry. I thought you were my husband.
Mel, why were you shooting at Malcolm?
Ever since he almost died, he...
he's been different, he's been strange.
I can't describe it.
He has a newfound appetite.
An insatiable hunger
he just can't seem to fill.
How do you know?
I've seen it before.
Where?
Right. I forgot who I was talking to.
It only gets worse.
It can't get worse!
He spent all our money.
And when I saw him today, he...
Wait. When did he come by today?
You just missed him.
He was frantic. He was
looking for money, and he was angry.
He was so angry.
And he had this look in his
eye, and he said things like...
Do you have any idea where
he might have gone?
(scoffs)
He said he was gonna go get a beer.
- (phone buzzing)
- Okay.
Thanks. Excuse me.
Malcolm's good, Chloe.
I can't find any
evidence tying him to the murders.
How's it going on your end?
Malcolm's not home. Mel
said he went out for a beer.
Does that make any sense to you?
No. When I saw him, he was scared.
I think he knows Lucifer's
gonna come after him.
He looked like a guy
getting ready to run.
Yeah, well, he doesn't
have the money to get far.
Yeah, but he's the kind of
guy who'd know how to find it.
Oh, maybe there's a
bar that owes him money.
Yeah, or one that he could
rob for some extra cash.
I'll look into it.
(door squeaks open and shut)
Don't move, or wobbly head gets it.
How did you get in here?
There's a manhunt for you.
And this is the last
place you'd look, isn't it?
I thought it was quite clever.
Ooh.
You need to get the hell out of here.
Oh, we're gonna need some
information first.
- Who are you?
- LUCIFER: Not this again.
He's my brother. I
know, shocking, isn't it?
He's much less handsome than I am.
AMENADIEL: We're
looking for Malcolm, Detective.
Now, we've been told that he's
seeing an associate named Tommy?
There are a lot of Tommys in...
A beer. Of course.
We'd very much like to
know what you just realized.
Too bad. I'm not telling you.
(laughs) But you want
to, though, don't you?
No, I don't.
Oh, you're a complicated
one. That is a surprise.
So, come on, what do you
want to do, Daniel? Hmm?
I...
I want to redeem myself.
Oh. And taking down
Malcolm would do that, wouldn't it?
So where is he?
Come on, you can tell us.
Like you said, we're
surrounded by police.
There's an old brewery on Third.
Mm-hmm.
A drug dealer named Tommy Campolongo
works out of there.
Ah. Not that complicated after all.
So you two will stay in
a holding cell while I...
(whooshing)
Okay. Tommy Campolongo.
That makes sense, that
he'd have cash on him.
But he's not gonna hand it over nicely.
I'm leaving the precinct now.
Okay, meet me there with
backup. I'm not far.
Chloe, don't go...
Damn it.
MAN: You like that?
(laughing)
And to think, after all this time,
I just thought you were dead.
What can I say?
It's hard to keep a good man down.
- Mm-hmm.
- And now
I'm ready to get the
old band back together.
You have some product you can move?
We've got some seizures
just sitting there in evidence.
Could actually get you a
supply today if you've got cash.
I always have cash, Malcolm.
You know that.
That I do, Tommy.
That I do.
How much you thinking?
How much you got?
(laughing)
(imitating laughter)
(clattering)
What's going on up there?
This ain't me.
What you waiting for?!
But hey.
Gift horse and all that... am I right?
Why don't you go ahead, open
up that safe, my man?
Oh...
hello there.
If you miscreants don't mind,
we're looking for Malcolm Graham.
Hand him over, and we
all can be on our way
without too much fuss.
You two made a huge
mistake walking in here.
(guns clicking)
(stammers)
What do you say we skip the
time-slowing shenanigans, hmm?
What about your mortality situation?
Well, it's kind of a non-sitch
when the detective's not around.
I'll explain later, but for now,
we'll just, you know, enjoy the moment.
(chuckles) After you.
Lovely.
Right, I should warn you...
(grunts)
(sighs) This is hardly a fair fight.
d Hey, hey... d
(gunshots)
d Hey, hey now d
(shouts)
d Hey, hey, there's a fire
and it's running, coming in here d
(grunting)
d Hey, hey now, hey, hey now d
d Hey, hey d
d Hey, hey now... d
Sorry, bro. Genuine mistake.
d Yeah, hey, hey
now, burning out of luck d
d Gonna wear the crown d
d Hey, hey now, things
are burning up... d
(gun clicks)
Oh, do you need some help with that?
d Things are burning up... d
(screams)
d Oh, oh, oh. d
(both laugh)
And to think, we
wasted all that millennia
fighting each other, right?
We still need to find Malcolm.
Absolutely.
You know, if we split
up, we'll cover more ground.
Okay, but no hogging all the fun
if you find him first... deal?
Deal.
(man groaning)
Oh!
(grunts)
d d
(groaning)
Wow. I mean,
wow. I could tell it
was something special,
but I had no idea that was gonna work.
(moaning)
But you never know until you try.
(groaning)
Got to say,
you don't look so scary now, Amenadude.
Oi!
What part of "no
hogging" don't you understand?
(groans, panting)
(sighs) Bloody hell!
There you go, spoiling
my fun again.
Leave me, and go get him.
You know how much I hate
being in anyone's debt.
I figure if I save you
now, that makes us even, right?
Besides, it's...
it's just a flesh wound.
Hardly can see what
you're whining about.
(panting)
What happened?
He was struck with a
blade not of this world, Maze.
One of mine.
Yes.
I'll handle this.
How?
Find him.
With pleasure.
(clattering)
Malcolm, freeze!
Stop!
(gunshots)
(panting)
(gun clicks)
Don't move.
Easy, Detective.
You're a hard man to find.
Look, I know you think I'm a bad guy,
but I'm simply trying to
catch our dear friend Malcolm
so I can tear his arms and legs off.
- This has nothing to do with you.
- You know I can't let you do that.
(sighs) You don't know what he's done.
You'd never believe me anyway.
But all you need to know is
that he's here to get money
and then he's gonna disappear. For good.
You mean this money?
I'm not here to arrest you, Lucifer.
I know you're innocent.
I always have.
So let's catch this bastard together
and put an end to all this.
Ah. Look at us,
reunited, and it feels so good.
Malcolm won't get far without
his getaway cash.
Where's Maze?
She's taking care
of something important.
Oh, of course your ninja
bartender is off on a secret mission.
Why, Detective, are you pining
- for some good cop/demon copop action?
- No.
I just want to clear
your name and find Malcolm.
No, no, no, no, no.
Who cares about the Devil's rap sheet?
Why don't we just skip that part
and go straight to the main course?
Because it's incredibly impulsive
and shortsighted.
Have you noticed that's my jam?
If we fix your reputation,
we'll preserve everything we've done.
You want to keep working with me.
- And to do that, you need to trust me.
- (door opens)
- (sighs)
- (indistinct police transmission)
- Okay. Well.
- Right. Very well, Detective.
I'm in your hands. But how you intend
to prove my innocence is beyond me.
Put your hands down.
We found the evidence we need.
LUCIFER: He did?
Can I rethink my surrender?
What'd you find?
It's better if I show you.
(indistinct chatter)
d d
(moans)
(groans) Enough,
Mazikeen.
I've made my peace with death,
whether I go to Heaven or Hell.
I know exactly where you're going.
Nowhere. You're staying right here.
Now shut up and let me help you.
(gasps) There's nothing
that you can do.
It would take something
divine to heal me.
d I'm Hollywood... d
You took that from Lucifer?
I kept it a secret.
I thought I could use
it to get us back home.
And you'd give that to me?
Believe me,
I don't understand this either.
d We'll always be together d
d Forever, forever d
d Forever d
d Forever. d
(sighs) Why do I feel like
I'm walking death row?
Should I order my final
meal now to save time?
Dan says he has it handled.
You do, right?
I do.
I'm here to turn myself in.
What are you doing?
I removed a firearm
from Evidence lockup,
and I gave it to
Detective Malcolm Graham.
I believe Detective Graham
then used that weapon to
shoot and kill Jacob Williams,
the crime that...
Mr. Morningstar is suspected of.
Well,
Detective Espinoza,
I...
didn't know you had the stones.
No more Detective Douche?
Well, not today, at least.
Let's go.
Dan...
(phone buzzing)
(sighs)
I need to take this.
Hey, honey. Everything okay?
MALCOLM: Hello, Decker.
Malcolm?
How's the precinct?
I still have a few
buddies at the stations.
Oh, and I made a new friend today, too.
Pulled her out of a boring
class for some bonding time.
Here, say hi.
Hi, Mommy.
Hey, Trixie.
Are you okay, honey?
Mommy's here.
Uh, that's enough of that.
(sighs) What do you want, Malcolm?
Aw. Poor Chloe Decker.
Did someone take something from you,
something valuable?
Hurts, don't it?
You want your money.
Bull's-eye.
Now, don't even think about talking
to the cops. Remember,
- you don't know who's with me.
- Okay.
And keep Lucifer out of this.
Just you...
or she dies.
d d
d You're an unusual suspect
now and may be right d
d The kind all men cannot recollect
or forget at night d
d You're the rough
detective with the smokey eye d
d Where the person you
are after is the other guy... d
Hey. Um, I need the
duffel bag we seized today.
Where is it? (clears throat)
We were just about to
take it to Evidence.
Okay. I need to examine it.
Sure.
LUCIFER: Ah,
there you are.
Is everything all right, Detective?
Yeah.
Of course.
I'll be right back.
Right.
d Well, I'm a rough
detective on a glory ride d
d You keep going
faster so I slow down d
d You hear me laughing d
- d In the background d
- (siren whooping)
(with American accent) Detective Decker,
step away from your vehicle.
Put your hands in the air
and walk towards me peacefully.
If you do not...
I repeat... if you do not,
we will have no choice but to shoot you
with our new bazooka.
We've actually been waiting months
and months to use it, so,
on second thought, please, speed away.
What are you doing?
Well, I could ask you the s...
(feedback squeals)
(normally) I could
ask you the same thing.
You going somewhere without me, hmm?
Right after all this
talk about trusting you,
you're immediately keeping secrets?
I don't have time to
explain to you. Something came up.
Something that obviously requires
quite a bit of cash.
I didn't know you had
it in you, Detective.
- It isn't for me.
- Oh, you're gonna make
it rain at the local strip clubs then?
- Lucifer...
- Or perhaps that phone call earlier
wasn't as innocuous as
you made it out to be.
Fine. You leave me no choice.
Malcolm has Trixie.
Oh.
If I get him his
money, he'll let her go.
Right. Because if
Malcolm's established anything,
it's his trustworthiness.
What choice do I have?
To ride shotgun with
the Devil, for starters.
If Malcolm sees you,
he'll kill her. I'm sorry,
but I can't risk
it... her life's at stake.
Right. So you're just gonna get
both of you killed then, are you?
He needs this money to leave town.
I won't give it to him until she's safe.
And what about your safety?
Trixie is all that matters.
- Detective, I...
- I don't have
time to argue with you, Lucifer.
I realize how bad this can
go, but I don't have a choice.
This is my daughter.
Promise me you'll let me go alone.
Fine.
You have my word.
(sighs)
Don't look so sad.
Your mommy's coming to pick you up.
Good. I don't like you.
What's not to like?
(grunts)
- Trixie.
- All right, easy, Decker.
Easy.
Mommy, can we go home now?
Yes, Monkey. (sniffles) We can.
Glad to see you came alone.
Now toss the gun.
(panting)
Now the other one.
There. You happy?
Yeah, once I get my money, sure.
So, where is it?
Not without Trixie.
- Oh, come on, Decker...
- Malcolm, that's the deal.
Go on.
Hi.
Okay, listen to me.
We're gonna play a game, all right?
I need you to hide until
I can come find you.
Mommy, I don't want to play a game.
- I know you don't, baby.
- (imitates gunshot)
But I need you to go hide
really, really well, okay?
Go.
(chuckles) Kids, huh?
(sighs, coughs)
It's there. It's-it's all there.
It's in the bag.
Yeah. I believe you.
You don't need to do this, Malcolm.
I know, but I was
gonna shoot you at Palmetto,
and now I feel like I've
been given a second chance here,
so I'm sure as hell not gonna waste it.
LUCIFER: Is this really what you did
with your second chance?
Deary me, Malcolm. Pathetic.
Hey, Lucifer.
Hey, buddy. Long time no frame.
Though that didn't stick
too well, did it?
Guess I need to find a
more permanent solution.
Give me the gun, Malcolm.
Why? Not afraid of you.
All you're doing is
getting yourself killed.
And for what?
To buy your precious detective
some more time?
No.
No, I want to ask you a question.
Oh. (chuckles softly)
What do you desire, Malcolm?
(whispering): Lucifer,
what are you doing?
What do you yearn for in that...
rotten soul of yours?
I...
You've been given a
second chance, Malcolm.
Is killing Detective Decker
really what you want to do with it?
I don't.
No, of course you don't.
You want to live, don't you?
I do.
More than almost anything.
Almost?
(gunshot)
(gasping)
There's one more thing.
You feel that?
That's what it's like to die, my man.
I know, 'cause I've done it.
And what I want, more than anything...
is for you to feel that pain.
To go through what I did.
Because we both know
where you're going to.
Bet you never expected
to miss this thing so soon.
Yeah.
Don't worry.
You won't be going alone.
I'll be sending Decker
along right behind you.
Oh, Chloe...
Oh, Decker...
(coughing)
Here, Chloe, Chloe, Chloe.
LUCIFER: I don't know if this is all
part of the plan.
Or if You can even hear me.
But if You're up there...
Dad...
(laughs)
I need a favor.
(Lucifer gasping)
I'll be the son.
You always wanted me to be.
(Lucifer choking)
I'll do as You ask. (heartbeat
echoing slowly)
Go where You want me to.
I...
In exchange,
all I ask is...
is that you protect Chloe.
(heartbeat stops)
(ethereal choral music plays)
(echoing) Home, sweet home.
d d
That can't be right.
(clinking)
It's open.
(low rumbling)
This isn't possible.
(gasps)
(panting)
(chuckles)
Hello, Malkie.
It doesn't matter.
(snorting, choking)
I've got your coin.
Oh.
I'll be back.
You're looking for this?
How...?
I know a guy.
Apparently, He wants me back here.
(sighs)
Sorry, pal.
One use only.
CHLOE: Trixie!
Come out, honey!
Mommy, is it over?
Yeah, baby, it's over. Come here.
Hi.
Oh, I'm so happy you're okay.
Excuse me if I don't join the group hug.
(whispering) I thought he killed you.
Oh, he did.
Yes.
I got better.
Hmm.
You promised you'd let me go alone.
True.
But I didn't say
anything about following.
What's wrong?
(sighs)
Isn't it past her bedtime?
Hmm?
(footsteps approaching)
(Lucifer sighs)
(broken glass clinking)
LUCIFER: Ah!
Sleeping on the job?
Luci, we still have to find Malcolm...
Malcolm, yes.
That's dealt with. It's
old news, really.
(grunts)
(sighs)
Where's Maze?
Well, I was gonna ask
you the same question.
Perhaps your snoring drove her away.
(chuckles)
(sighs)
I spoke to Dad.
Excuse me?
Yeah. I offered Him my
services in exchange f...
Well, that doesn't really matter.
He accepted.
He replied to you.
Mmm.
Well, not in words.
But His message was clear.
And what does Father want?
Someone's escaped from Hell.
Must've seen a window of opportunity
whilst you were incapacitated.
I think He wants me to bring
our jailbird back.
That's it?
Well, it shouldn't be too hard
to track down a single errant soul.
(chuckles)
(fingernails clinking glass)
You're afraid.
Mmm.
Damn right I am.
Right, but you're never afraid.
Who could possibly scare you, brother?
Lucifer...
Who escaped Hell?
Mum.
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- www.Addic7ed.com -
www.tvsubtitles.net