- Previously on Lucifer...
- Hey, Lieutenant,
are you going somewhere?
I put in for a transfer.
Maybe you don't have to go.
As a thank you for watching Trixie,
maybe we can go grab
that coffee sometime.
Dinner would be more romantic.
Did you know that Linda
and Amenadiel are a thing?
So our old flames are having a fling.
I don't care, why should you?
Unless you're still hot for angel.
No!
You know, for an immortal,
you really do bleed a lot, don't you?
I'm still human. I still feel
all the pain that comes with death.
It's just the wounds heal.
Do your thing. Ask me.
Kane.
What is it that you desire?
To die.
I will find a way to
end your infinite misery
if it's the last thing I do.
Lucifer?
Lucifer!
Hello, Lucifer?
If it were that easy to kill me,
I would have been dead a long time ago.
Very well.
Right, have you tried...
- grenade down the throat?
- Yes.
- Acid bath?
- Mm-hmm.
- Devoured by wolves?
- Yes.
- Dropped into helicopter blades?
- Mm-hmm.
I've been trying to kill myself
since the Bronze Age.
I have tried
everything.
Even jumped into a volcano once.
What, you survived molten lava?
Yeah, it was a rough six months.
Just, whatever I do, I just...
regrow.
Huh, like a blue-eyed,
square-jawed tapeworm.
So if I cut you exactly in
half, would there be two Pierces?
No. Only one side would heal.
You see, I call it the, the
"master molecule" theory.
Yes, yes, Wolverine rules. I get it.
But...
there must be some method that works.
Lucifer, why do you
care so much about this?
Because my Father laid a
curse on you to live forever,
so killing you would be an epic
loogie in the old man's eye.
Well, you are the Devil.
You must have something shockingly evil
up your sleeve.
Mm, you mean, uh...
- something like this?
- Aah!
Ouch!
Thanks.
You're most welcome.
'Cause that little bad boy was
forged in the bowels of Hell.
Oh, yes, demon steel.
Can kill even me, so...
time to say good-bye
to Hollywood, Pierce.
Good-bye, Lucifer.
No, I-I don't understand.
How does this not work?
I should have known
that you wouldn't be
able to figure this out.
Well, I mean, the good news is
we've got all the time
in the world to do so.
For me, that's a bad thing.
Hey, Dan.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
I feel like I'm having déjÃ
vu. This street seems so familiar.
Yeah, well, it should.
We took a look at that house
right there on the corner.
Remember? Right after Trixie was born.
Oh, yeah. Great public schools,
really safe neighborhood.
Oh... or not.
June Lee, 34.
Local chemistry teacher. She
lived right down the block.
Forestry service left the
wood chipper here overnight,
and someone took advantage.
Did you get a chance to talk
to any of the lookie-loos yet?
Nope.
All yours.
Okay.
Hello.
I'm Detective Decker.
Who would do this to poor June?
Well, I'm hoping that you
all could help me with that.
Um... did any of you hear
or see anything out of
the ordinary this morning?
No. I mean, I heard that
wood chipper going, but...
I didn't know.
And did any of you know anyone
that would want to hurt June?
No.
Everyone really loved her.
She was very active in the community.
We just got mani-pedis together.
Mm, sorry.
Ah, thank you for your help, Maze.
No worries.
This actually gives
me time to brainstorm
a little problem of my own.
Ah.
So, this is for anything with wings.
- Ooh.
- I grab them like this.
And then I stab 'em with my blade.
Right.
This beauty...
This is for anything with horns.
Oh, goody.
- So I hook 'em like this.
- Yeah.
And then, bam!
Blade straight to the heart.
Right, I'm just gonna stop you there.
Do these grisly struggles
always end with you stabbing
a victim with your blade?
My blades were forged in Hell.
How else am I supposed
to kill a celestial being?
Damn. I already stabbed
him with one of your blades.
Well, I wish you would've told me that
before I hauled all
this out of the basement.
Nothing on Earth.
Nothing from Hell.
I mean, there must be some
way to snuff this candle.
Well...
Decker makes you killable, right?
- Hmm.
- Why don't you
see what's going on there?
Rub some of that on Pierce.
Apples to oranges, Maze.
What's going on there
is just a cruel joke from Dad.
And what's going on with Pierce isn't?
Your Father
is all about mind games
and loopholes, remember?
Yes, perhaps you're right, Maze.
Maybe I should find out
what makes Pierce vulnerable.
Get inside his head.
Not with the cranial saw.
Well, not yet
anyway.
Why is my couch in the
middle of my office?
Oh, good. You're here.
Please, take a seat.
How are you feeling today?
What are you doing?
Oh, answering a question
with another question.
That's called "evasion."
All right,
and your body language
suggests you're quite upset.
No, I'm just not a fan
of your redecorating.
That's awfully passive-aggressive
of you, Pierce. Why don't you
tell me how you really feel?
Get out of my office.
Good, good. Anger.
That's called a breakthrough, yeah.
Oh. Don't worry.
This is a safe place.
Why are you doing this?
Well, how am I supposed
to solve the mystery of how to kill you
if I don't understand you first?
Your strengths, your weaknesses.
Because everyone has a
Kryptonite, Lieutenant.
So in other words, you still
have no idea how to kill me?
But... this is the idea.
I'm not a crier.
I'm not a sharer.
So unless you have something
that's case-related,
we're done talking.
And turn my desk around.
Decker.
Please tell me you're working
on something interesting.
Pierce.
Lieutenant, you're still here.
D-Does that mean
you've decided to stay, or...?
Yeah.
At least for now.
Oh, that's great.
That's really, really great.
Two really's? Really?
Yeah, just 'cause...
I have a twist in my case,
and I could use your help.
So the suburban wood chipper victim,
we recovered a finger, ran a print.
Turns out June Lee isn't June Lee.
It's a false identity?
Our vic's real name is Sandra Jang,
and according to public record,
she died three years ago.
Fascinating. You know,
the lieutenant has a lot of
experience in fake deaths.
You must mean because I came up through
Missing Persons in Chicago.
Hmm.
Oh, great. We could really use
your experience on this, then.
Yes, I, too, would
love to learn everything
about your experience.
Sure.
Decker, why don't you pull
the original death certificate.
There might be something there.
You got it.
I know what you're trying to do.
If you mean solve a mystery, then yes.
And with you and I working
on this case together,
it'll kill two mysteries
with one stone, hmm?
Emphasis on the kill, of course.
Oh...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
So if we can figure out why
Sandra faked her death three years ago,
it might point to her killer.
In my experience, people
who fake their own death
are running from something or someone.
Right, something or
someone that scares them,
makes them feel vulnerable.
Any experience of that in
your own life, Lieutenant?
Sandra definitely could've been running.
- Check her rap sheet.
- Possession of narcotics
and distribution.
Mm-hmm. For a gang
called the Korean Power.
Oh, not your typical gangbanger.
Uh, that's 'cause
she's not a gangbanger.
She's some kind of a chemist.
Tech unlocked Sandra's laptop,
found, uh, recipes for
synthetic chemical compounds
all filed under the label "KPOP."
It's a kind of music,
- right?
- Oh, dear.
Poor Daniel, so behind the times.
K-Pop is a kind of Ecstasy.
It's one of the best kinds, actually.
Wait, so Sandra wasn't
dealing for the gang,
she was cooking for them.
I wonder if K-Pop is
still on the market?
Oh, well, it was as of last Tuesday.
It's wonderful stuff.
Yeah, it makes your skin
feel like a baby chinchilla.
And as a nightclub owner,
you might know where to find some?
Oh, absolutely. Yes, and
I'd be happy to guide you
on your roll, Detective.
Though I would wait till you have
a day off to recover.
- I'm not...
- You want to squeeze a dealer.
Right, and work our way up
the chain to the Korean Power,
maybe find Sandra's killer.
There are dozens of
homicides tied to the gang.
Okay, one Ecstasy
dealer coming right up.
You two can meet me at Lux in an hour.
- Sure.
- Right. Daniel?
- Yeah?
- You can stay.
Oh, here's one.
Some idiot named Ben Simpson.
Absconded in a stolen ice cream truck.
Six-five. Aggravated assault
with a blowtorch. Snore.
Don't you clowns have
anything challenging?
What is that?
Do you smell that?
Axe Body Spray.
Oh, hello. Uh, do I know you?
Used to.
I'm Lucifer's... friend.
Oh, so... we're friends?
Hell no.
You were a monstrous bitch
and I hated you. We were mortal enemies.
Right. I get that a lot.
Yeah, but now something's different.
It's...
wonderful.
And Lord knows I could
use a distraction.
Oh, well, I have been
trying to make changes.
You know, new leaf and all.
Hasn't been easy,
but I'm glad it's finally starting to...
come through.
Oh, something's coming
through all right.
Oh.
You smell incredible.
What, um, exactly did you
say our relationship was?
Shh. Don't talk.
I've got to go hog-tie a fugitive
in an ice cream truck right now.
But... I will definitely be back.
Where's Pierce?
He said he was coming.
Well, he's probably
busy at the precinct.
And if you're worried
about him being checked out, relax.
He's sticking around L. A. For a while.
I kind of convinced him to stay.
Oh, don't be foolish.
The man's clearly staying for me.
Turns out we have quite a bit in common.
Right. So, back to reality,
where we have a case to solve,
where is this dealer you promised?
Two house specials, please.
Lucifer, you know I
don't drink on the job.
Here you go. Two house specials.
Your bartender is a drug dealer?
What, you think I
hired him for abs alone?
Where'd you get the K-Pop?
I get it from the Korean Power.
Best "E" in town, or used to be.
Sad but true.
Previously hangover free,
but now in the morning,
your mouth's like Gandhi's flip-flop.
Hmm, what changed?
Their cook.
The gang used to have
some genius lady chemist,
but I heard she got greedy.
- She stole from the Korean Power?
- Yup.
Big, powerful, scary, boss dude,
and she pilfered right
from under his nose.
Huh.
Pretty ballsy.
I mean, not that I would ever...
Yes, yes, get on with it.
So, the boss put a
hit out on her, did he?
Yeah, but her lab blew up
before they could get to her.
- Freak accident.
- Accident?
Do you know this boss' name
or where we can find him?
Yeah. Brandon Hong.
He likes to hang out
at this one karaoke spot
over on Irolo.
But these guys don't mess around.
Right, well, mmm...
off we go, Detective.
What? Off we go to where?
To the karaoke parlor,
talk to a gang leader.
Maybe do a duet if you're
feeling adventurous.
We have to verify this
testimony with Vice.
We have to get a warrant,
assemble a SWAT team.
You know, actually plan
to do a gang takedown.
Right. Is that the sort of thing
the lieutenant would get involved in?
No, Pierce will not get involved
until we bring him a suspect.
Which is why we should
just go to the parlor
and skip to that part.
Lucifer, this is a ruthless drug lord
with who knows how many armed thugs?
You can't just walk in there
with your three-piece suit
and say...: "Hello, drug dealers."
I would never do that.
_
Come out, come out wherever you are.
- And who are you?
- I'm Lucifer.
Morningstar. But don't
worry, I'm here alone.
The police raid won't
happen for a few more hours.
Police raid?
Yes. So as you can see,
I'm in a bit of a rush.
Could you point me to the bigger gun?
- Your boss?
- Get rid of him.
What is it with people
trying to avoid me today?
♪ More than a feeling ♪
- I'm only trying to help.
- Help?
- Who?!
- You. The lieutenant.
I'm a giver, damn it.
And now you
are gonna help me.
Mr. Hong, thank you for coming in.
So, out-out of curiosity,
what... how did you know
that we wanted to speak to you?
Ah, when you're in my line of work,
word gets around, you know?
And what line of work is that?
Oh.
I run the Korean Power.
- Ah.
- Uh, we are a criminal organization
specializing in extortion
and drug dealing.
And, yes.
Sandra Jang used to cook our Ecstasy.
Oh. And while you're
being so forthcoming
about your felony distribution,
you care to confess to murder?
I'd love to help you,
but Sandra's death wasn't our doing.
What, even though she stole from you
and faked her own death to escape?
Yeah, she was a smart cookie.
I totally fell for the old
my-lab-exploded-and-I-died schtick.
But then,
like a voice from beyond, she called me.
Sandra stole money from
you to start a new life.
Why would she get back
in contact with you?
To pay the money back, with interest.
She was sick of looking
over her shoulder, I guess.
The suburbs gave her a double
garage and a conscience.
Yeah, I find that hard to believe.
You and your guys,
you aren't necessarily
known for your kindness.
Thank you.
And you're right.
I never forgave Sandra.
But not for stealing, for leaving.
When I found out she was still alive,
I begged her to come
back, but she said no.
Best cook I ever had.
Our profits went down over
40% when we lost her formula.
So she was worth more
to you alive than dead.
Oh, um...
I've instructed my guys to cooperate.
You know, alibis and stuff for
the night Sandra was killed.
Whatever the police need.
Okay, you do understand that
even if you weren't involved
in Sandra's death, you have
confessed to several felonies
and we will be arresting you.
Whatever it takes to bring
Sandra's killer to justice.
Right.
That was the most cooperative
arch-criminal I've ever met.
Did you go to that club on your own?
What did you do to him?
Nothing. Just made him a deal.
Of course you did.
In exchange for his cooperation,
I gave him the formula we
found on Sandra's computer.
I mean, a few years in prison
is just a small price to pay
for doubling your profits
with a superior product.
You can't just hand out
random, illicit drug recipes.
Not random, Detective, the best.
I mean, you don't want inferior Ecstasy
out there on the streets, ruining orgies
and dubstep parties, now, do you?
Rhetorical. My point
is, I got us our suspect,
so can we finally
involve the lieutenant?
We are not involving Pierce
until we check Hong's story.
And if what he says is true,
he's not even a suspect.
There's one way to find out.
There is?
Well, what are we gonna find in there?
We already know about
Sandra's criminal past.
Yes, but what about
her criminal present?
Sandra paid cash for her
house, then two years later,
paid back the Korean mob, with interest.
Right. How'd she get that money?
Exactly. You can't do that on
a chemistry teacher's salary.
So, what do we think?
She was hacking into banks?
Or she decided to dust off her
old skill of cooking Ecstasy.
- Right.
- Okay.
Now that we know what we're looking for,
let's try to find proof
that she was still making
and now selling drugs.
Huh. That's weird.
It's not connecting.
Oh, let me have a look at it.
Oh, Lucifer, please don't mess with it.
What does this do, anyway?
Stop shaking it. You're gonna break it.
Ah, you're right, Detective.
It does help to know
what you're looking for.
Are those client lists? Ooh.
Well, an angry one, maybe.
"I know what you're doing.
End it or you're dead."
Ooh.
So, you can take the girl
out of the Ecstasy biz,
but you can't take the
Ecstasy biz out of the girl.
Well, actually, it's not Ecstasy.
It's more sort of a homebrew Adderall.
It's very smooth.
Did your partner just
admit to snorting evidence?
The only thing I admit to is
being very focused on this case.
We think Sandra adjusted
her product to her new environment.
Type-A moms,
high-pressure dads...
And all the Ivy League-bound
brats in between.
And if she was selling,
these death threats suggest
that someone didn't want those
drugs in the neighborhood.
We think she was trying
to determine who sent them.
And maybe looking got her killed.
All right. Get close to the neighbors.
See who you can smoke out.
Right. I-I had the exact same idea,
and there is a house for
rent on Sandra's block.
However, the owner will
only rent to couples.
Great. You and Lucifer are on it.
No, I'd love to,
but I canvassed the entire neighborhood.
They know I'm a cop. Dan, too.
So find another officer
with knowledge of this case
to go undercover.
Oh, don't worry.
We already have.
Hey, hey.
It's the welcome wagon.
Yeah, but not in the lame way.
We just want to be the first to say hi
to the, uh, new couple on the block.
- I'm Brian. This is my wife Anya.
- Hey.
Thank you. That is so thoughtful.
Honey!
We have guests.
Ah. Right. Brian and Anya, this is Marc.
Hi. Oh.
Oh.
Mmm.
All right.
What, plastic plates?
What are we, barbarians?
Don't we have any china in there?
You know this isn't real, right?
I mea...
You realize this is just for the case.
This is my chance to
really get to know you.
Pierce, I'm taking it seriously
and so should you for our cause
and for the case, obviously.
So, let's just get in there
and put on a good show.
Shall we? Just don't give me
your resting Pierce face.
What face?
So, how did you two lovebirds meet?
We were high school
sweethearts, actually.
- Aw.
- We were biology partners.
He asked me out while we
were dissecting a crayfish.
My wife. Oh, the stuff she remembers.
How about you? How'd you two meet?
- At work.
- Well, um, actually,
we met through my Dad.
Oh!
- So sweet.
- Well, not really.
My Dad's a right bastard.
Oh, right, yes.
Tough, right? When
parents don't approve.
It's true. True. And my
Father would definitely
disapprove of this.
Isn't that right, Marky Marc?
Well, let's not start with that
with these nice people, Luke.
I'm sorry. Marc loathes
talking about himself.
He's shy.
But don't let that put you off.
I mean, we are neighbors now, after all.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
Feel free to ask him... I
mean, us... anything you want.
Okay. All right.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
All right.
Thank you.
Smells delicious.
Ah, I get it.
You know, when Chloe and I got divorced,
I was so worried about Trixie.
What she would think,
when I would see her.
But I realized, it's
the quality of the time,
not the quantity, you know?
I'm really glad we did this, Dan.
You're such a nice, normal guy.
Well, thank you, I think.
- I meant that as a compliment.
- Mm-hmm.
I mean, after the past few months,
normal is exactly
what I need in my life.
Hey, sexy.
What's up, Dan?
Uh, hello.
You two know each other.
Oh, yeah.
We, uh, killed a guy together once.
Maze...
No.
Uh, what she means is,
we had a killer time,
together, once.
Why are you here, Maze?
Isn't it obvious?
The three of us?
I'm sorry.
Did we...?
Oh, no.
No. No, no, no, no, we didn't.
No. Course n...
But if you wanted to...
um,
now... whatever...
you're into.
I have heard that
it's... Can be empowering
'cause I've-I've been reading
this, uh, feminist social...
Well, I'm into it.
If she is.
It's ho... hot.
Oh... uh, can I have
another drink, please?
Thanks.
Milano?
Ooh. They're aren't any
nuts in there, are there?
I-I blow up like a balloon.
Of course, allergies.
- Yeah.
- I didn't think of that.
What makes us vulnerable is
often right under our noses.
Shellfish, maybe?
Huh?
Bees? Latex?
Oh, you know I don't have
any allergies, sweetie.
Let's talk about this lovely community.
You seem so tightknit.
Yes, yes. It must have been devastating
when that poor woman was found
ground up like hamburger meat.
Our Realtor told us.
Yeah, it was horrible.
Huge loss. We're...
we're kind of one big
family around here.
Well, most of us, anyway.
Some of the neighbors
can be a little uptight.
Ah, come on, babe, the guys
don't want to hear about that.
Right? We're here to welcome 'em.
- Hear about what?
- The Neighborhood Watchdog.
Someone has been writing notes
and terrorizing the block.
Uh, "Trim your hedges, or else."
"Stop using non-organic weed killer,
or I'll make you drink it."
This Watchdog seems rather
preoccupied with gardening.
No. People have been getting
notes for all kinds of things.
Uh, loud music, parking,
holiday decor.
It's like Martha Stewart and
the Terminator had a baby.
Any idea who this "Watchdog" is?
No, actually.
Well, I suppose we
all have our mysteries.
Don't we? Speaking of,
wouldn't you two like to know more
about this little enigma?
- Hmm?
- Well,
this has been nice.
Um, but remember, we
have to get get up early
for that thing tomorrow morning.
Uh...
No idea what you're
talking about, darling.
Here you go.
I thought you went to the bathroom.
No.
I'm sorry, I just...
needed a few minutes.
Truth is, I've... been
through hell lately.
That's it.
No wonder I wanted you.
I can smell it on you.
The pain, the torment.
What, it's that obvious?
Girl, it is all over you.
I guess I thought I was doing
a better job of covering it up.
You see, um...
I died recently,
or... well, almost... died.
And since then, it's been a struggle
to get my life back to
some semblance of normal.
That's what you want?
Normal.
Yes. Please, God, yes.
Well, I am definitely not God.
Or normal.
So, guess I'm out.
Oh, y-you are?
I just...
I just told you my deepest secret.
Yeah.
Sorry.
I thought it was you I was attracted to,
but turns out, it's just my old life.
And I'm... not sure if
I want to go back there.
Hey, but Dan's probably
still into it, though.
Hmm.
Thanks so much for dinner, bye.
Bye, have a good one.
This Watchdog weirdo seems promising.
And those notes sound
just like the one we found
in Sandra's stash.
I just can't imagine someone so obsessed
with obeying the rules of suburbia.
Where do you think you're going?
I cook, you clean, remember?
Domesticity can have a
strange effect on people.
Question is, now,
how do we draw out this Watchdog?
Well, don't you worry
about that, Detective.
Trust me,
no one's a worse
neighbor than the Devil.
Lucifer.
What, are you building something?
Yes.
Our reputation as the most
annoying neighbors on the block.
It's 4:00 a. m.
Maybe we can finish this in the morning.
"We"?
You're barely involved.
You know, I-I...
I thought this was supposed
to be about you and I
spending time together.
No. No, no. This is
about catching a killer.
Guys, someone's approaching the house.
You just need to open up to me.
- Guys?
- That won't solve anything!
- Guys, heads up.
- Everyone has their Achilles' heel.
- Someone's approaching.
- We just need to find yours.
Right now, mine is you.
Guys. Damn it.
We've been through this.
Feel like I don't know you.
What are you talking about?
LAPD. Don't move.
Oh.
Hello.
Have you come for your casserole dish?
Hands up.
It's not illegal to hold people up
to our community standards.
The police should be thanking me.
I'm out there every
night helping you guys.
Helping? Is that what you were
doing when you killed June Lee?
What? I di... I didn't hurt June.
I understand. You're out there,
you're trying to keep
your neighborhood clean.
And then June's there, dealing drugs.
Wait, you think I was trying to
get June to stop dealing drugs?
I was her best customer.
You were buying her Adderall?
Uh, yeah.
Me and half the block.
How do you think I had the energy
to be out there every night, all night?
I mean, June changed my life.
I learned Mandarin.
I built a deck around
my... I-I lost 40 pounds.
Okay.
So you're saying you didn't
write that threatening note?
No, that's not even my
handwrit... look, look at it.
It's so sloppy. Of course,
what do you expect from someone
clueless enough to put a whole
body into a wood chipper? Wha...
I-I mean,
saw before you mulch.
Everyone knows that.
Thanks.
Ah. Now, he would know
not to put onion skins
down the garbage disposal.
You know, why wouldn't I put onion skins
down the garbage disposal?
They're garbage.
- They're compost.
- You know what?
Thank God that this marriage is over.
Guys.
Brian's not our killer.
But your cover is still intact
and I have a new plan.
You lovebirds ready
to go back to suburbia?
Ah.
Till death do us part,
darling.
Well, how's this angle, Detective?
A little to the right, and make sure
you put the guest book
where I can see it.
Don't worry, Decker, we'll
be checking handwriting
as we go along, I just
hope people show up
after Lucifer's antics.
Ah, I've simply piqued their curiosity.
Oh, we... we'd like everyone to sign.
Please.
Makes it more personal.
Um, why is that hummus so
far away from the crudités?
- What?
- Everyone knows
you put the snacks next
to the dipping sauce. I...
Why do I feel like I'm
the only one putting
any effort into anything?
Probably because you're
making everything about you.
Me?
In case you've forgotten,
I am doing this for you.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
And if you're not committed,
then there's no point
to us even being here.
The only reason I'm here
is because I have to be.
- Ah.
- Everything else is just an empty promise.
You have no idea what you're doing.
I beg your pardon?
You say you're a man of your word.
But you're not.
Can't believe he just said that.
Excuse me!
Lucifer.
What the hell are you
guys doing back there?
This is a sting... you can't
just leave in the middle of it.
I just can't be around him right now.
Lucifer, sometimes
when you go undercover,
things get real, people
get on each other's nerves.
But here's the thing:
you can't change your partner.
Tell me about it.
Okay... as hard as it is right now,
I need you to stick it
out until the job's done.
Pierce is never gonna be
the guy who cares about
where the hummus is, or whatever.
But he does care about what matters.
Like solving this case.
He can't do it without
you, and he knows that.
- Does he?
- Yes, he does.
So, please, get back in there
and get those signatures.
Right.
You moved the nachos.
Well, yeah, I didn't want
anyone to spill salsa...
Into the macaroni.
Wasn't sure you were coming back.
I made you a promise.
And I am a man of my word,
no matter what you may think.
I may have overreacted.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
But...
you were right about one thing.
I don't have all the answers.
But I hope that
we can find them... together.
I mean, after all, you may be
the only person on this planet
who truly understands me.
I'm not ready to give up on that.
Aw...
Wow. Cover officially restored.
Okay, now can we please
check the book for signatures?
Forgive me.
Ah, Marcie, uh,
some words for the chef?
Ooh, I've got mustard on...
Some words for the chef!
Lovely. Would you mind
working the word "pervert"
in there somewhere?
Could you address it
to "scheming whore"?
Just a little private joke for Marc.
Brian said he signed
for us both already.
Well, Marc and I would
like everyone to write
- a little message, if you don't mind.
- Oh.
Okay. Uh, let's see.
Actually, um, I think it's, uh...
I think it's time for us to go, dear.
But we just got here.
Uh, yeah, I know, but we really
need to go.
Brian, please.
What-wh-what are you doing?
Just put the book down.
- Brian!
- Brian...
- Brian, please...
- Just a little message.
No, no, no, I know what you guys are
- trying to do here.
- Brian.
Hey, Brian, just relax, okay.
Just calm down.
Take it easy.
Everybody get back!
Go on, get back. All
right, yeah? Get back.
Brian. Bri...
We're leaving.
Thanks. It was great.
- What about hedge trimmers?
- Tried it. Didn't work.
- Put it down, Brian.
- Uh...
I didn't want to hurt anybody.
I know. And I know you don't
want to hurt anyone right now.
You're not a killer,
you're just protecting one.
Brian, what is she talking about?
You wrote the threatening note to June.
We accused your
husband, but he must have
recognized your handwriting
when we showed it to him.
That's why he didn't want
you signing the guest book.
You know?
How could you do
something so stupid, babe?
I'm not stupid.
I know that you and June
were having an affair.
- No.
- I saw you
sneaking around with her,
and then you lost all that weight.
I thought I would just write her
one of those notes to scare her off,
but then you still kept
sneaking out every night.
And then you went and confronted her.
Yes, but then she just kept denying it,
and I got so,
so angry I just... shoved
her, and then she...
she hit her head.
But I d... I didn't mean to kill her.
I just...
I just didn't want you to leave me.
But he wasn't having an affair.
June was his drug dealer.
It's true.
I was buying pills from
her to help me lose weight.
For you, so that I could
go back to being the guy
that you fell in love
with in high school.
I didn't want you to leave me.
I'm so sorry I doubted you.
I just... I don't know
what I would do without you.
Neither do I. Oh...
Okay, show's over.
Yeah, I suppose there's
some cold comfort
in them being arrested together.
At least they've got each other.
Yeah, they do.
Dan?
Hey.
I just wanted to come by and apologize
about the other night.
You have nothing to apologize for.
I absolutely, completely blame Maze.
That girl is a freak.
She is odd.
But she also made me realize
some things about myself.
Maze isn't the only odd one.
I'm a mess.
All that talk about
feeling normal again?
Wishful thinking.
I have a long road ahead.
You know, whatever this is that we have,
it has never been normal.
And I decided that I
just have to own that.
I like you, Charlotte.
You are unlike anyone I have ever met.
So if you need time to
sort some things out,
I can wait.
You're worth it.
So, I heard the divorce went through.
What are you gonna do
with your half of Lux?
Very funny, Decker.
What's up?
Some of us from the precinct
are going down to the Paddock
for beers after work,
and I thought you might want to join,
if you don't have anything better to do.
I don't think I should.
Oh, yeah, no big deal.
Just, like I said, a lot
of people are going, so...
Listen, Chloe,
you and I, it's not a good idea.
Oh, I wasn't suggesting
anything romantic at all.
- I just...
- Listen, it's just
we deal with death every day,
and...
everybody's gonna die.
Someday you'll die, and I just...
Yeah.
Losing your brother, it's still
really affecting you, huh?
Understatement of the millennia.
I understand. I do.
And about tonight, it's not a big deal.
But...
just so I know that I'm not crazy, um...
in the surveillance van,
when I asked you to stay in L. A.,
we did have a moment there, yeah?
We did share a moment.
Which is why I had to tell you
that I'm not relationship material.
Mm.
Well, for what it's worth,
it was a really nice moment.
Lucifer, this better be good.
I was really looking forward to sleeping
far away from you tonight.
Oh, it is good.
I've finally got you figured out.
- Really?
- Mm, yes.
You're terrified of letting
someone get close to you
'cause you know they'll
eventually leave you.
You'll outlive them.
You want to die because
you don't want to be alone anymore.
Yeah, well, duh.
- What's your point?
- If we're gonna kill you...
then we have got to do it together.
Is that right?
Mm.
You see, I don't think you've
been spending time with me
trying to figure out how to kill me.
I think you want to spend time
with someone who's
been screwed by your Dad
as much as you've been.
You are the one that
doesn't want to be alone.
I suppose one might call us friends now.
And it is nice to have
a friend who can relate.
I get you.
No, you don't.
But you've been on the
earth, what, five years?
You'll see.
It's hard not to get attached.
Okay. Okay.
So we both have some issues
that we need to work through.
But if we're gonna get revenge on Dad,
we've got to be committed.
I've already married you.
I'm not sure how much
more committed I could be.
True. True.
But there are so many things
that we never got to try.
Fine.
Go get the chain saw.
Oh, I thought you'd never ask.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net