Penny, hello.
Hey, Sheldon.
What is shaking?
I'm sorry?
It's colloquial,
a conversation opener.
So, do you find
the weather satisfying?
Are you currently sharing in the triumph
of some local sports team?
What's wrong with you?
You're freaking me out.
I'm striking up a casual
conversation with you.
S'up?
Please don't do that.
All right, but I'm given to understand
that when you have something awkward
to discuss with someone,
it's more palatable to preface it
with banal chit chat.
So, this wasn't
the awkward part?
All right.
S'up?
Oh, good, I used that right.
Anyway, you're aware that Leonard has
entered into a new romantic relationship
which includes a sexual component?
Okay, feeling the awkward now.
Her name is Dr. Stephanie Barnett
and she is a highly distinguished
surgical resident at Freemont Memorial.
- Leonard told me.
- Good.
What he may have left out is how
important this relationship is to me.
To you?
See, of the handful of women
Leonard's been involved with,
she's the only one
I have ever found tolerable.
Well, what about me?
The statement stands for itself.
Aren't you sweet?
Anyway, should you have
any interaction with her,
it would be most helpful
that she not see you as a sexual rival.
Yeah, I think she's pretty safe.
You say that now,
but consider the following scenario:
You're sitting in your apartment,
it's late, you're alone.
Your hypothalamus is swimming in a soup
of estrogen and progesterone
and suddenly even Leonard
seems like a viable
sexual candidate.
Or a "hookup"
as it's referred to
by today's urban youth.
- Really?
- Yes. Now, should that happen,
I would ask you to find
some way to suppress your libido.
I could think about you.
Fine, whatever works.
Always nice talking
to you, Sheldon.
Peace out!
Subtitles: sub-way.fr
This is very pleasant.
Glad you're enjoying yourself.
And you said there'd never be
enough pasta for the three of us.
I stand corrected.
You know, Italian housewives
have a rule of thumb.
A handful of dry pasta
about an inch in diameter
is sufficient for each person
as it doubles in volume
when cooked.
- That's very interesting.
- Thank you.
She doesn't mean it.
She's just being nice.
Well, since Leonard seems to be
dropping the conversational ball,
I guess I'll just have
to pick it up.
Have you ever witnessed
a violent crime?
- No.
- Good.
What's your favorite fruit?
Strawberries.
Technically not a fruit,
but all right.
Where did you do
your medical internship?
Lawrence Memorial
in Galveston, Texas.
Really? That's where I was born!
You're kidding!
I spent so much of my childhood
at that hospital.
When I was 12,
I got to ride there in a helicopter.
- Why, what happened?
- Radiation burns.
A little mishap while I was
building my own CAT scanner.
I'm sorry, you tried to build
your own CAT scanner?
No, I didn't try, I succeeded.
In fact, I was briefly
able to see the inside
of my sister's guinea pig, Snowball,
before he caught fire.
It led to an interesting
expression in our house:
"Not a Snowball's chance
in a CAT scanner."
Excuse me.
When I come back, just for fun,
the subject will be
alternative history.
Specifically, how would
the Civil War have gone differently
if Lincoln had been a robot
sent from the future?
Look at that,
there's even pasta left over.
Do you understand
that this was supposed to be a date?
I do. Do you?
Because frankly,
you've been in a foul mood
since I sat down.
Okay, here's my question.
Why did you sit down?
To help.
Look, if you fail at this relationship,
and history suggests you will,
then we risk losing
the medical officer
that our landing party
has always needed.
What landing party?
You're Kirk, I'm Spock,
Wolowitz is Scotty,
Koothrappali is the guy
who always gets killed...
and now we've got McCoy.
So, we're all standing around
looking at the post-op X ray
and there it is, clear as day,
right in the guy's chest cavity...
one of my earrings.
Oh, my God, what did you do?
What do you think I did?
I discreetly slipped off
the other earring,
put it in my pocket
and then got the hell out of there!
I have a bone to pick with you, sir.
Hi, Sheldon.
Hi, Stephanie. I'm sorry I'm late,
but your companion left
the most indecipherable invitation.
What invitation?
"We're going to the movies."
What movie? What theater? What time?
If you were trying to make it
impossible to locate you,
you couldn't have done a better job.
Clearly I could have.
It took me nearly 20 minutes
to browse the history on your computer
to see what movie
times you looked up.
Wait here, I'll find us seats.
- We have seats.
- Not the right seats.
What is he doing?
He's finding
the acoustic sweet spot.
Does he always do this?
Sometimes he brings
a toy xylophone.
I am really sorry about this.
No, it's fine.
You know, he's sweet.
My apologies, you've been
sitting in it all along.
- You want to slide over one?
- No, just sit here.
Oh, yeah, this is it.
What, Sheldon?
What, Sheldon?! What, Sheldon?!
Tell me what you see here.
The blunt instrument that will be
the focus of my murder trial?
This is Stephanie's Facebook page.
Now, where it should say
"in a relationship," what does it say?
"Stephanie Barnett is single."
Furthermore, earlier this evening,
she threw a digital sheep
at some guy named Mike.
Who's Mike?!
Why does he get a digital sheep
and not you?
It's just her Facebook page
and we've only been going out
a couple of weeks.
You don't see it, do you?
We're losing her.
I'm going to make this
very simple for you.
You are not in this relationship.
I am.
Ergo, you have no say
in anything that happens
between me and Stephanie.
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
Pursuant to Starfleet
General Order 104,
Section A: You are deemed unfit
and I hereby relieve you
of your command.
General Order 104, Section A
does not apply in this situation.
- Give me one good reason why not.
- Because this is not Star Trek!
What?
This is banana bread.
This is a door knob.
It's my understanding
that an unsolicited gift of food
can be a precursor
to an impromptu invitation
to come in and chat.
Would you like to come in?
I suppose I could spare
a few minutes.
Were you robbed?
How can you be sure?
What do you want?
I'm certain this will come
as no surprise to you,
but Leonard is failing
in yet another relationship.
- He's having problems with Stephanie?
- She's sending virtual livestock
to random men on the Internet.
If I have any hope of keeping
them together, I need data.
Specifically, I need to know exactly
what Leonard did
that caused you to pop
an emotional cap in his buttocks.
- What?
- Again, urban slang.
In which, I believe I'm gaining
remarkable fluency.
So, what is the "down"
and the "low"?
And don't worry,
this is all entirely confidential,
so, you feel free to include
any and all shortcomings in the bedroom.
We never got to the bedroom.
Because?
All right, you know what?
I'll tell you what happened.
We were young,
we were very much in love,
but we could only communicate
through a time-traveling mailbox
at my lake house.
It's not enough that you made me
watch that movie,
but now you mock me with it?
Gentlemen, I have a question
about dating and relationships.
You told me you were going
to have the talk with him.
I've been waiting for someone
to have the talk with me.
More to the point,
it's about finding a way
to keep Leonard
and Stephanie together.
I don't think you can.
Why not?
Look at Leonard's record.
27 days with Joyce Kim.
During which she defected
to North Korea.
Two booty calls with Leslie Winkle.
For which she awarded him the nickname
"Speed of Light Leonard."
- And the three hour dinner with Penny.
- Which would have been two and a half
if they ordered the souffle
when they sat down.
Based on the geometric progression,
his relationship with Stephanie
should have ended after 20 minutes.
Yes, I'm aware of the math.
Y equals 27 days over 12 to the nth.
The issue remains.
How do we circumvent
his inevitable rejection?
If you want to guarantee
his appeal to Stephanie,
your best bet would be to kill
all the other men on the planet.
Here's what you shouldn't do.
Don't shpritz him with that body spray
from the commercial where the women
undress when they smell it.
That doesn't work at all.
No matter how much you put on.
That's all you've got?
Apocalyptic genocide
and "go easy on the cologne"?
What?
Zucchini bread.
- Thank you.
- May I come in?
I see.
Apparently, my earlier inquiry
regarding you and Leonard
crossed some sort of line.
I apologize.
Well, thank you.
Have you and I returned
to a social equilibrium?
- Yes.
- Great.
New topic.
Where are you
in your menstrual cycle?
What?!
I've been doing some research online,
and apparently, female primates,
you know, apes,
chimpanzees, you...
They find their mate more desirable
when he's courted by another female.
Now, this effect is intensified
when the rival female is secreting
the pheromones
associated with ovulation.
Which brings me back to my question.
Where are you...
Clearly, I'm 14 days too early.
All I'm saying is if they can cure
yellow fever and malaria,
why can't they do something
about lactose intolerance?
Leonard, you're going
to have to let this go.
You had a little cheese dip, you farted.
I thought it was cute.
- You want some more wine?
- Yeah, I mean...
I assume I'm not driving
anywhere tonight.
What are you doing?
I have a craving
for white asparagus
that apparently is destined
to go unsatisfied.
Excuse me.
- What is wrong with you?
- I'm helping you with Stephanie.
By making constipated moose sounds?
When I fail to open this jar
and you succeed,
it will establish you
as the "alpha" male.
You see... when a female
witnesses an exhibition
of physical domination,
she produces the hormone oxytocin.
If the two of you
then engage in intercourse,
this will create
the biochemical reaction in the brain
which lay people naively interpret
as "falling in love."
Would it work if I just
punched you in the face?
Yes, actually it would,
but let's see how the lid goes.
I'm not strong enough, Leonard,
you'll have to do it.
- For God's sakes.
- Go ahead, it's pre-loosened.
You want some help with that?
I got it.
He's got it,
and that's not surprising.
It's something I long ago
came to peace with
in my role as the beta male.
Open it.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not.
- I'm bleeding.
- Like a gladiator!
- Honey, you're going to need stitches.
- Stitches? With a needle?
Well, yeah, I mean, just a few.
Yeah, hang on a sec.
FYI, I was defrosting
a steak in there.
What a beautiful job Stephanie did.
I might have gone with a mattress suture
instead of a blanket stitch,
but you can't argue
with her results.
It's a shame it won't scar.
The war wound is a time-honored
badge of masculinity.
I can't remember a time
when you weren't talking.
Just for the record, my efforts
to establish you as the alpha male
were not aided by you
bursting into tears.
I did not burst into tears,
my eyes just got a little watery.
Watery?
She stuck a needle into my hand!
Hey, how's my big cry baby?
I didn't cry.
I'm just teasing you.
But, yeah, you did.
It's all good. What do you say
we get you home and put you to bed?
Are you still going
to spend the night?
No, I think that you probably
need to rest.
She's right. As long as you're vomiting,
coitus is contra-indicated.
Thank you, Dr. Cooper.
You're welcome, Dr. Hofstadter.
Okay, I'm going to go
get your discharge papers.
What?
You seem like
a perfectly pleasant person.
I can't understand why women
have such a hard time loving you.
Can you open this for me?
- Can I see your stitches?
- Sure.
Answering the question
once and for all
why Wolowitz bailed out
of medical school.
- Leonard, congratulations.
- What for?
Your Facebook status update.
Leonard Hofstadter is
"in a relationship."
What? No, that's not right.
Oh, man, did you switch
your status before she did?
Speaking as an expert,
way to look needy.
Seriously? You went first,
after only two weeks?
That's bold...
It's not bold, it's a mistake.
I didn't change my status.
Well, then who did?
I had no choice.
He cried in front of her.
You hacked my Facebook account?
It's hardly hacking
when you use the same password
for everything, "Kal-El."
Are you insane?
Now she's going to think I'm desperate.
You've destroyed this relationship!
And you know what the worst part is?
You don't even understand
what you did wrong
because you can't conceive of something
that you are not an expert in!
- In which I am not an expert.
- Don't even!
I don't want to hear
another word out of you.
What's wrong, Lassie?
Timmy fall down the well?
She just updated
her Facebook status.
"Stephanie Barnett is
in a relationship
"with Leonard Hofstadter."
Really?
Look at that.
I have a girlfriend.
If I am permitted to speak again,
Dr. Sheldon Cooper for the win.
www.tvsubtitles.net