Advantage left-side competitor.
Wow, you're really
good at this.
Well, I have an extremely
low center of gravity.
I'm like a pyramid.
How you doing over there?
Oh, I hope it's just a sprain.
I cannot walk into that E.R.
with another video game injury.
Hey, Sheldon,
you want to play next?
Oh, I would, but
I'm on my way out.
Where?
Texas.
Right now?
Why?
Is someone sick?
Yes.
My sister's uterus came
down with a baby.
Oh, she's pregnant?
That's great.
You're gone an uncle--
Uncle Sheldon.
No, I will be
Uncle Dr. Cooper.
How come you never said
she was pregnant?
Well, I never told you
about my brother's kidney stone.
You want to hear
about everything
that comes out
of my family's genitals?
Well, congrats, and it's nice
you're gonna be there
for your sister.
Yes.
I'm filling in for her husband
who's recovering
from a horrible
motorcycle accident.
Lucky duck.
Wow, so, how long
will you be gone?
Well, she's due tomorrow.
Although it did take her six
years to finish high school,
so who knows?
Can I give you a ride
to the airport?
Oh, no, thank you, I don't want
to be an inconvenience.
Chop-chop, Leonard.
We leave in ten minutes.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unveiling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 7x11 ♪
The Cooper Extraction
Original Air Date on December 12, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
All right, here's the deal.
Sheldon is gone,
so the tree decorating rules
are out the window.
Yeah, which means
we don't have to use
his ridiculous
ornament-spacing template.
And I'm happy to report
its kickstarter campaign
is holding strong at zero dollars.
Ah.
Wait, so Star Wars
and Star Trek characters
can go on the same branch?
I know, it's crazy.
Welcome to the Thunderdome,
people!
I've never done this before.
It's kind of fun.
Yeah, if your mom could see
her little Bar Mitzvah boy
right now,
she'd have a heart attack.
Good idea, I'll take a picture.
Honey, I'm a little strapped
for cash this year,
so for Christmas I was
thinking of giving you...
this.
I love it.
Okay.
But it is what you got me
last year.
Yeah.
And last night.
Hello.
Hi, Stuart.
Oh, good, I'm glad you guys
didn't wait for me to start.
Although you said 7:00
and it's-it's 7:00,
but that's fine.
Oh, it's probably Sheldon.
Hi, Sheldon.
Everybody's here, say hi.
Hey. - Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Howdy.
Hi.
Hello.
The second I go out of town
you throw a Christmas party
without me?
Yeah, kind of.
That's so thoughtful.
You guys are the best.
Hey, how's your sister?
She went into labor an hour ago.
That's wonderful.
So you're at the hospital?
No, she chose to have a home
birth... because she wants
to live in the Stone Age
and a cave wasn't available.
You know, many
people believe
that home births are
better because the mother
is in a warm,
comfortable environment
where she can be nurtured
by loved ones.
And turn the bedroom floor
into an amniotic Slip 'n Slide.
Shelly, come on!
Your sister's fully dilated
and she wants
a nice family picture
before there's blood everywhere!
Oh, boy.
I picked the wrong day
to wear my good robot T-shirt.
If you were having
Sheldon's baby
would you really want
him in the room?
Yeah, if he's in the room
when they're making the baby,
I'll give you ten dollars.
Hey, I brought over
It's a Wonderful Life
if you guys want
to watch it later.
Oh, I love that movie.
I've never seen it.
- Me neither.
- It's great.
It's Christmastime and
Jimmy Stewart's really depressed
and he's gonna jump off a bridge
and kill himself...
Don't need to see it.
Living it.
But then he gets to see
what the world
would be like
if he'd never been born.
Hey, you ever imagine
what that would be like?
Not being born?
What do you think?
You make jokes about Sheldon,
but if it weren't
for him,
I don't think
any of us
would be sitting
in this room right now.
Really? Sheldon not being here
is the main reason
I'm in this room.
It's true.
None of you would know me.
You wouldn't
know Bernadette.
You wouldn't be dating Penny.
You don't know that.
I've been going to the
Cheesecake Factory for years.
I could have picked her up.
Oh, you weren't joking.
No.
Okay, sweetie,
let me tell you
exactly how that
would have gone down.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna ask her out.
I'm gonna squirt chocolate milk
out of my nipples.
Sorry, I thought
we're saying things
that are never
gonna happen.
Maybe this time
he's going to do it.
Hope you're thirsty,
here it comes.
Watch me.
Hey, you guys ready to order
or you need a few minutes?
I, uh, ah, um, I...
A few minutes it is.
You didn't ask her out,
but that was a lot of sounds.
You guys are
making me nervous.
Fine, then go talk
to her on your own.
I will.
Excuse me.
Yeah?
Hi, uh, um, I'm Leonard?
Really? You don't
sound so sure.
No, I am he.
Uh, any-anyway, um,
there's been something
I've wanted to ask you
for a long time. Um...
What's that?
Eh, uh, well,
I was wondering--
if you're not too busy--
um, uh, if,
if you'd be interested in...
...telling me where
the restroom is?
I think you're too late.
Come on, I would not
have peed my pants.
She nailed it.
Sounds about right.
But, you forget, I did
ask you out in real life.
Which couldn't have happened if
you didn't live across the hall
from her, which couldn't have
happened without Sheldon.
Same goes
with you guys.
If Leonard wasn't with Penny,
she never would
have set you up.
Doesn't matter. Bernadette
still would've been working
at The Cheesecake Factory,
and I still would've been
working this beefcake factory.
You would've been all over me.
Well...
Hey, Penny, can
I take that table?
Sure, why?
The one in the turtleneck
is cute.
Open wide,
here comes the happy train.
Mm-hmm, chug-a
chug-a, yum, yum.
Oh.
Hang on.
You got a... you got
a little something.
Never mind.
Oh, man,
that is so us.
You know, maybe you and
I wouldn't be together,
but you wouldn't have
done so great yourself.
Why?
Because I know exactly
the kind of guy you
would've ended up with.
Hey, babe.
Hey. Did you remember
to pay the rent?
Better. I used the money
to buy these magic beans.
Hey, he may be
an idiot, but at least
he didn't pee himself.
Oh, hold on.
Aw, babe, I peed myself.
Me, too.
The end.
Hi, Sheldon.
Everything okay?
No, it's not.
I've seen things.
Lady things.
Listen to me.
That is not the way
they usually look.
Doesn't matter.
This is no way
to make new humans.
People coming out of people.
It's some kind
of dirty magic show.
Sheldon Lee Cooper.
You get back
in this room right now.
Bring a mop.
Did you hear that?
A mop.
I have two PhDs yet somehow
I'm the janitor
of my sister's birth canal.
Hey, Sheldon sent us all
an e-mail.
"Happy holidays from Texas."
Aw.
And there's pictures.
Aah!
Don't open them.
Do not open them.
Oh, come on.
Childbirth is a
natural, beautiful...
Oh, it's like someone
sawed a cow in half.
My father's a gynecologist,
I think I can handle it.
And, now, I'm gay.
You know, I was thinking.
Without Sheldon,
most of us would have never met,
but Penny would still
live across from him.
And with Leonard
out of the picture,
we all know what
that would mean.
We do?
Hey, Sheldon.
Hello.
Doing laundry?
Of course
I'm doing laundry.
Saturday night is laundry night,
and I'm in a laundry room, so...
I believe your inference
is justified.
Oh, my
inference is justified.
Sheldon, you
are so funny.
Anyway, I need to
do my laundry, too,
because these
clothes are so dirty.
Almost as dirty as the dirty
girl who's wearing them.
Okay, that's enough.
Disagree.
Keep going. - More.
So, what do you think?
A tad asymmetrical, but nothing
to be concerned about.
Please, Sheldon. I need you.
To... what?
To take me.
I'm not taking you anywhere
till you put on a shirt.
Come on, Sheldon.
You and me right here.
Penny, for the thousandth time,
I'm saving myself
for someone special.
Perhaps a cute
bespectacled neuroscientist
with hair
the color of mud.
I think I know how
to change your mind.
That's enough.
Ew...
I was okay with it.
How's it going, Sheldon?
Actually, much better.
Oh, good.
Is the baby born yet?
I don't know. I just got back.
Where'd you go?
My mother asked me
to get some towels.
I took advantage
of the vague request
and went to Bed,
Bath & Beyond.
Excuse me! I'm on the phone!
So rude.
Here's another one.
Penny,
if it weren't for Sheldon,
you never would have met
comic book legend Stan Lee.
Great.
At least Leonard,
Howard and I would have
always been friends.
Hey, how come you three never
got an apartment together?
We talked about it,
but Howard was in
a pretty serious
relationship with his mom.
I lived with her to save money.
Yeah, you didn't have
to buy groceries
'cause you were breast-feeding.
Aw, so I guess
if it weren't for me,
you'd still be living
with her, huh?
Not exactly.
What do you mean, "not exactly"?
Well, things would be
a little different.
Howard, where's my lunch?!
I'm starving!
I know you're starving.
The neighbors know
you're starving.
There's starving people in
Africa who know you're starving!
That's it?!
There's not enough food!
Well, you cleaned out Earth!
I don't know what else to do!
How is this
any different?
You didn't let me finish.
Here you go, Mother.
You're a good boy, Howard!
Such a good boy!
Wait-- did she die
or did you kill her?
Eh, tomato, tomahto. The
important thing is she's dead.
Hey, so how come you two
didn't move in together?
This guy wanted
a place of his own
because he was sure he was
gonna be a ladies' man.
Yeah, I was wrong.
But I do think you and I
would have had a great time.
Come on, Leonard, dinner.
Coming.
Hang on.
Why would I be fat?
You'd have no girlfriend
to see you naked,
you'd try to fill the void
with food,
and I'm an enabler who once
deep-fried a pancake.
Why can't you be fat, too?
What do you want
to do for dessert?
I think there's still
half a cake from breakfast.
No, there's not.
Hey, guys.
Stuart.
What are you doing?
I...
just wanted to be
in anyone's story.
Yeah, but why are you fat?
'Cause Leonard was fat.
Amy, what about you?
What do you think you'd be doing
if you never met Sheldon?
It's hard to say,
my life would be
so... different.
You can say "better."
Sheldon can't hear you.
I don't know.
♪ Happy birthday to me
♪ Happy birthday
to me ♪
♪ There's tears
in the frosting ♪
♪ Happy birthday to me.
I'll stop now.
How's it going, Sheldon?
That's it.
The baby's here.
It's a boy.
Congrats.
Aw. - Yay.
Oh, thank you.
I wasn't sure I was
gonna to make it.
But my mother
gave me some ice chips,
my sister told me to breathe.
And I just thought
to myself, "Sheldon,
"if you can make it through
the Green Lantern movie,
you can make it through this."
Well, good
for you, buddy.
We'll let you
get back in there.
Oh no, no, I'm not
going back in there.
That baby is so irritating.
He has literally been
crying his entire life.
Aw, he's already taking
after Uncle Shelly.
Come on, Sheldon, you should go.
Why?
Well, you always
complain that you never
had an intelligent
role model growing up,
and now you can
be one for your nephew.
Ugh, all right, I'll go.
But from what I've seen,
his attention span
is as limited
as his bladder control.
You actually
got him to do it.
Yeah, you keep saying
how much Sheldon has
affected all of us,
but you've clearly
had an impact on him.
If that were true,
I wouldn't still
be living alone.
Well, not exactly alone.
I do have a 50 pound
sack of rice
with one of Sheldon's
T-shirts on it.
I'm telling you, Sheldon cares
for you more than you think.
I wish I could believe you.
I also wish there wasn't a mouse
living in Rice Sheldon.
Hang on, I'm gonna
give you a little
early Christmas
present.
I'm gonna show you something,
but if you ever told Sheldon
he'd probably never
speak to me again.
So, if you want to
tell him, that's fine.
Look.
I don't understand.
He made you
his screensaver.
Oh.
Wow.
I had no idea.
He is so into me.
Wait, wait,
where'd I go?
Oh, well, it's
you, Swamp Thing,
Stephen Hawking,
Spider-Man...
but, look, you're
in the mix.
I am in the mix.
And I'm the hottest one.
Who's that?
Oh, Madame C.
That's fine, she's dead.
You okay?
Just really glad
you're back.
Me, too.
I got a lot of TV
to catch up on.
I missed you.
To quote Han Solo,
"I know""
Did you miss me?
I would've preferred
to have you there with me.
Oh.
Or instead of me.
Did you hold the baby?
I did.
And?
How did it make you feel?
Looking into the
blank, innocent eyes
of a creature that
couldn't begin to comprehend
anything I was saying?
Basically just
another day at the office.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna ask her out.
Yeah, and chocolate milk is
gonna squirt out of my nipples.
Put up or shut up.
You make it, I'll drink it.
You guys need anything else?
Uh,
your phone number
and one more cheesecake.
I'm sorry, I have a boyfriend.
In fact, there
he is now.
Ready to go, sweetheart?
Not until I get
my kiss.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net