English (HI) Subtitles.
[MP4] The Big Bang Theory S08E11 (720p) The Clean Room Infiltration - HDTV [KoTuWa]
Hey, how are things going
with your parents?
Not great.
They hired divorce attorneys.
You know, speaking
of attorneys,
if I ever needed
a lawyer,
I would not hire
She-Hulk.
You know what?
That was almost on topic.
I'm gonna say,
"Good job, Sheldon."
Wait, She-Hulk's
a lawyer?
Yeah, she works at
a law firm in New York.
Yes, but she's the only
monster at the firm.
Between you, me
and the wall,
I think she's an
affirmative action hire.
Anyway, Dad's gonna
be here in town,
so I won't be able to do
Christmas dinner this year.
If you're not up
to hosting Christmas dinner,
I'm happy to do it.
You can even
bring your father.
That would be nice.
I've always wanted to do
a traditional
Victorian Christmas.
Parlor games,
goose and figgy pudding...
Ugh!
English pudding.
Y-You get yourself all
excited for pudding,
and here comes a cake
with raisins in it.
I'm not going.
You're going.
Why do you hate me?
I don't hate you.
I love you.
Well, you call it love,
but it has a lot
of raisins in it.
Amy, good luck getting
these guys excited
about a dinner
with a theme.
I gave up when no one cared
about my Tom Hanks-giving.
I think a Victorian Christmas
sounds nice.
I agree.
Why not?
Me, too.
You guys suck!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
♪ The Big Bang Theory 8x11 ♪
The Clean Room Infiltration
Original Air Date: 2014-12-11
Sync, corrected by elderman
@elder_man
You know the best part
of working in the clean room?
No allergies.
Check it out.
(inhales deeply)
Oh, that-that...
that's a lot of oxygen.
(chuckles)
We should get
going to Amy's.
Can you believe
there was a time
when we would have
needed an array
of giant Cherenkov telescopes
to detect cosmic particles?
And here we are building
our own multi-wire detector
like a couple of badasses.
I know. If we were still single,
we'd be tripping
over all that booty.
Ladies do love a man dressed
like a kitchen garbage bag.
Oh, no.
How the hell
did a pigeon get in here?
You shut the loading doors, right?
I thought you did.
Do you know what a
disaster this is?!
You mean 'cause this room isn't
supposed to have dust in it,
and we just let in
a flying crap machine?!
What do we do?
Should we call someone?
And tell them that we
compromised all the equipment?
Let's just get it out of
here before anyone knows.
Okay, how do we catch it?
Well, what if we turn
off all the lights
except for one, and
it'll come to it.
It's not a moth!
Don't yell at me.
You're not gonna get
any good ideas out of me
if you're yelling.
Okay, so if I remain calm,
I'll get more gems like,
"Turn off the lights"?!
Great, we're turning
on each other.
That's just what the
bird wants us to do!
So, Dr. Koothrappali,
long flight?
20 hours.
Oh, that's rough.
Not at all. Did you know that
when you fly transcontinental
without your wife, you don't
pray for the plane to crash?
Can you please talk
about anything else?
Forgive me.
How are you
and Leonard?
Oh, great.
Everything's good.
I see you got engaged.
Yes, we did.
Let me tell you a story.
Dad!
Sorry.
I'm sure you won't grow
to hate each other.
(ringtone playing)
Hey, Leonard. What's up?
What? How did that happen?
Yeah, okay.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
Sorry. I have to run
to the university.
What's going on?
There's been a problem
with our experiment.
A bird got into the clean room.
You want me to come?
Uh, no.
You had a long flight.
You stay here and relax.
"Relax."
Easy for you to say.
Your mother isn't cleaning out
your bank account.
40 years,
the woman never cleaned a thing.
(quietly): You're just
gonna leave him here?
"Relax," he says.
Yup. Bye.
(singing along to music):
♪ Here comes Santa Claus,
here comes Santa Claus ♪
♪ Right down Santa Claus Lane ♪
♪ Vixen and Blitzen
and all his reindeer ♪
♪ Pulling on
the reins... ♪
Yeah, I appreciate the ride...
♪ Bells are ringing,
children singing ♪
♪ All is merry
and bright ♪
♪ So hang your stockings
and say your prayers ♪
(radio turns off) ♪ 'Cause Santa Claus
is coming tonight... ♪
Why'd you turn it off?
Because in the last ten minutes,
Santa came to town,
kissed Mommy and ran Grandma
over with a reindeer.
I had a drunk uncle
who did all those things.
Nobody sings songs about him.
Maybe you'd like it more if you
thought of Santa as a superhero
and his power is bringing joy
to children.
My uncle was accused
of that, too.
It turned out
to be legal in Oklahoma.
Okay, new subject.
Let's talk
about presents.
What did you get Amy?
Oh, we're not exchanging gifts.
Come on, Sheldon, you
have to get her something.
Why should I?
She knows
that I don't like Christmas,
and yet, every year,
she forces me to celebrate it.
Not only am I going to this
foolish dinner against my will.
At the Christmas tree lot,
there was mistletoe,
and she kissed me
under it in public.
Like we were the stars
of a Tijuana sex show.
She's just excited
about the holidays.
Yes, and she's not taking
my feelings into account at all.
Maybe it's time
I teach her a lesson.
How?
Hmm. It'd have
to be something heinous,
something that makes her
as miserable as she's making me.
Oh, I've got it.
(gasps)
This is good.
What?
I'm going to buy her a present.
Yeah, you're gonna
have to walk me through that.
With gift-giving, there's
an implied social contract.
If I show up
tonight with a present,
and she doesn't have one for me,
she'll feel terrible.
Then you're both sad?
Yes.
Maybe she'll feel so guilty,
she'll never make me celebrate
the holidays again.
So your evil plot here is to buy
your girlfriend a present?
That's right.
So stay on my good side, or I'll
get you a little something, too.
(cooing)
Okay, here's the plan.
I'm gonna put the food
in the bag,
and when he lands in the bag
to eat it, we close it up.
A Slim Jim?
It's all I could find.
It'll work.
Sure.
If the pigeon's stoned
or a trucker.
Okay, well, what's your plan?
I told you my plan.
Let's call Building Services
and get help.
And admit that we contaminated
the clean room?
No, admit that you
contaminated the clean room.
Why do you keep assuming
it was me?
Because you do this kind
of thing all the time,
and then you try
to cover it up.
Like when?
(scoffs)
What about when you
flipped the Mars Rover,
or lost Koothrappali's dog,
or almost drove off
with that baby?
Again, it looked like my car,
and the baby didn't even cry
until his mother punched me
with her keys.
Fine, put the Slim Jim
in the garbage bag.
Well, what if you said it
without sounding
so condescending?
I can try, but your
plan has the words
"garbage bag" and
"Slim Jim" in it!
Hey, what's going on?
Oh.
Genius here wants
to catch a bird
with a garbage bag
and a Slim Jim.
Should have put it
in the bag first.
So, if you don't
mind me asking,
do you think you might
start dating again?
It's much too soon for that.
Why? Do you know someone?
No, but if things don't
work out with me and Leonard,
I'll give you a call.
Wait. How much do you talk
about Star Trek?
Okay, let's get this
Victorian party started.
I've done some research
about some traditional
parlor games we can play.
Like what?
Well, there's a fun one
called Ball of Wool.
You take a ball of wool,
and you put it right
in the center of the table.
Then people sit
on opposite sides of the table
and try to blow the wool off.
Sorry.
She's taken, too.
You know what I think
your problem is?
You're jealous
because you and I
used to be
best friends until
Koothrappali came along.
And you found somebody
you could push around?
Hey!
Stay out of this.
Okay.
You know, maybe I'm
best friends with Raj
because he doesn't think
he's smarter than me.
Actually...
I said, stay out of it!
N-No. No, Raj, go ahead,
say what you were gonna say.
All I'm gonna say is
you guys need
to stop this right now.
It-It's bad enough that
my parents are fighting,
now I have to hear
the two of you?
And who cares who's smarter?
If it's Leonard or me or...
you know, it's Christmas,
let's say it's Howard.
Well, if you're so smart,
you get the bird out.
No, you're the one
who let him in.
How do you know
it wasn't Leonard?
Come on.
What about that sweater?
No, it's not good enough.
It has to be perfect.
I think the nicest gifts
I've got from Howie
show how well
he knows me.
Hmm.
Let's see,
what do I know about Amy?
She loves medieval literature;
Chaucer's her favorite.
And her eyes sparkle when
she watches old French movies.
I enjoy how harp music causes
her fingers to dance
as if she's playing along.
Wow, you really do love her.
I do.
Now, let's find
the kind of gift
that makes her feel
small and worthless.
You won!
Certainly doesn't
feel like it, does it?
You know, my wife used to throw
theme parties like this
all the time.
Oh, I guess that's
where Raj gets it from.
Well, he and his mother
spent a lot of time together
when he was young.
I was always working.
Hey, you know, Raj is dating
a doctor who works a lot.
(chuckles)
Him and his mom have a type.
You g... Y-You got to laugh
at that, right?
No? All right.
All right, let me see
if I've got this straight.
A picture of you on my lap
is a way to punish
your girlfriend
for making you
celebrate Christmas?
Correct.
Santa thinks dating you
may be punishment enough.
There's an argument
for that.
But I want to make sure.
Smile.
Ho, ho, ho!
Okay. On the
count of three,
I'll shoot the fire extinguisher
and get him airborne.
Howard, you wave the blanket
and guide him towards the exit.
Raj, you hold open the
curtain so he can fly out.
Are you sure a dummy
like me can handle something
as complicated
as a blanket?
Do you want the
fire extinguisher?
Yeah, I do.
Great.
Here you go.
Okay.
One, two, three.
Uh, you have to
take the pin out.
You miss the blanket now,
don't you?
On three.
One, two, three.
(splat)
What did you do?
It was an accident.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Relax, it wasn't your fault.
Uh, maybe it's just stunned.
Dude, i-it's not breathing.
Oh, no. I killed it.
Oh, not again.
What do you mean, not again?
When I was ten,
I was playing
in my backyard and...
sat on a blue jay.
I mean, I tried
to bring it back to life
with electricity, but it just...
caught on fire.
The worst part was
it smelled delicious.
Uh, guys, I found
an article here
that says you can do CPR
on birds.
Great! Do it!
I'm not doing it.
You killed him, you do it.
I'll do it.
No.
I need to do it.
This is on me.
Okay.
"Mouth over beak
and light chest compressions."
Don't blow too hard.
If you pop him, I will vomit.
Anything?
(raspy):
I am tasting a lot of Slim Jim.
(coughs)
Wait, wait, his wing moved!
Oh, he blinked his eyes!
He's alive!
It's a Christmas miracle!
I might argue a Hanukkah
miracle, but I'll take it.
Come on, little guy, let's get
you outside. Get the curtain.
(bird caws)
Someone should really
close that loading door.
Well, that's that.
The room's compromised.
They'll have to change
all the filters,
probably shut it down
for weeks.
You were right. Go ahead,
call Building Services.
Tell them it was my fault.
No, we're both to blame.
You know, let me take
the heat on this one.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Yeah, just leave me out of it.
You know if they come here
and see crap everywhere,
they're just gonna
blame the Indian guy.
(ringtone playing)
Hey. I'm sorry,
we're still here.
Is everything okay?
It's kind of boring.
Although it did get exciting
for a minute
when Amy inhaled a wool ball.
How much longer
do you think you'll be?
I don't know.
There's still
a bird in here.
We are gonna get in
a ton of trouble.
Honey, it's Christmas Eve.
Who even knows you're in there?
No, our names are on
the sign-in sheet.
So erase them and walk out.
I can't do that.
Can't do what?
She says take our names
off the sign-in sheet
and leave.
(chuckles): We can't do that.
Yeah.
ALL: ♪ Jingle bells, jingle
bells, jingle all the way ♪
♪ Oh, what fun it is to ride ♪
♪ In a one-horse
open sleigh, hey! ♪
Mmm. Amy,
that pudding was delicious.
If you like raisins.
Thank you. And it's figs.
Oh.
Oh, in that case,
it was pretty good.
You feeling okay? You hardly
touched your goose.
It smelled too much
like blue jay.
Can I help you
clean up?
Oh, you Heimliched a ball
of wool out of me; you're good.
Uh, what do you say
we exchange gifts?
Oh, Sheldon,
we didn't bring any.
I thought you hate
giving gifts.
Yeah, I do.
Which is why I got Amy this.
You got me something?
Oh, not just
something, no.
It's from the heart,
it's holiday-themed,
and I swallowed the gift receipt
so you cannot return it.
Look at you on Santa's lap.
That's so sweet.
Of course it is.
It's the perfect gift.
H-How are you feeling right now?
Guilty? Sad?
Wishing you were Jewish?
No, I love it.
Oh, really?
Well, how about now?
(Christmas music playing)
SHELDON (recorded):
Happy holidays to my dear Amy.
I hope you treasure this
as much as I treasure you.
(mouthing)
And you got me nothing.
Christmas is ruined.
Let's never speak of it again.
Well, this was fun.
Actually,
I did get you
something.
But what about our agreement?
Well, you got me
something. Here.
Cookies?
They're your Meemaw's
Christmas cookies.
I called and got
the recipe.
They're perfect.
It tastes like her hugs.
Merry Christmas, Sheldon.
I can't believe this.
You're happy, I'm happy.
Well, maybe a holiday that's
all about giving isn't so...
Get your hand out of that box!
Okay.
The next game is called
Hot Boiled Beans.
Of course it is.
One person is sent
out of the room
while the others
hide a small item.
Then they invite
the first person back by saying,
(chanting): "Hot boiled beans
and bacon for supper,
hurry up before it gets cold."
If you people think this is
better than Tom Hanks-giving,
you're all crazy.
Sync, corrected by elderman
@elder_man
www.tvsubtitles.net