Sheldon, it's not a great time!
What do you want?
Hello to you, too.
I'm sorry,
but this is important.
What is it?
Back to the Future II was
in the Back to the Future III
case...
and Back to the Future III
was-- get this--
in the Back to the Future II
case.
So?
So, did you do that, or am I
in the house with an intruder?
Sheldon, I got to go inside.
It's getting rough out here.
You're dodging the question;
I knew it was you.
What was that?
What was what?
This isn't
a very good connection,
but it sounded like someone
just released a kraken.
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
You know there's
no such thing as a...
No...!
Penny... Penny...
Penny...!
What's the matter?
Um... well, I was worried
that you might be
missing Leonard.
And that might be causing
you to have bad dreams,
like the kind you'd get if you
watched Clash of the Titans
right before you went to bed.
Sweetie, did you have
a bad dream?
To be honest, I did.
Aw.
Back to the Future II was
in the Back to the
Future III case.
Leonard did it.
Good night.
No, wait.
Perhaps I should sleep here
so you don't miss
Leonard as much,
uh, 'cause you're being
kind of a baby about it.
You know what?
That would make me feel better.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Good night.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
I think you'd be
pleased to hear
that this morning in
the parking garage,
I saw this oil
stain on the ground
that was shaped just like
my ex-girlfriend, Lucy,
and I didn't get upset at all.
I'm proud of you.
Well, you should be,
'cause she was looking good.
Dear Lord!
You're an astronomer.
Although you may
have earthly woes,
get your mind back
on the stars.
Gee, even the lowly
dung beetle
chooses to plot its course
by using the Milky Way.
Is that true?
Everything I say is true.
Now, of course,
the dung beetle also enjoys
eating feces, living in feces
and making little
balls out of feces.
So pick and choose which
aspects of its lifestyle
you want to embrace.
Come on,
you can talk to girls now.
It shouldn't be hard for you
to meet someone new.
How can I meet someone new
when everywhere I look,
I see Lucy's face?
Tell me you don't see her smile
in the crust
of this chicken pot pie.
Oh, will you stop it!
Now, listen to me.
There's a welcome party
for incoming post-docs tonight.
Go to it and meet someone
who isn't made of grease or pie.
You think you're so cool
because your wife is a person?
Look,
Bernie's at a neuroscience
conference with Amy--
I'll go with you.
You would do that for me?
Of course.
You're my friend.
I want you to be happy.
Thanks. Oh, Sheldon,
since Amy's out of town,
would you like to join us?
I want you to be happy, too,
but not enough
to do anything about it.
Howie, stop.
I can't talk like that.
Amy's right here.
Sheldon, stop.
For the last time,
I will not bring home bed bugs.
The hotel's nice.
There's a pool, a gym--
the bar looks like fun.
Because I looked in the bed,
and there are no bugs.
Aw, I love you, too.
If I don't talk to you
before you go to sleep,
I'll meet you in dreamland.
Good night.
No, I will not consider sleeping
in my garment bag.
Penny, did you ever wonder
how Starfleet captains...
No.
Well, now that I've piqued
your interest,
welcome to the exciting world
of 3D chess.
Why don't you just admit
you only want to play this game
because you always
play it with Leonard
and you miss him?
You overestimate
his significance in my life.
Oh...
Do I miss
how he makes a face
on my toaster waffle
with syrup?
No.
Do I miss the way
he fixes the zipper on my jacket
when it gets stuck?
I don't think so.
Do I miss how
we say "good night"
to each other through the walls
of our bedroom
using Morse code?
Okay, I get it, I get it.
You are an emotionless robot.
Well, I try.
All right, let's just get
this stupid game over with.
Great. I'll go first.
Okay.
By the way,
how are you with zippers?
Why?
Well, I really need
to go to the bathroom,
and this one's gone
all cattywampus.
Wow, your work on
jellyfish neural nets
sounds so interesting.
It is.
You can download my paper
off the university server.
I will. You can
download my paper
on the Van Allen Belts from the
university server as well.
I will.
All right.
How'd it go?
Well, if you like dry,
factual statements
interspersed with painful
moments of silence,
it was bananas.
Check it out.
Mrs. Davis from Human
Resources is here.
She's probably on the lookout
for sexual harassment.
Oh, great.
There go my chances
of being sexually harassed.
I heard her husband left her
for a hot, young undergrad.
That's so much better
than the old, ugly ones.
Mr. Wolowitz,
Dr. Koothrappali.
Mrs. Davis,
nice to see you.
You know, I recently read
a fascinating article
on infidelity among penguins.
Okay.
So if the fact
that your husband left you
makes you feel unattractive,
just remember,
penguins get cheated on,
and they're adorable.
It was better when you
couldn't talk to women.
I was thinking of going
to the lecture
on posterior cingulate
cortex lesions
in the formation
of autobiographical memory.
Oh, brain lesions
are fascinating.
Unless they're yours,
then they're a drag.
To the advancement of science.
And to the sick and dying
who make it possible.
This is fun; we never
really get to talk shop
with Penny around.
We usually just end up
talking about boys.
Which is fine,
but it's nice to mix it up
with a little intellectual
conversation.
From the two gentlemen
at the bar.
Oh, my gosh, boys
bought us drinks!
Boys bought us drinks!
Thank you, thank you,
thank you so much.
Be cool.
You be cool!
Guys are hitting on us, and
not just to get to Penny.
You're right.
Thank you.
Ooh! Bad move.
Really? Why?
My queen can now take your rook
from below.
So that means I lose, right?
It's over!
If I make this move...
but I won't because we're having
too much fun.
Okay, let's take a break.
We're all out of alcohol.
I wasn't going to get alcohol.
Gosh, I wonder what
Leonard's doing right now.
I miss him so much.
Well, if you'd like,
we could call him.
I-I mean that
you could call him.
As I've explained,
the absence of my friends
does not cause me pain.
As rock and roll bad boy,
Paul Simon, once said,
"I am a rock.
I am an i-i-i-island."
I'm calling him.
Oh, goodie!
Put him on speakerphone!
Excuse me, ladies,
but my pants are buzzing.
North Sea, how can I "kelp" you?
Leonard?
Penny?
Hey, it's Penny.
Everybody say hi to Penny.
Hi, Penny!
Wow, it sounds like
you're having a good time.
Best time of my life!
Isn't it 5:30
in the morning there?
Is it?
Hey, everybody,
it's 5:30 in the morning!
Uh...
okay, well,
we were just calling you
because we were missing you.
Iceberg!
Uh-oh, hang on.
Are you in danger?
No, it's a drinking game.
Whenever we see an iceberg,
we take a shot!
Berg! Berg!
Berg! Berg! Berg! Berg--
Leonard, Leonard?
I cannot believe we were
missing that jerk.
You were.
So what happened?
How'd it go?
It's fine. I thanked them again
and let them know
we're not available.
So I can drink this
without having
to give up the goodies?
Yes, it's all cool.
Although, if you wanted
to talk to one of them,
no one would blame you.
And why would no one
blame me?
I don't know
what I'm saying.
Well, it sounds
like you're saying
that I could do better
than Sheldon.
Boy, these drinks are strong!
Hoo, mama, I'm gonna be gginhu !
No, tell me,
I want to know
what you meant by that.
I just meant
that you're not married
and your boyfriend's kind of...
Sheldon.
And your husband
is extremely Howard.
What's your point?
Sorry.
I have no point.
That was a stupid thing
to say.
Can we please just go back
to having a nice time?
We could, but unfortunately
my brain is lesion-free
and I remember that
rotten thing
you just said about
my sweet baboo.
Come on. I apologize.
Can we please
just let it go?
Sure.
Thanks.
Your husband's weird
and his clothes are ridiculous.
I can't believe it!
All this time
I've been doing nothing
but sit around
and miss that guy.
And you know what
the worst part is?
That you're having to process
your emotional pain
without vodka?
No.
Yes.
But you know what
the second-worst part is?
He does not miss me at all.
Allow me to comfort you.
At least you've got your health.
Really? Tha-That's it?
That's comforting?
Um, uh, in a hundred years,
you'll both be dead
and it won't matter?
No! Come on!
You're supposed to say,
"Of course he misses you.
The only reason he's partying is
to cover up his pain."
Oh, no, I don't think
that's true at all.
This is ridiculous.
Why am I upset just because
he's off having a good time?
Well... perhaps you're
obsessively picturing him
engaged in drunken coitus
with another woman.
Is that it?
Did I get it right?
Okay, tha-that's great.
You can stop trying to make me
feel better now.
Actually, I can't.
Before Leonard left,
he made me promise
that I'd take care of you.
He did?
Yes.
Oh, that's really sweet.
Plus, if I do a good job,
he said he'd bring me back
a sailor's cap.
Now I miss him even more.
Well, if it's any consolation,
I'm sure Leonard's tormented
every moment he's away from your
warm embrace and cherry lips.
Thanks.
Oh, seriously?
Uh, excuse me, Mrs. Davis?
What?
I'd like to apologize
for being insensitive.
And for possibly making penguins
seem like jerks,
'cause 99% of them
are stand-up guys.
Forget about it.
You know, you-you and I,
you and I have a lot in common.
Is that right?
Oh, yes, I-I, too,
am in the throes of heartbreak.
Okay, fine,
I'll tell you about it.
Here is a hot beverage
to comfort you.
It's in a to-go cup.
Make of that
what you will.
Come on. It's still early.
Let's do something.
Well, I have been toying around
with an idea for 4-D chess.
How about we just talk?
All right.
In 4-D chess...
No.
Come on, let's talk
about our lives.
Tell me something
about you I don't know.
Hmm.
I own nine pairs of pants.
Okay, that-that's a good start,
but I was thinking
maybe something
a little more personal.
I see.
Hmm.
I own nine pairs
of underpants.
How about I go first?
But I don't want to know
how many underpants you own.
Although, based on the floor
of your bedroom,
I'd say it's a thousand.
Okay, look, here's something
people do not know about me.
When I first moved out
to L.A.,
I did a topless scene
in a low-budget horror movie
about a killer gorilla.
Ugh! After I did it,
I felt so ashamed.
Thankfully, that thing
never came out.
I've seen that.
Yeah. Serial Apeist.
Howard found it online
the day we met you.
Oh, God...
And it was literally
the moment you walked
out the door.
But I see the type of personal
revelations you're going for.
Okay, here's one I thought
I'd take to the grave.
Okay.
Hmm.
A while back,
YouTube changed
its user interface
from a star-based rating system
to a thumbs-up rating system.
I tell people I'm okay with it,
but I'm really not.
That's your big revelation?
Yes.
Whew! I feel ten pounds lighter.
Okay, you know what?
I give up.
I'm going to bed.
Here's something else
you don't know about me:
you just hurt my feelings.
What did I do?
I opened up and shared something
deeply upsetting to me,
and you treated it
as if it were nothing.
I-I didn't think
it was a big deal.
It is to me; that's the point.
Sheldon, you are right.
I'm really sorry.
I should've known better.
Your apology is accepted.
Thank you.
How about a hug?
How about a hearty handshake?
Come on.
Now I know how you felt
getting mauled
by that sex-crazed
gorilla.
Good night.
Mm-hmm.
It was rather flattering to have
strangers send us drinks.
Yeah, that felt nice.
Maybe tomorrow morning
we put on some hot pants
and see if we can score us
some free omelets.
So, hypothetically, if-if we
were to have gone with them,
which one would you have picked?
I think I would
have gone with the short one
with the goofy haircut.
Oh, good, 'cause I liked
the tall thin one.
He seemed intelligent,
kind of a loner,
maybe a little sexually
inexperienced,
like I'd have to teach
him a thing or two.
Not my guy.
I caught him staring
at my rack.
It'd be nice to be with a man
who wants to know
what's underneath my cardigan.
FYI, it's another cardigan.
Your short sexed-up guy
kind of sounds like Howard.
Your brainy virgin kind
of sounds like Sheldon.
Good night.
Night.
All right, Dr. Koothrappali,
it's been nice talking to you,
but I need to go home
and relieve my babysitter.
Yeah, I can relate
to being a single parent.
I have a dog.
Yeah, it's exactly
the same thing.
Good night.
Mrs. Davis...
I, uh, I must confess,
I came here tonight
in a futile attempt
to pick up some lonely postdoc,
but instead I got to connect
with you at a human level.
That's a much better evening.
You're a lovely person.
Are you hitting on me?
No, no, no, that would be crazy!
I mean, if I were hitting
on you, you'd know it
'cause you'd feel uncomfortable
and a little sad for me.
You're sweet.
Good night, Dr. Koothrappali.
Good night.
Looks like she accepted
your apology.
And then some.
I think we had a moment.
Oh, please, you did not
have a moment.
Who died and
made you king of moments?
Okay, fine. Let's say
there was a moment.
There was.
There wasn't.
But... But even if there was,
what are you gonna do about it?
I will slowly seduce her until
she falls helpless into my bed,
hungry for the pleasure
only I can give her.
So nothing.
No, not a thing.
Ah...
I'm so glad the police
finally caught
that psychotic
genetically engineered ape.
That is my girlfriend!
I swear to God!
Leonard! Leonard!
www.tvsubtitles.net