Whatcha doin' there?
Working on a new plan
to catch the roadrunner?
The humorous implication being
that I am Wile E. Coyote?
Yes.
And this is a schematic
for a bird-trapping device
that will ultimately backfire
and cause me physical injury?
Yes.
(quick chuckle)
What I'm doing here
is trying to determine
when I'm going to die.
A lot of people are working
on that research.
So what is all this?
My family history
factoring in longevity,
propensity for disease,
et cetera.
Interesting.
Cause of death for
Uncle Carl was KBB.
What's "KBB"?
"Killed by badger."
How's that?
It was Thanksgiving.
Uncle Carl said, "I think
"there's a badger living
in our chimney.
Hand me that flashlight."
Those were the last words
he ever spoke to us.
I don't think you need
to worry about death by badgers
being hereditary.
Not true.
The fight or flight instinct
is coded genetically.
Instead of fleeing, he chose
to fight barehanded
against a brawny member
of the weasel family.
Who's to say that I don't share
that flawed DNA?
You can always get a badger
and find out.
(quick chuckle)
But seriously,
even if I disregard
the Uncle Carl factor,
at best I have 60 years left.
That long, huh?
60 only takes me to here.
I need to get to here.
What's there?
The earliest estimate
of the singularity,
when man will be able
to transfer his consciousness
into machines
and achieve immortality.
So, you're upset
about missing out
on becoming some sort of
freakish self-aware robot?
By this much.
Tough break.
You want eggs?
You don't get it, Leonard.
I'm going to miss so much--
the unified field theory,
cold fusion, the dogapus.
What's a dogapus?
The hybrid dog and octopus.
Man's underwater best friend.
Is somebody
working on that?
I was going to.
I planned on giving it to myself
on my 300th birthday.
Wait a minute.
You hate dogs.
A dogapus can play fetch
with eight balls.
No one can hate that.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
The Big Bang Theory 4x0
The Cruciferous Vegetable Amplification
Original Air Date on September 30, 2010
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
What do we owe you?
It came to $28.17.
Let's say six bucks apiece.
Here you go.
Thank you.
What?
Never mind. I got it.
Oh, you wanted me to pay.
It's no big deal.
No, no, no, no.
You're right.
We're not going out anymore;
I should pay for myself.
(both snickering)
What?
He said, "If he had
woman parts,
he'd eat for free
the rest of his life""
Yeah, but you wouldn't be able
to talk to yourself.
I'm a little low on cash.
How much you got?
Nothing.
How can you walk
around with no money?
I'm cute. I get by.
It's okay,
you can owe me.
Thank you.
Sheldon, six bucks.
No, thank you.
I'm not eating pizza tonight.
But it's Thursday.
Thursday's pizza night.
Not for me.
Thursday is now Cruciferous
Vegetable Night.
Tonight's selection:
Brussels sprouts.
Really?
You're changing the
Sheldonian calendar?
It's a small price to pay.
For what?
No, no, don't ask.
Sorry, sorry, sorry,
sorry, sorry.
In order to live long enough
to fuse my consciousness
with cybernetics,
I need to change my diet.
Wait. Cybernetics is
robot stuff, right?
Correct.
So you want to turn yourself
into some sort of robot?
Essentially, yes.
Okay, here's my question.
Didn't you already do that?
No.
Flattering, but sadly, no.
I'm also planning
to begin an exercise regimen
designed to strengthen
my cardiovascular system.
AKA jogging.
Wait. Honey,
have you ever run before?
Certainly.
I've run from bullies, dogs,
angry chickens...
and one particularly
persistent P.E. teacher
determined to bend me over
and give me a scoliosis test.
You're right.
Penny jogs.
Maybe you guys
can run together.
That's an excellent idea.
Yeah, if we chat,
it will create the illusion
of time going faster.
No, it won't.
Um, how does he know I jog?
Oh, he watches you from his car
with high-powered binoculars.
Oh, my God, that is so creepy!
I know!
And he says he's
not gonna stop.
Then see a shrink
and figure out how
to talk to women.
(knocking)
(Sheldon groans)
(knocking continues)
(groans)
(knocking)
(loud groan)
What the hell?
What's the matter?
I have pain radiating
from my navel
to my lower right abdomen.
I'm nauseated
and feverish.
I believe I may have cholera.
There's no cholera
in Pasadena.
Just like last summer,
when there
was no malaria
in Pasadena.
Well, if it's not cholera,
then based on a quick
Internet search,
the other explanations in
decreasing order of likelihood
are Hirschsprung's Disease,
botulism, a 30-foot tapeworm
or accidental ingestion
of chrysanthemum blossoms.
When would you have accidentally
eaten chrysanthemum blossoms?
It's part of an
unlikely scenario
that involves sleepwalking
and a 24-hour flower mart
with a less-than-
vigilant proprietor.
Oh, Lord, my belly!
Ever had your
appendix out?
I haven't.
I've been meaning to,
but who has the time?
Let's get you
to the hospital.
So this is how it ends...
with cruel irony.
Just as I make the commitment
to preserving my body,
I am betrayed by my appendix,
a vestigial organ.
Do you know
the original purpose
of the appendix, Leonard?
No.
I do. And yet I'm doomed
while you live on.
Funny how things
work out, isn't it?
Oh, Lord, I think
it's about to burst!
(loud fart)
On the other hand,
it might have been
the Brussels sprouts.
Good night.
(door closes)
Appendicitis.
What a nervous Nelly.
Penny! Penny!
Penny!
Coming, coming.
Hey, nice knees.
Thank you.
They're my mother's.
Oh.
And the Flash
shirt is what?
Because, what,
you're gonna run really fast?
No, the Flash shirt is
because it's Friday,
but it's nice when
things work out.
Where's your
heart rate monitor?
I don't have one.
What about your pedometer?
Don't have one.
Do you have telematics
in your shoes connected
to an iPod?
Uh, no.
What do you do,
you just go out there
and gambol about
like a bunny?
No. I just run till I'm hungry,
then I stop for a bear claw.
Why are you doing that?
It's good to stretch your
muscles before you run.
All right.
All right,
let's start with a toe touch.
(exhales)
Okay, you do it.
I am doing it.
Oh. Wow. Good job.
Okay, um,
can you do this?
We'll never know.
Okay, let's just warm up
on the run.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
I've been reading up
on biomechanics.
I think you'll be
surprised at my...
(both yell
and tumbling down stairs)
PENNY:
Oh, my God,
are you okay?
SHELDON:
I think so.
Oh, let me
help you up.
Thank you.
(loud fart)
Oh, Sheldon!
If it makes you
feel any better,
Thursday is no longer
Cruciferous Vegetable Night.
Here's my chicken curry.
Howard, your
shrimp biryani.
Thank you, sir.
Palak paneer,
that's Penny.
Thanks.
And for Rajesh
Koothrappali,
from whose homeland
these tasty dishes originate,
one large order of
chicken McNuggets.
Hey, what's my share?
Uh... 12 bucks.
Okay, can I get you after Friday
when I get paid?
Sure.
What am I up to now?
Well, okay, with
the Indian food, the pizza,
the Thai food, the tank of gas,
the frozen yogurt
and your rent, uh...
a little over $1,400.
(both snickering)
What now?
He's just expressing
his admiration that
you don't even have to
put out to get free stuff.
It's not free-- I'm
gonna pay him back.
(snickering)
Shut up!
Sheldon, are you gonna join us?
Coming!
Greetings, friends.
Greetings, whatever
the hell you are.
I am a mobile
virtual presence device.
Recent events
have demonstrated to me
that my body is too fragile
to endure the vicissitudes
of the world.
Until such time as I am able
to transfer my consciousness,
I shall remain
in a secure location
and interact with the world
in this manner.
Really? That's
your question--
when did he
put a ramp in?
You're in my spot.
This may seem a little odd
at first,
but over time,
you'll grow accustomed
to dealing with me
in this configuration.
Yeah, to be honest, I
don't see much difference.
Thank you.
That's what I was going for.
Now, Leonard, tomorrow,
when we go to work,
you'll need to allow
some extra time
to get me down the stairs.
For your convenience,
I disassemble into four pieces.
This is ridiculous.
I'm coming to talk to you.
(stammers)
You don't know where I am.
My physical body
is safely ensconced
in a secure,
undisclosed location.
You're in your bedroom.
No, I'm not.
I can hear your voice
coming from your bedroom.
(softly):
No, you can't.
Wait.
Come back.
Halt.
Authorized personnel only!
So, either one
of you weirdos
want to buy my underwear?
Only 1,400 bucks.
Sheldon,
this is ridiculous.
I'm behind you.
Please look at me when
you're talking to me.
I am looking at you.
No, you're not.
Pay no attention to
that man in the bed.
You cannot exist
as a virtual presence.
Not here
and certainly not at work.
Oh, good God.
At my age,
do you know
how I'm statistically
most likely to die?
At the hands of your roommate?
An accident.
That's how I'm going
to make it look.
Until I can transfer
my intellect
to a more durable container,
my body will remain
safely ensconced in my bed.
Fine, but don't expect my help.
You have to help--
it's in the roommate agreement.
No, it's not.
Section 74.C.
The various obligations
and duties of the parties
in the event one of
them becomes a robot.
I'll be damned.
This is delightful.
Uh-huh.
It's much easier to enjoy
the picturesque route
we travel to work
when you remove the specter
of fiery vehicular death.
Refresh my memory.
Why didn't I just put you
in the trunk?
Because I called shotgun.
Remember?
Right.
You seem tense.
Perhaps this will relax you.
(peaceful recorder music
playing)
I don't want to listen
to music, Sheldon.
Very well.
I don't understand
why you're not enjoying this.
Together, in this car,
with my enhanced capabilities,
we're like Knight Rider.
Except in Knight Rider, the car
isn't a yammering sphincter.
You mock the sphincter,
but the sphincter
is a class of muscle
without which human beings
couldn't survive.
There are over 50
different sphincters
in the human body.
How many can you name?
I was wrong-- this is exactly
like Knight Rider.
Perhaps you'd be interested
in a different game.
No.
This is a photograph of the 1911
Solvay Conference on the theory
of radiation and quanta.
Using Photoshop, I've
introduced a few anachronisms.
See if you can spot all 24.
I'll give you the first one.
Madame Curie should not
be wearing a digital watch.
And go.
(Jeopardy! theme playing
over recorder)
That's it. Bye-bye.
(music stops)
Bazinga.
Whoa!
(tires screeching, horn honking)
I have an override switch.
I almost died!
And I'm safe and sound in bed.
Who's crazy now?
I'm still going
to go with you.
Hello, Professor Hoskins.
Nice to see you, Mindy.
And konnichiwa, Dr. Nakamora.
Sorry the Swedes
disproved your theory.
Leonard, my door.
What about it?
Be a lamb and open it for me.
Why? What's the problem?
You think you have me stymied,
don't you?
No, I think a doorknob
has you stymied.
Oh, look, it's Leonard
and R2-D-Bag.
That's my joke.
I told it last night.
You can't just use it.
Raj, be a lamb
and open the door for me.
Oh, sure.
He's a lamb.
You're not.
I'm a lamb.
Isn't this nice?
The pleasures of fellowship
and camaraderie
without having to tolerate
your germy breath on my skin.
I say we just take him
to Tatooine
and sell him to some Jawas.
That's two, dude.
Write your own jokes.
Oh, great.
(clears throat)
Hi, I'm Penny,
I'll be your waitress.
Why are you introducing
yourself?
I'd rather people not know
I have any prior connection
to you whatsoever.
Can you tell me
the specials this evening?
Sheldon, I'm not waiting on you.
Obviously.
I don't even have
water yet.
Because you're not here.
That's discrimination
against the otherwise located.
I'm going to have
to go over your head.
Manager... manager.
Oh, Lord,
look who it is.
Is that Steve Wozniak?
I think it is.
The Great and Powerful Woz.
Penny,
Steve Wozniak was
one of the cofounders
of Apple Computer.
He and Steve Jobs started it...
Yeah,
I know who he is.
I watch Dancing with the Stars.
I must speak to him.
Of course you must.
You know, there's an
Olive Garden down the street.
You guys should try it sometime.
Excuse me,
Mr. Wozniak?
Oh, hey.
Nice virtual presence device.
Thank you.
I just want to say
I'm a big fan.
You're my 15th favorite
technological visionary.
Only 15th?
It's still six spots
above Steve Jobs.
I care neither for turtlenecks
nor showmanship.
Yeah, I never got
that turtleneck thing.
One of my proudest possessions
is a vintage 1977 Apple Two.
Despite the file system
limitations of Apple DOS 3.3,
it was a pretty nifty
little achievement.
Thanks, we were shooting
for "nifty."
You know, if you had it here,
I'd autograph it for you.
Don't move
for 15 to 30 minutes,
depending on how
the buses are running.
Nerds.
(panting)
I'm coming, Woz, I'm coming.
(gasps)
Ow!
(clattering)
Oh!
(shattering)
Aw.
Penny... Penny... Penny.
What up, Shel-Bot?
I can't get out of bed.
I hurt my ankle.
What do you want me to do?
Sing me "Soft Kitty."
Really, you want me
to sing "Soft Kitty"
to a computer monitor?
Would you rather come over
and sing it to me in person?
♪ Soft kitty, warm kitty ♪
♪ Little ball of fur... ♪
Closer to the microphone.
♪ Happy kitty,
sleepy... ♪
No.
You have to start over.
♪ Soft kitty,
warm kitty ♪
♪ Little ball of fur ♪
♪ Happy kitty,
sleepy kitty ♪
♪ Purr, purr, purr. ♪
-- Sync, corrected by elderman --
-- for www.addic7ed.com --
www.tvsubtitles.net